<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>brawlstars-newsEntries-en</id>
  <title>Brawlstars - News</title>
  <updated>2025-01-03T02:59:02.630850+00:00</updated>
  <link href="https://github.com/skrwo/supercell-inbox-rss/"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="1.0.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <subtitle>RSS wrapper of Brawlstars inbox News</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>7mbdhGMIuxgANUhIvnrXct</id>
    <title>Trophy Season Rework is Coming!</title>
    <updated>2024-10-16T18:56:47.382000+00:00</updated>
    <content>&lt;p&gt;It’s that time of the year when we rework a whole system again! This time, it’s the Trophy Season Reset!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;What are the main problems with this system?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s unnecessarily complex and not fun&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;On top of that, the rewards suck!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;It discourages players from using their favorite Brawlers (because at one point it becomes too hard to push them)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Also the matchmaking times get too long at high Trophy matches
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Our goals with the new system are:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Make the system clearer (not necessarily simpler) and fun!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Make it more welcoming to casuals, but also more meaningful for ladder warriors &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Make it more rewarding and therefore more engaging&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Remove the friction from playing high Trophy Brawlers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, here’s all that is changing:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;We are adding more Tiers and making the system clearer and more rewarding!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/5h4eQqyBWGwTRtotVgEFS2/257b9151dbda80e96ac9f808121880b2/icon_season_trophy_800x450.png?w=800&amp;h=300&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A lot of things are changing this time, so it might be hard to compare the old system vs the new, but in summary, the new Trophy Season system should be more intuitive and more rewarding, all for the same amount of effort you currently put into the game.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are now 50 Tiers in total. The top Tier is now called Max!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;To reach Max Tier with a Brawler you will need 1000 Trophies&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the new system, you will progress a Tier every 20 Trophies&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trophy gain and loss will be adjusted to fit better with the new system and be more forgiving under 1000 Trophies&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;You’ll only start losing more Trophies than you win after 1100 Trophies&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trophy Season will start and end at the same time as the Brawl Pass season&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The now monthly Trophy Season reset will always reset all Brawlers back to 1000 Trophies&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;There’s no Trophy reset for any Brawler below 1000 Trophies&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So what happens after you reach 1000 Trophies?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;With 1000 Trophies you reach the highest Tier available (Max)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Trophies you get after 1000 will still be counted but now they become &lt;b&gt;Season Trophies&lt;/b&gt; and they help you progress towards a new item, &lt;b&gt;THE TROPHY BOX!&lt;/b&gt; (more on that below!)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The base level Trophy Box also unlocks for everyone who has at least 1500 total Trophies, but you can only progress it further with Brawlers above 1000 Trophies&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;New Reward: The Trophy Box!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/6J9fVVvKqwnb9I2FryKCbJ/38ce02ca9cb8871e424e083ecd27310e/bling_box_legendary_3d_mockup.png?w=700&amp;h=700&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yes, it’s a new Box! Instead of just getting Bling at the end of each Season, you now get a Trophy Box!
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Trophy Box unlocks once you get a Brawler to 1000 Trophies or when you reach 1500 total Trophies&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Any Trophies gained above 1000 Trophies are now Season Trophies. Season Trophies level up your Trophy Box&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Trophy Box has 5 levels: Small, Big, Mega, Omega and Ultra - the bigger the Box, the better and more rewards you get&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tier upgrade rewards got removed but don’t worry, with the new system you will also be getting more Bling than before&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The contents of the Trophy Box are mainly cosmetics, including a guaranteed Skin and, depending on the level of the Box, it could also even contain a Mythic, Legendary, or Hypercharge Skin and Gems!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;amp;%^$ this text, look at the image below:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/1AQ1VBv4a1goHu3EgexRLp/b67b06ec058fd7080e1fbcaab17f86c0/info_popup.png?w=2660&amp;h=1498&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;But isn’t it grindy to get there?
&lt;/b&gt;- Yes, it is grindy to get the higher level Boxes, but if you play the same amount you are playing today, you’ll still be getting more rewards than before and skill should be taken more into account in the new system&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;Matchmaking!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/1miXHdHljokzu5n8WRZT2y/9c316a27d6ca24a0d23e80c2c86f0178/battle_end__1_.png?w=2666&amp;h=1500&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Everyone’s favorite topic! There are some changes to it, but mostly after 1000 Brawler Trophies:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Matchmaking will consider Brawler Trophies and will try to match players with a similar Trophy count&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;After 1000 Brawler Trophies, players will all be in the same matchmaking pool, this should help with matchmaking times in high Trophy Brawler matches&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;You only start losing more Trophies than you gain after 1100+ Brawler Trophies&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Underdog gets removed after 1000 Trophies&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Win Streaks will be tied to individual Brawlers to make Trophy pushing more fair&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The highest Win Streak record will still be kept in your profile&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;
But does this mean that the pros and the casuals will all be in the same pool after 1000 Brawler Trophies?
- Yes, but the number of pros is much, much, much smaller than the number of casuals, so it might happen, but it should be rare&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;Leaderboards!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the sweaty ones out there, we’ll have two leaderboards &lt;b&gt;per Brawler&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;A &lt;b&gt;Seasonal Leaderboard&lt;/b&gt; that gets reset every Season&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;An &lt;b&gt;All-Time Leaderboard&lt;/b&gt;, that tracks the highest Trophy count ever reached with that Brawler&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;For each time you make it to the Top and enter the Seasonal Leaderboard, you get a Prestige Icon for your profile. That icon then features a number that increases each time you place in the Top with at least one Brawler, once per Season&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/2GnwGMFKvgevknyQzOFj5u/21fd9d1456fbee742a45a30c071d154f/profile.png?w=2341&amp;h=1179&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How about previous Trophy records from before the rework?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;They will remain in the “All-Time Leaderboard” we mentioned above, until someone else beats them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;Previous Achievements!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/5Jk8P4t9x6IHJSv35iPeyq/c571655a65c32dfb046f73b9ecd9b371/emoji_og_35.png?w=677&amp;h=672&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If in the current system you have Brawlers at Tier 35, you might be wondering if it was all in vain. And the answer is… partly, but your achievements will LIVE FOREVER! &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Players that have had at least 1 Brawler at Tier 35, will get a unique Pin&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Players that have had at least 10 Brawlers at Tier 35, will get a new exclusive title, only available to those who achieved this feat before the rework&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Your all time high will be taken into account for this, so if you’ve had Brawlers at Tier 35 in previous Seasons, but not in the current one, that will still count!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The total number of Brawlers you ever had at Tier 35 will also be marked in your profile, so you can still use that to impress your mom&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the first Trophy Season reset after the update, every Brawler above 1000 Trophies will be reset back to 1000&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;When Will This Happen?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;A lot of the changes will be already happening on update day which is coming near the end of October!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you have a Brawler over 1000 Trophies you will already be able to add progress to your first Trophy Box that will drop with the Season Reset, right after the Scary Tales season ends on November 7!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;IMPORTANT!&lt;/b&gt; Take into account that some of the values mentioned here are not final and may change by the time the update releases!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And some smaller details and values might still change by the time the update releases but let us know your thoughts and questions on social media about these changes and if there are any big doubts we can address them in another post!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bye!&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/#/en/news/7mbdhGMIuxgANUhIvnrXct"/>
    <link href="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/NdMlWsmu3ZMJtwQgcP6Fh/d65a2a49e2c807bdda86fda3b822d108/1011_Trophy_Season_changes_800x433.png?w=800&amp;h=433&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"/>
    <category term="News"/>
    <published>2024-10-15T14:59:13+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>3m11hStMKajzs0h0foCrsu</id>
    <title>The Future of Brawl Stars in 2025!</title>
    <updated>2024-10-17T02:05:17.828000+00:00</updated>
    <link href="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/#/en/news/3m11hStMKajzs0h0foCrsu"/>
    <link href="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/170H92TK8tcG8S8ebQCE9z/5eb7073df0972faa3cde604c20cd9c65/Roadmap_Thumb-draft-03.jpg?w=800&amp;h=433&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"/>
    <link href="https://youtu.be/KHf4hb5iJhE"/>
    <category term="News"/>
    <published>2024-10-16T15:01:51+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>6lPj9ejyfc6JQ2OHWnAG6V</id>
    <title>Win 10 Dead Boxes in the #deadgame event!</title>
    <updated>2024-10-23T10:15:47.342000+00:00</updated>
    <content>&lt;h1&gt;How to get 10 Dead Boxes!!&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There’s a new Box: THE DEAD BOX! And you can get 10 of them for FREE in the #DeadGame event if the whole community reaches 20 billion Takedowns!!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;The #DeadGame event starts RIGHT NOW and ends on October 31st! &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;In a Dead Box you can find:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;- ALL the non-exclusive Brawl-O-Ween Skins (including the recently released Zombie Skins and 199 Gem Skins!)
- Brawl-O-Ween themed Pins, Profile Icons, and Sprays
- Coins, Star Powers, Gadgets, and Hypercharges! (no Power Points)
- Bling
- Gems
- And Brawlers!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;MORE REWARDS!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the way to 20 billion Takedowns, you can unlock more in-game events and a Hypercharge Starr Drop!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;- &lt;b&gt;Double Mastery&lt;/b&gt; &lt;b&gt;Madness&lt;/b&gt; event starting RIGHT NOW!
- At 5 billion Takedowns - &lt;b&gt;Double XP&lt;/b&gt;
- At 10 billion Takedowns - &lt;b&gt;HYPERCHARGE STARR DROP!!&lt;/b&gt;
- At 15 billion Takedowns - &lt;b&gt;Double daily Starr Drops&lt;/b&gt;
- At 20 billion Takedowns - &lt;b&gt;10 Dead Boxes for everyone!*&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;*The 10 Dead Boxes will only be delivered on October 31st even if the milestone is reached earlier.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;How to get 20 billion Takedowns?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Every Brawler you defeat in a match counts as a Takedown. If the whole community reaches 20 Billion Takedowns during the #DeadGame event, everyone will get 10 Dead Boxes. You can also DOUBLE your progress by playing the zombie-themed Game Modes (Zombie Brawl, Dead Weight and Zombie Plunder). Each takedown in these game modes counts as doubled!
They will be rotating daily throughout the #DeadGame event!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;SPECIAL GIVEAWAY!!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;During the event, 5 lucky players will be able to get ALL THE ITEMS from the Dead Box, including all Brawlers, Skins, and Resources by participating in this special giveaway!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To participate in the giveaway, post a screenshot or a video on social of you playing any of the zombie game modes and use the #DeadGame and #BrawlStars hashtags in your post!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the end of the event, on October 31st, we will pick 5 lucky winners and deliver the rewards directly!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;QUESTIONS YOU MIGHT HAVE!!!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Will the non-exclusive Brawl-O-Ween Skins also be available in the Shop?
&lt;/b&gt;A: Yes! All of them! The older ones with a discount and the new ones at full price&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Can I get more Dead Boxes?
&lt;/b&gt;A: We’ll have 10 for free if the milestone is reached, and if you would like to get more, there’ll also be more boxes for Gems in the Shop.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Will I know if I win the giveaway?
&lt;/b&gt;A: Yes, you’ll get a message in your game inbox. We won’t share the names of the winners publicly to respect their privacy. If they want to share they won, they are allowed to.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Is it true that Marzio has been dead for 100 years, and what we see now is a ghost of him?&lt;/b&gt;
A: Definitely &lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/#/en/news/6lPj9ejyfc6JQ2OHWnAG6V"/>
    <link href="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/5y3zMhRZyjyYvAh1HGwCs5/a4a6954310ed54a83fab22ce5eced1c9/1003_Brawl_is_Dead_Inbox_800x433.png?w=800&amp;h=433&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"/>
    <category term="Community"/>
    <published>2024-10-17T07:00:17+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>1wjRgpCFvWVCozwpWrcf8D</id>
    <title>How to get a free Legendary &amp; Hypercharge Starr Drop!</title>
    <updated>2024-10-29T05:10:35.507000+00:00</updated>
    <link href="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/#/en/news/1wjRgpCFvWVCozwpWrcf8D"/>
    <link href="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/3GLieOlpj4sXHwnTUlnlzq/ed879368ea74abb82e2b067c1c0bc1e6/BS_BSWF_2024_Thumb_Draft_01.jpg?w=800&amp;h=433&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"/>
    <link href="https://youtu.be/ZC-egC-ElAU"/>
    <category term="Community"/>
    <published>2024-10-28T10:21:18+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>2JfjjxnuG0fEhhzMGulYyC</id>
    <title>How to get all the Angelic and Demonic Drops!</title>
    <updated>2024-12-06T09:07:43.299000+00:00</updated>
    <content>&lt;h1&gt;Announcement (10th of November)&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;SPIKE IS BACK TO LIFE! 🤙&lt;/b&gt;

Also:
- Mico with the Demonfire ability should not leave a trail while in the air anymore
- Angel vs Demon modifiers are on for Spirit Wars and Heist again
- And Spirit Wars will be the next mode in the Contest tomorrow!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Announcement (8th of November)&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;b&gt;SPIKE IS DEAD! (but not for too long) 🌵❤️‍🩹&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;So:
- We are disabling Spike from the game until his exploit with Demonfire gets fixed
- We are trying a different way to fix it that doesn&amp;#39;t require maintenance but it requires the rotation of every server we have live. This means that the fix is going to be released slowly as opposed to at the same time to all the players
- Once the fix is 100% deployed, we&amp;#39;ll activate Spike again (maybe in 2 or 3 days)
- For a similar reason with Mico, we are also removing the Angels VS Demons modifiers in Heist and Spirit Wars
- Demonfire will have its functionality reworked so it won&amp;#39;t cause as much damage to safe/turrets as now - this will also be slowly fixed in the next couple of days
- Spirit Wars also won&amp;#39;t be in Contest until we have maintenance to properly fix most of the issues with the new Angel and Demon abilities
- As compensation, we&amp;#39;ll deliver 3 Angelic and 3 Demonic Drops in the Shop for everyone after maintenance next week!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You have the chance to get the new DEMON MORTIS and ANGEL EDGAR Hypercharge Skins for free in the Angels vs. Demons Season!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Here’s how the season will go:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Every day at 09:00 UTC, you will flip the Coin of Fate to decide if you will become an Angel or a Demon for the day!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Your Daily Starr Drops will become Angelic or Demonic Drops depending on your fate!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Open Angelic or Demonic Drops to progress through the CODEX OF DOOM and unlock 12 unique Angel and Demon Abilities!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;You will get FREE WILL on the weekends which will allow you to pick your side for the day!
Compete with your new Abilities in brand-new Contests!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Get more Angelic and Demonic Drops by topping the Contest leaderboard&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new Contest will happen every 3 days, starting with the Season&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Keep opening Angelic &amp;amp; Demonic Drops until the end of the #AngelsVsDemons season for a chance of getting Demon Mortis, Angel Edgar, and all the other Demon and Angel Skins!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Angelic and Demonic Drops&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They are a new item that gives more progression resources (Coins/Power Points) than the average Starr Drop and the chance to unlock Angel and Demon Skins!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Every day the Coin of Fate will flip and will decide if you will be Angelic or Demonic for the day. This will define which kind of Starr Drops you will get. On weekends, you get Free Will to pick the side you want to be in. You then get to instantly open the Starr Drop of your side!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Once your fate has been decided, your Daily Starr Drops will be replaced by the new Angelic and Demonic versions. This will be the case during the whole Season (you can still earn normal Starr Drops from other places, such as the Brawl Pass or the Trophy Road).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To open them, you have to tap and hold the screen until completion. The longer it takes to open a Drop, the better the reward is going to be!

Angelic and Demonic Drops can give you:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Coins &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Power Points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gadgets&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Star Powers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hypercharges&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;XP Doublers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gems&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Credits (only as a fallback if you have all the Brawlers of a certain rarity)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brawlers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Skins related to the theme&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Angel and Demon cosmetics (Pins, Sprays, etc)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Angel and Demon Skins (including Demon Mortis and Angel Edgar)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can check all the drop rates of the Angelic and Demonic Drops in the table at the end of this article!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Angel and Demon Abilities and the CODEX OF DOOM!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For this season, a set of Angel and Demon Abilities will be given to all Brawlers! You can check them all in the CODEX OF DOOM (the book icon on the main screen). 
You can only use the Angelic Abilities on the Angelic day and the same goes for the Demonic Abilities. 
You can only use one ability at a time, so if you want to chose a different one, you have to equip it by accessing the CODEX OF DOOM! 
To unlock them, you must collect a set number of Angelic and Demonic Drops. It starts from 1 Starr Drop and increases as you unlock more abilities. Both bars work independently
They can only be used in Game Modes with the Angels Vs Demons modifier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where to get Angelic and Demonic Drops?
&lt;/b&gt;
You can get them from your Daily Starr Drops, weekend events, Contests, and from the Shop (1 Angelic and 1 Demonic Starr Drops for free in the Shop, and more for Gems).
If you play the whole Season and get all the possible Angelic and Demonic Drops available for free, you should end up with more than 100 Angelic and Demonic Drops (50 each). Here’s the breakdown:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;3 Daily Starr Drops, for 28 days = 84&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;2x Daily Starr Drops on 3 weekends = 18&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;9 Contests (happens every 3 days) = 0 to 180*&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;2 Shop Freebies (1 Angelic Starr Drop and 1 Demonic Starr drop)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Total: 104 to 284&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;*The number of Angelic/Demonic Starr Drops you get is based on your performance in the Contests. The higher you are, the more you get. &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;IMPORTANT: To unlock all Angelic and Demonic Power-Ups, you need in total 116 Starr Drops (58 for each side).&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;What is the CONTEST?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There’s a way to get more Angelic and Demonic Drops, but it requires some skill. Every day you will earn 5 tickets and will be able to compete in a leaderboard with other players. The better your performance, the more Angelic or Demonic Drops you get!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The contest happens in the new Angel Vs Demon Game Modes, only and you can practice the upcoming map before it moves to the Contest (it’s available to the left of the other normal Game Modes)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new Contest happens every 3 days, so use your tickets before the next one starts, otherwise you will lose your tickets!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Game Modes!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With this Season, we will have 3 Game Modes. (Soul Collector, Trio Showdown, Spirit Wars)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Soul Collector: &lt;/b&gt;
In Soul Collector, players will drop a soul each time they are defeated
The more souls you collect, the more points you get
You can defend your team&amp;#39;s dropped souls, and they will disappear after a certain time
The first team that collects 6 souls, or the one with the highest number of souls when the timer runs out, wins!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Trio Showdown:&lt;/b&gt;
It’s like Duo Showdown, but with 3 players, so it’s a Trio Showdown!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Spirit Wars:&lt;/b&gt;
Destroy the enemy defense turret! It’s a new type of Siege!
Collect Amulets to summon Spirits to a Battle (there are 3 Battles per match).
Amulets appear randomly around the middle of the map.
Grab an Amulet and hold it for a few seconds to activate it.
When a Battle starts, Spirits are summoned equal to the number of Amulets you have, to a maximum amount. If you collect more than the maximum, your Spirits grow stronger for every extra Amulet you have!
PRO GAMER TIP: Don’t attack the turret without Spirits to back you up!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;QUESTIONS!!!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Can I buy the Angel and Demon Skins directly?&lt;/b&gt;
A: Angel Edgar and Demon Mortis Hypercharge Skins are available as a fallback offer if you buy all the Angelic and Demonic Drops from the Shop and don’t get them and their color variations. All the other Angel and Demon Skins (and cosmetics) will be available for Gems (and Bling) after the Angels Vs Demons Season ends. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Can I get Angel Edgar and Demon Mortis after the Angel Vs. Demons Season ends?&lt;/b&gt;
A: Yes. They will be added to the Ultra Trophy Box in the December Update, and it might be available in other special events. These might change in the future, but that’s the current plan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Can I get all the Angel and Demon Abilities for free?&lt;/b&gt;
A: Yes, but it does rely A LITTLE BIT on your skill. If you lose all your matches in the Contest but collect everything else, you will end up with 104 Angelic/Demonic Drops. But this is the worst scenario possible. If you get some wins in the Contest should be enough for you to get all 116 Angelic/Demonic Drops required to complete the CODEX OF DOOM!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Angelic Drop Chances&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;table&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Reward&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Chance&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;100 Coins&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;27.06%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;200 Coins&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;3.25%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;500 Coins&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;1.08%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;1000 Coins&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;0.11%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;100 Bling&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;16.23%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;250 Bling&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;2.71%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;500 Bling&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;1.08%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;1000 Bling&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;0.11%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;200 XP Doublers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;16.23%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;2000 XP Doublers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;0.11%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;50 Power Points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;5.41%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;100 Power Points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;2.16%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;200 Power Points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;1.08%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;1000 Power Points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;0.11%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;100 Gems&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;0.11%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Random Gadget&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;0.76%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Random Star Power&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;0.54%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Random Hypercharge&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;0.32%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Random Rare Brawler&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;1.08%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Random Super Rare Brawler&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;0.76%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Random Epic Brawler&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;0.43%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Random Mythic Brawler&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;0.22%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Random Legendary Brawler&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;0.11%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Angelic Pin&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;4.33%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Angelic Spray&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;6.49%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Angelic Player Icon&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;4.33%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Angel Max Skin&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;0.43%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Angel Gene Skin&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;0.43%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Light Angel Blue Colt Skin&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;0.43%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bell Nani Skin&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;0.43%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stara Skin&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;0.43%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unicorn Bonnie Skin&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;0.43%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dionysus Angelo Skin&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;0.43%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nightmare Sandy Skin&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;0.43%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dark Angel Edgar Skin&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;0.11%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lightbearer Edgar Skin&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;0.11%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nightbringer Edgar Skin&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;0.11%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Demonic Drop Chances&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;table&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Reward&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Chance&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;100 Coins&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;27.29%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;200 Coins&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;3.28%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;500 Coins&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;1.09%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;1000 Coins&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;0.11%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;100 Bling&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;16.38%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;250 Bling&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;2.73%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;500 Bling&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;1.09%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;1000 Bling&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;0.11%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;200 XP Doublers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;16.38%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;2000 XP Doublers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;0.11%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;50 Power Points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;5.46%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;100 Power Points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;2.18%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;200 Power Points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;1.09%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;1000 Power Points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;0.11%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;100 Gems&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;0.11%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Random Gadget&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;0.76%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Random Star Power&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;0.55%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Random Hypercharge&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;0.33%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Random Rare Brawler&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;1.09%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Random Super Rare Brawler&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;0.76%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Random Epic Brawler&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;0.44%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Random Mythic Brawler&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;0.22%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Random Legendary Brawler&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;0.11%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Demonic Pin&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;4.37%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Demonic Spray&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;6.55%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Demonic Player Icon&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;4.37%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Demon Willow&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;0.33%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Demon Otis&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;0.33%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Impie Colette&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;0.33%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Demon Emz&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;0.33%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Underworld Bo&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;0.33%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Crimson R-T&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;0.33%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dark Knight Draco&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;0.33%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Inferno Chuck&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;0.33%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Demon Mortis&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;0.11%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Devilish Mortis&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;0.11%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lambent Mortis&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;0.11%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/#/en/news/2JfjjxnuG0fEhhzMGulYyC"/>
    <link href="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/3APNUKD5kYF8MexBcsejqd/da6658bac583279ab8cc98be1cfd446f/1107_Season_start_800x433_v2.png?w=800&amp;h=433&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"/>
    <category term="Game Updates"/>
    <published>2024-11-07T09:08:38+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>2KtNTVzMPzrxuH3nQGMVj</id>
    <title>PATCH NOTES: Angels vs Demons</title>
    <updated>2024-12-04T09:25:51.808000+00:00</updated>
    <content>&lt;h1&gt;Maintenance - November 14th&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;FIXED: &lt;/b&gt;
▫️ Colt&amp;#39;s mad behavior with the Smite Ability
▫️ Doug&amp;#39;s Super charges with the Revengeance Ability
▫️ Clancy level charge with the Demonfire Ability
▫️ Players unlocking duplicated Abilities in the Codex of Doom
▫️ Contest Leaderboard showing incorrect player names
▫️ Minor localisation fixes
▫️ Replacement of Mad-Evil Showdown map, due to performance issues

&lt;b&gt;Balance and General Changes 🛠️&lt;/b&gt;

&lt;b&gt;MOE&lt;/b&gt;
Projectile speed (Main attack) - 3600 → 2800
Damage (Main attack) - 540 → 500

&lt;b&gt;KENJI&lt;/b&gt;
Star Power &amp;quot;Nigiri Nemesis&amp;quot; (shield) - 90% → 60%
Super charge from Super - 100 → 65

&lt;b&gt;LARRY&lt;/b&gt;
Health points 3000 → 2800

&lt;b&gt;SURGE&lt;/b&gt;
Hypercharge rate - 30% → 20%

&lt;b&gt;GALE&lt;/b&gt;
Super charge from Basics - 90 → 80 (4 → 5 attacks)

&lt;b&gt;CHARLIE&lt;/b&gt;
Damage (Basic attack) - 760 → 800

&lt;b&gt;ASH&lt;/b&gt;
Rage from getting hit - 150 → 180 (20%)

&lt;b&gt;SPIKE&lt;/b&gt;
Health points 2600 → 2800

&lt;b&gt;BROCK&lt;/b&gt;
Health points 2400 → 2700

&lt;b&gt;CLANCY&lt;/b&gt;
Damage at all ranks (Main attack) - 800 → Damage at Rank 1: 600, Rank 2: 700, Rank 3: 800 (unchanged)
Super damage at level 3 - 760 → 700

&lt;b&gt;FRANK&lt;/b&gt;
Damage (Main attack) - 1240 → 1160

&lt;b&gt;BYRON&lt;/b&gt;
Super charge rate - 10 ticks → 9 ticks (or 3 bullets)

&lt;b&gt;ALSO: &lt;/b&gt;
▫️ For the players who bought the Demonic and Angelic Drops in the Shop and didn&amp;#39;t get every Hypercharge Skins, the remaining ones will be available in the Shop with a discounted value (gems) until 1 week after the event ends!
▫️ We also fixed the Contest Leaderboard for players who were getting fewer Angelic/Demonic Drops than they should
▫️ We&amp;#39;ll now go through the list of every player affected by this issue and deliver the rewards they should have received. Unfortunately, we won&amp;#39;t be able to let each player decide what they would like to get, so we&amp;#39;ll split the Drops into 50% Angelic and 50% Demonic
▫️ The compensation will (hopefully) be delivered in the next couple of weeks!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Maintenance - October 31st&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Fixes:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixed Gadgets and Star Powers charging Supers;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixed weird behavior with Winstreak and Ranked&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixed all-time Global Leaderboard showing inaccurate data&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixed Byron healing other brawlers entities using his basic attack such as Pets and Turrets. The same behavior was happening with Pearl&amp;#39;s Gadget &amp;quot;Made With Love&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mandy&amp;#39;s projectile speed was nerfed around 10% from the current value and &amp;quot;In my sights&amp;quot; Star Power projectile speed: 16% → 15%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;(We might still see some weird behavior in the Leaderboards!)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;NEW BRAWLERS ✨&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;JUJU: Mythic - Artillery&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;
Juju owns the Oddities Shop and is followed everywhere by her “pet” voodoo doll, Gris-Gris (pronounced Gregory). Although she can control the elements, Juju is also a talented toymaker who makes dolls to sell to Starr Park&amp;#39;s many visitors.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;MAIN ATTACK: ELEMENTAL ENERGY&lt;/b&gt;
Juju throws projectiles empowered by the environment she is standing on, giving them different properties!
• Ground: More damage
• Grass: More range
• Water: Has a slowing effect

&lt;b&gt;SUPER: FROM THE OTHER SIDE&lt;/b&gt;
Juju summons Gris-Gris. This spooky voodoo doll drags itself to the nearest enemy and throws damaging needles at them.

&lt;b&gt;STAR POWER: GUARDED GRIS-GRIS&lt;/b&gt;
Gris-Gris is summoned with a protective shield.

&lt;b&gt;STAR POWER: NUMBING NEEDLES&lt;/b&gt;
Gris-Gris&amp;#39; attack now also slows the enemy for 1 sec.

&lt;b&gt;GADGET: VOODOO CHILE&lt;/b&gt;
Juju&amp;#39;s next main attack has the power of all three elements.

&lt;b&gt;GADGET: ELEMENTALIST&lt;/b&gt;
Juju gains a temporary buff based on the current environment she is standing on.
• Earth: Damage reduction
• Grass: Invisibility
• Water: Increased movement speed

&lt;b&gt;TRAIT:&lt;/b&gt; Juju can walk on water.

JUJU IS RELEASED ON &lt;b&gt;OCTOBER 30&lt;/b&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;SHADE: Epic - Assassin&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not much is known about this mysterious pile of clothes, other than the fact it has some cool sunglasses. Discovered by Gus, Shade was given a name and now the two spooky Brawlers haunt the Ghost Station together.

&lt;b&gt;MAIN ATTACK: HAUNTED HUG&lt;/b&gt;
Shade hugs its opponents with a wide embrace, accidentally dealing damage, and doing more damage to those caught in the center of the hug. It can also hug enemies through walls!

&lt;b&gt;SUPER: INCORPOREAL FORM&lt;/b&gt;
Shade leaves the physical world and can move directly through the environment. It also gains a movement speed boost.

&lt;b&gt;STAR POWER: SPOOKY SPEEDSTER&lt;/b&gt;
Hitting opponents with the center of Shade&amp;#39;s main attack gives a short movement speed boost.

&lt;b&gt;STAR POWER: HARDENED HOODIE&lt;/b&gt;
Shade gets 30% damage reduction while in its Incorporeal Form.

&lt;b&gt;GADGET: LONGARMS&lt;/b&gt;
The next main attack has 50% longer range.

&lt;b&gt;GADGET: JUMP SCARE&lt;/b&gt;
Shade spooks nearby enemies, slowing them for 4 seconds.

&lt;b&gt;TRAIT:&lt;/b&gt; Shade can travel over water.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;SHADE IS RELEASED ON &lt;b&gt;NOVEMBER 28&lt;/b&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;NEW HYPERCHARGES 🔥&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;(These will be released after the Brawl Stars World Finals, on November 4)&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;8-BIT: AIMBOT&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;8-Bit&amp;#39;s turret now has a laser that shoots nearby enemies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OTIS: SILENT STUNNER&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Super now also stuns for 1.5s on impact.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;RUFFS: THE GOODEST BOY&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ruffs&amp;#39; Super deals more damage and his power-up fully charges a Hypercharge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;DARRYL: BARREL O&amp;#39; BULLETS&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shoots his shotguns around himself during a Barrel Roll.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;PENNY: NEW LOBBER&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Penny deploys a bigger turret that shoots 2 cannonballs at a time instead of 1.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;STU: INFINITRO&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stu&amp;#39;s Super can be used continuously while Hypercharged.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hypercharge Skins will now keep their Hypercharged state until defeated, not just for the duration of the Hypercharge!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;NEW SEASON, NEW EVENT: 😇 ANGELS VS. DEMONS 😈&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Demons are invading Starr Park! Only Angels can stop them. Become an Angel or Demon, open Angelic &amp;amp; Demonic Drops, and get the chance to unlock the new DEMON MORTIS and ANGEL EDGAR Hypercharge Skins for &lt;b&gt;free&lt;/b&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here’s how the season will go:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Every day at 09:00 UTC, you will flip the Coin of Fate to decide if you will become an Angel or a Demon for the day!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Your Daily Starr Drops will become &lt;b&gt;Angelic &lt;/b&gt;or &lt;b&gt;Demonic Drops &lt;/b&gt;depending on your fate&lt;b&gt;!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Open Angelic or Demonic Drops to progress through the&lt;b&gt; CODEX OF DOOM&lt;/b&gt; and unlock 12 unique Angel and Demon &lt;b&gt;Abilities&lt;/b&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;You will get FREE WILL on the weekends which will allow you to pick your side for the day!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;New game modes: Spirit Wars &amp;amp; Soul Collector! Trio Showdown returns!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Compete with your new Abilities in brand-new Contests!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Get more Angelic and Demonic Drops by topping the Contest leaderboard&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new Contest will happen every 3 days, starting with the Season&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Keep opening Angelic &amp;amp; Demonic Drops until the end of the #AngelsVsDemons season for a chance of getting Demon Mortis, Angel Edgar, and all the other Demon and Angel Skins!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;More in-depth information will be revealed closer to the Season launch!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;REWORK: TROPHY RESET 🏆&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are now 50 Tiers in total. The top Tier is now called Max!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;To reach Max Tier with a Brawler you will need 1000 Trophies&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the new system, you will progress a Tier every 20 Trophies&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trophy gain and loss will be adjusted to fit better with the new system and be more forgiving under 1000 Trophies&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;There’s no Trophy reset for any Brawler below 1000 Trophies&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;With 1000 Trophies you reach the highest Tier available (Max)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Trophies you get after 1000 will still be counted but now they become &lt;b&gt;Season Trophies&lt;/b&gt; and they help you progress towards a new item, &lt;b&gt;THE TROPHY BOX!&lt;/b&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trophy Season will start and end at the same time as the Brawl Pass season&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The now monthly Trophy Season reset will always reset all Brawlers back to 1000 Trophies&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The base level Trophy Box also unlocks for everyone who has at least 1500 total Trophies, but you can only progress it further with Brawlers that have earned Season Trophies

&lt;b&gt;THIS IS A BIG ONE, SO READ THE FULL LIST OF CHANGES &lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%25253A%25252F%25252Fsupercell.com%25252Fen%25252Fgames%25252Fbrawlstars%25252Fblog%25252Fnews%25252Ftrophy-season-rework-is-coming%25252F')"&gt;&lt;b&gt;HERE&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;b&gt;!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;NEW SKINS 🎨&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;Season: Angels vs. Demons&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Angel Larry &amp;amp; Lawrie | Brawl Pass&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Radiant Larry &amp;amp; Lawrie | Chroma #1&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dark Angel Larry &amp;amp; Lawrie | Chroma #2&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Demon Mortis | Hypercharge | Gacha&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Devilish Mortis | Chroma #1&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lambent Mortis | Chroma #2&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dark Angel Edgar | Hypercharge | Gacha&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lightbearer Edgar | Chroma #1&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nightbringer Edgar | Chroma #2&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Light Angel Colt (Color Variation) | Epic&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Impie Colette (Color Variation) | Epic&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Demon Otis | Epic&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Demon Willow | Epic&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Demon Emz | Epic&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Angel Max | Epic&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Angel Lily | Ranked&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Angel Gene | Super Rare&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;Season: Starr Toon Studios 2&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bizarre Maisie | Brawl Pass&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Requiem Maisie | Chroma #1&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Platinum Maisie | Chroma #2&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Paper Cordelius | Legendary&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rude Lou | Mythic&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Be Less Ash | Super Rare&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sugarplum Rosa | Ranked&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;Miscellaneous skins&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rusty Otis | Rare &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;High Flyer Lola | Rare&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sous Chef Ruffs | Rare&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cinema Shade | Rare&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unlucky Juju | Rare&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;True Silver/Gold&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;True Gold Kenji&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;True Silver Kenji&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;True Gold Moe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;True Silver Moe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;True Gold Hank&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;True Silver Hank&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;BUG FIXES &amp; OTHER CHANGES ⚒️&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;FIXED: Lawrie will damage and defeat himself if he is active when Larry gets hexed by Willow’s Super&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;FIXED: If Amber is on top of a Brawler when triggering her Gadget &amp;quot;Dancing Flames&amp;quot; it will instantly do 3x the damage &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;FIXED: Clancy&amp;#39;s True Silver and True Gold skins do not have the Basic Attack animation for Stage 2 and Stage 3&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;FIXED: Club Chat messages are overflowing from the chat window when scrolling down&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;FIXED: Lou’s Super description does not state it does damage over time&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;FIXED: Nani’s Gadget &amp;quot;Warpin&amp;#39; Time&amp;quot; implies it does damage in the description&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;FIXED: Surge&amp;#39;s upgrades are labeled as &amp;#39;Level&amp;#39; instead of &amp;#39;Stage&amp;#39; in his Gadget and Hypercharge&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;FIXED: Mandy&amp;#39;s attack projectile speed in some of her Skins&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;FIXED: Lily remains stuck in the Shadow Realm when she defeats Cordelius after Cordelius uses his Hypercharged Super on her&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;FIXED: If Lily uses her Gadget &amp;quot;Vanish&amp;quot; before a teammate Cordelius defeats an enemy Brawler he used his Super on, Cordelius will remain in the Shadow Realm until Lily&amp;#39;s Gadget duration expires&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;R-T can now float over water during his Super&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brawlers who can do more damage with their main attack in certain scenarios will now show an orange number with “!” (for example, Draco). This will be expanded to all Brawlers in the future.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Club Trophy requirements can now be increased up to 100,000&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Inbox will now send a message summarizing your Mega Pig rewards&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;If all Club members are inactive, you will now receive recommendations for active Clubs&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Win-streaks are now per Brawler (after the update, your current win-streak will be transferred to your selected ‘favorite Brawler’)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mega Pig quests may show up during Mega Pig event&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ranked Points adjustment to make Masters more skill based: Lowered Ranked Point gain and minimum Ranked Point gain for Legendary III and Masters, and increased Ranked Point loss and minimum Ranked Point loss for Masters&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our test with ads (where certain players could watch ads to receive Starr Drops) is discontinued and players will no longer see any ads in the game for the foreseeable future&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/#/en/news/2KtNTVzMPzrxuH3nQGMVj"/>
    <link href="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/1OyN00be2dTFEqQZInvoiP/79a2a6b777ca34b31a2725d8db9aa205/1029_Update_800x433.png?w=800&amp;h=433&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"/>
    <category term="Game Updates"/>
    <published>2024-11-13T22:00:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>nSZBd0biUgnb3PpDzK4Z4</id>
    <title>To Brawl... AND BEYOND!</title>
    <updated>2024-12-06T13:41:39.734000+00:00</updated>
    <link href="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/#/en/news/nSZBd0biUgnb3PpDzK4Z4"/>
    <link href="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/7KKm0NlixRWGcEeWKNFkOy/f0dc634d844448489a443c0ef395d516/1206_Toy_Story_Animation_Teaser_v2.png?w=800&amp;h=433&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"/>
    <link href="https://youtu.be/PtutVHfyBx8"/>
    <category term="Video"/>
    <published>2024-12-06T13:14:40+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>6ISdhQB8e5PcfijYIx42TB</id>
    <title>Brawliversary and Brawlidays Events!</title>
    <updated>2024-12-20T07:43:14.464000+00:00</updated>
    <content>&lt;p&gt;Happy Birthday to all of us! It’s Brawl Stars’ 6th birthday since our global launch! &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So as always, we’ll celebrate from today, until the Brawlidays! Which means… PRESENTS!
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here’s what you should know about it!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Buzz Lightyear is available FOR FREE now in the Brawlidays Calendar (available in the Shop).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Complete Buzz Lightyear’s Space Ranger Mastery Track before he leaves the game!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mega Tree event! Join a club, use your tickets, and collect Presents to open it on December 25th.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;BUZZ LIGHTYEAR HAS LANDED IN BRAWL STARS!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can collect Buzz Lightyear FOR FREE in the Brawlidays Calendar!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Buzz Lightyear is a temporary Brawler available from December 12th to February 4th.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;He has his own Space Ranger Mastery with unique items. Complete it before he leaves the game!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Buzz Lightyear starts at power level INFINITY with a Gadget and a Hypercharge (no Starr Power).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;He has 3 different modes, Wing, Laser, and Saber Mode. Each one of these changes Buzz Lightyear’s main attack and Super.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Every trophy you collect with Buzz Lightyear will already count towards the Trophy Boxes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;BRAWLIDAYS CALENDAR!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;From today until December 25th, you will get a freebie every day! Starting with Buzz Lightyear on day one! Here’s the list!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;DAY 1&lt;/b&gt; - Buzz Lightyear
&lt;b&gt;DAY 2&lt;/b&gt; - Player Icon
&lt;b&gt;DAY 3&lt;/b&gt; - 1 Present
&lt;b&gt;DAY 4&lt;/b&gt; - Pin
&lt;b&gt;DAY 5&lt;/b&gt; - 1 Present
&lt;b&gt;DAY 6&lt;/b&gt; - Player Icon
&lt;b&gt;DAY 7&lt;/b&gt; - 1 Present
&lt;b&gt;DAY 8&lt;/b&gt; - Pin
&lt;b&gt;DAY 9&lt;/b&gt; - 1 Present
&lt;b&gt;DAY 10&lt;/b&gt; - Pin
&lt;b&gt;DAY 11&lt;/b&gt; - 1 Present
&lt;b&gt;DAY 12&lt;/b&gt; - Player Icon
&lt;b&gt;DAY 13 &lt;/b&gt;- Legendary Starr Drop
&lt;b&gt;DAY 14&lt;/b&gt; - Spray and 1 Hypercharge Drop&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These Freebies will be available until December 31st, so collect ALL OF THEM!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;MEGA TREE CLUB EVENT&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you are not in a Club, JOIN A CLUB!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;From December 12th to 25th, everyone in your Club, including you, will receive 3 tickets every day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Use those tickets in the Mega Tree event to get WINS!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;For every 25 Club Wins, you and your Club will get one Present to be opened on December 25th.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;In Mega Tree you’ll play random Game Modes with random Modifiers (just as in Mega Pig)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;PRESENTS AND SKINS&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Toy Story Skins will only be available in the Shop!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Toy Skins is a different Skins group and will be first available inside Presents.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;From Presents, you can get resources, including Gems, Bling, Skins, Brawlers, Hypercharges, and the newly released Toy Skins! &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Toy Skins will also be available in the Shop on December 25th&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;THANK YOU!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thank you for being part of one more year of Brawl Stars and enjoy the freebies!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/#/en/news/6ISdhQB8e5PcfijYIx42TB"/>
    <link href="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/4ivEQjVaH7P2JmezF0OKYC/ca4db0a89c8ba6675918825bb2b1b3ee/1212_Buzz_Lightyear_Event_inbox_800x433_v2.png?w=800&amp;h=433&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"/>
    <category term="Community"/>
    <published>2024-12-12T04:00:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>K7TfOp3wt8dbNVjgWwuCc</id>
    <title>GET BUZZ LIGHTYEAR &amp; BRAWLIDAYS PRESENTS FOR FREE!</title>
    <updated>2024-12-12T08:06:29.364000+00:00</updated>
    <link href="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/#/en/news/K7TfOp3wt8dbNVjgWwuCc"/>
    <link href="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/1tsITpAQaZY3Uas8PvNh6H/b86a08802e0f118bf162f3235f265edb/BS_Brawliversary_Thumb_1.jpg?w=800&amp;h=433&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"/>
    <link href="https://youtu.be/4KrSb74_C3k"/>
    <category term="Community"/>
    <published>2024-12-12T06:00:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>49BuyTboQeye3O4NAEvQCR</id>
    <title>PATCH NOTES: Toy Story!</title>
    <updated>2024-12-26T23:52:06.732000+00:00</updated>
    <content>&lt;h1&gt;Maintenance and Balance Changes - December 18th&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Balance Changes:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Buzz Lightyear 🚀&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Saber Mode:
Health points 4500 ➝ 4200
Super charge from basics 4 hits ➝ 5 hits&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Laser Mode:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Damage - 1160 ➝ 1080 (which also slightly decreased the Super charge)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Fixes&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixed the placement of the Hot Zone in the Watersports map&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Sk8 Beats environment now has the correct music&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jessie’s turret now appears in battle cards, and during her win animation&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixed some visual issues with Kenji’s lose animation&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Solved an issue with Kenji being able to knock the ball out of the map in Brawl Ball 5v5&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Buzz Lightyear Hypercharge description now has the correct icon for Speed stats (instead of the Health icon)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Winning with Buzz Lightyear no longer displays trophy loss or gains on the home screen. The trophy count will remain the same&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixed the crash error when Buzz Lightyear flies out of the map&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Janet no longer returns to the starting point of her first Super when using her Hypercharged Super just before landing&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gray’s Gadget &amp;quot;Walking Cane&amp;quot; now charges his Super&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first Puddle created by Berry&amp;#39;s Super no longer does 3040 damage at the first tick&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixed Melodie&amp;#39;s animation while and after Hypercharged&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nita and Dynamike Brawlidays recolor Skins are now correctly labeled&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Desert Scorpion Chuck poles are now correctly placed on the map&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Optional update for Android and iOS&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fixed the game crashing for the Arabic and Hebrew languages when selecting Buzz Lightyear on the Brawlers selection screen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;New Collab: Toy Story!&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The latest Brawl Stars collab is here with Disney and Pixar’s Toy Story! We’ll have Toy Story Skins inspired by movie characters like Colt Woody, Bo Beep Bibi, Jessie Jessie, and Surge Lightyear. But that’s not all—we will also have Buzz Lightyear as the first-ever Temporary Brawler in Brawl Stars!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;BUZZ LIGHTYEAR &lt;/b&gt;- Temporary Brawler&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Buzz Lightyear has landed in Starr Park! Featuring three different Brawling modes, you’ll be able to play with Buzz for FREE from December 12th until February 4th, 2025!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Basic Attack&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Laser: &lt;b&gt;SET TO STUN&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Buzz Lightyear fires a laser blast that deals damage on impact and applies a burn effect, causing additional damage over time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Saber: &lt;b&gt;SABER SLASH&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Buzz Lightyear skillfully swipes his saber dealing heavy melee damage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wing: &lt;b&gt;GALACTIC BLAST&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Buzz Lightyear fires two laser beams, dealing increased damage to targets at closer range.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Super&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Laser: &lt;b&gt;LASER FRENZY&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Buzz Lightyear fires a burst of lasers, dealing immediate damage and inflicting a burn that damages opponents over time&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Saber: &lt;b&gt;TO THE RESCUE!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Buzz Lightyear leaps into the air, charging forward with his saber, knocking back all opponents he strikes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wing: &lt;b&gt;FLYING WITH STYLE&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Buzz Lightyear leaps into the sky, swooping down on opponents while dropping a payload as he&amp;#39;s moving.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Gadget&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;All modes: &lt;b&gt;TURBO BOOSTERS&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Buzz Lightyear activates his turbo, sprinting forward in his current direction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Hypercharge&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;All Modes: &lt;b&gt;BRAVADO&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Buzz Lightyear gains a boost to all his base stats, increasing his speed and strength, while his Super remains unaffected.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mastery Title: &lt;b&gt;TO INFINITY AND BEYOND!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;
Important info about Buzz Lightyear&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Buzz will be unlockable as the first free reward of the Brawlidays calendar&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can choose the Brawling mode in the Brawler selection screen after clicking on Buzz&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Buzz Lightyear will &lt;b&gt;NOT &lt;/b&gt;be available in Ranked&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Buzz’s Trophies work the same as with standard Brawlers, EXCEPT all the Trophies you earn with Buzz will count towards the Trophy Box + on Season reset, all of his Trophies under 1000 will automatically be added to the new Season’s Trophy Box&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;When Buzz leaves the game before the January Season ends, his Season Trophies will still count towards that Season’s Trophy Box&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Brawlidays&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Brawlidays are back! This time with a new Daily Freebie Calendar, a Mega Tree Club Event, and PRESENTS!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Presents are similar to Starr Drops, but include the new Toy Skins (not the Toy Story Skins!), a selection of old Brawlidays Skins, Currency and Gems!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Brawlidays celebrations start on December 12th and end on December 25th!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;Brawlidays Calendar&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Brawlidays Calendar will have FREEBIES EVERYDAY and starts with the FREE temporary Brawler from the Toy Story collab, Buzz Lightyear! &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Remaining Freebies include the new Toy Skins, Brawlidays Cosmetics, progression and the new Presents!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even if you miss a day, you can still claim all your freebies until January 1st, 2025&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;Mega Tree Club Event&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Mega Pig has turned into a Mega Tree!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;takes place for a longer period and there’s no limit to how many rewards you can get!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;You will get Tickets to use everyday and even if you miss a day, those tickets will pile so you can use them anytime during the duration of the event&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;With the tickets you can play for your club, a win will count towards the overall score. The higher the score, the more rewards your Club will get at the end of the Mega Tree event&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Mega Tree will also feature a bigger pool Game Modes and Modifiers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Mega Tree Club ends on December 25th, and everyone in the Club will be able to open all their Presents that day&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Pizza Planet Event&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Pizza Planet event is coming in January and &lt;b&gt;you can get the Surge Lightyear Skin and the new Brawler Meeple FOR FREE! &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Your main objective in the event is to earn Pizza Slices and use them in the new Arcade Shop!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the Arcade Shop, you can spend Pizza Slices on special offers featuring the new Starr Force Skins, special cosmetics, currencies, Presents, Brawlers and, if you save enough Pizza slices, you’ll even be able to get the new Brawler, Meeple for FREE!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Every day in the Arcade Shop “The Claw” will also pick 1 free offer for you to claim!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;To collect Pizza Slices, you can complete Special Quests or play the new leaderboard event!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;This event plays similar to the Contests from the Angels VS Demons Event, with each leaderboard running for 3 days&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;You get tickets every day and then use them to play matches. If you win, then you get a score that increases your leaderboard ranking&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;On top of that, you can earn even higher scores by being good! So winning faster, doing a lot of damage, healing, completing the objectives, and taking down Brawlers will all add up to your score!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The total score of the match is attributed to the whole team, and if your team wins, you also get a score multiplier on top of that!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;This event will also feature several 2v2 variations of the standard game modes and the new Brawl Hockey and Special Delivery game modes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some of these modes will also be running as Trophy modes alongside the event&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There will also be a Daily Pizza Delivery in the regular Shop, where you can claim Pizza Slices every day, and at the end of the calendar, there will be Surge Lightyear for FREE!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Pizza Planet starts on January 2nd and ends on February 5th&lt;/b&gt;, together with the Starr Force Brawl Pass Season!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;New Brawlers&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;MEEPLE &lt;/b&gt;- Controller (Epic)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meeple knows the rules to every board game in existence, and if you break them… Well, let’s just say you don’t want to break them. They hate cheaters and those who don’t follow the rules, but there&amp;#39;s one exception to the rules… Meeple themselves!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Basic Attack: &lt;b&gt;BOOMHAVEN&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meeple shoots various projectiles that will slightly home towards the nearest enemy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Super: &lt;b&gt;CRITICAL SUCCESS&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meeple cheats, somehow rolling a NAT21 on a d20, allowing all team projectiles in the Super area to pierce through environments&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Star Power: &lt;b&gt;DO NOT PASS GO&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;When you shoot through the environment deal more damage&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Star Power: &lt;b&gt;RULE BENDING&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Critical success also increases allies&amp;#39; reload speed within the area by 20%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gadget: &lt;b&gt;MANSIONS OF MEEPLE&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meeple’s next attack creates dice towers around the impact area and deals damage on impact.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gadget: &lt;b&gt;RAGEQUIT&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meeple lashes out in rage at nearby enemies, stunning them. Ragequit stuns for a longer period of time the fewer hitpoints Meeple has.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mastery Title: &lt;b&gt;CHEATER&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;
OLLIE &lt;/b&gt;- Tank (Mythic)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ollie rides his customized hoverboard around Starr Park, grinding rails and causing trouble! A fan of old-school hip-hop, Ollie blasts his favorite tunes wherever he goes. His music is contagious… literally. Brawlers can’t help but dance when they hear it!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Basic Attack: &lt;b&gt;BRING THE RUCKUS&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ollie’s hoverboard fires soundwaves which deal damage and go through enemies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Super: &lt;b&gt;HYPNOTIZE&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ollie dashes forward with a gnarly hoverboard trick and starts charging a music blast, dealing damage and hypnotizing all enemies around him. While charging the music blast Ollie can’t attack. Enemies will move towards Ollie and cannot be controlled while being hypnotized. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Star Power:  &lt;b&gt;KICK, PUSH&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;While near walls Ollie kicks off his hoverboard and gains 20% extra movement speed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Star Power: &lt;b&gt;RENEGADE&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;After dashing forward with his super, Ollie gains a shield, decaying over time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gadget: &lt;b&gt;REGULATE&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ollie jumps and does a rad kickflip, hypnotizing all enemies where he lands. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gadget: &lt;b&gt;ALL EYEZ ON ME&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ollie’s next attack will hypnotize any enemies hit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mastery Title: &lt;b&gt;BASED&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;New Hypercharges&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gray&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;- &lt;b&gt;ANOTHER DIMENSION&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Summons a second pair of portals that also gives allies a shield when passing through&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Janet - &lt;b&gt;MAGNUM OPUS&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gives full movement control during her Super (and can even stay still in the air now!)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ash - &lt;b&gt;RAT KING&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Super now spawns double the amount of rats!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eve - &lt;b&gt;GENERATIONS&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Spawn an egg that continuously launches out hatchlings until it decays or gets destroyed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Berry - &lt;b&gt;DOUBLE SCOOPS&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Paint area is much wider and extends past Berry’s final Super position&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Melodie - &lt;b&gt;FLASH MOB&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Adds up to 3 additional hypercharged notes when using her Super (so you can have max 3 regular + 3 hypercharge notes = total of 6 notes maximum!)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;New Skins&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;TOY STORY&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Surge Lightyear&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Woody Colt&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bo Peep Bibi&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jessie Jessie&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;TOYS&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pop Penny&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cuddly Kit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Loopy Lola&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pop-up Darryl&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;BRAWLIDAYS&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reindeer Bonnie&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jolly Janet&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reinbear Nita&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sugar Bomb Mike
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;STARR FORCE&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hebi Kenji&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mamushi Kenji | Chroma #1&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aodaisho Kenji | Chroma #2&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Moon Driller Moe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gigantophis Gray&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Runner Nita&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Starr Horse Berry&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Extraterrestrial Eve&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;GOOD RANDOMS&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pop Melodie&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;REDWHITE Melodie | Chroma #1&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;BLACKGREEN Melodie | Chroma #2&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Quit Playing Poco&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bye Bye Buzz&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Woodriver Stu
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;BRAWLENTINES&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Romantic Dynamike&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cupid Bo&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;MISC&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jungle Gene&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Galactic Gale&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Maverick Crow&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Robo Penny&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ollie-G&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Strike Meeple&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;World Finals Leon&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Balance Changes&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;Buffs&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;El Primo&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;HP increased: 6000 → 6300&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;El Primo gains some extra durability to suplex opponents more effectively and just MORE&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Lou&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reload speed reduced: 1300 → 1100&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Lou&amp;#39;s hard-to-hit shots now benefit from faster reloads to improve overall effectiveness or so you can miss them more often&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Willow&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Increased Super projectile size: 50 → 150&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Increasing the projectile size enhances reliability and aligns better with her mind-control theme, if you still often miss after this, then the issue should be elsewhere (as in you)&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Griff&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Increased Super damage: 660 → 720&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;A raise for Griff to align with his money-centric views on life&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Maisie&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Increased main attack damage: 1400 → 1500&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;This buff should make her shots more rewarding and satisfying to hit! Unless you miss&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Charlie&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Increased HP: 3300 → 3500&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Additional durability to help Charlie be more effective in close quarters&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Mico&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Increased HP: 3000 → 3300&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;More HP for monke&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Nani&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hypercharge stats boosts:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Damage increased: 15% → 25%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Movement speed Increased: 15% → 25%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Nani?! Her Hypercharge should now feel more Hyperchargey!&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;
Nerfs&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Moe&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Main attack reload speed increased: 1500 → 2000&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Super damage: 800 → 600&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;While previous nerfs helped, This little $%t$’s Main attack and Super are still too strong, so these changes should make playing him require more brains&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Kenji&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reload speed increased: 800 → 1000&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Kenji was ALSO still quite strong after the prior nerfs so we reduced his reload speed to balance his DPS, Super charge, and general survivability&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Frank&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Star Power Power Grab damage decreased: 50% → 25%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Bonk - now with slightly less bonk&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Surge&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;HP decreased: 3300 → 3000&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Surge was getting too Alpha and really needed an HP reduction to encourage more strategic engagements and reduce his dominance&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Melodie&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Super charge rate decreased: 4 → 5 Ammo&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;We’re tuning her Super charge rate down to balance her already strong win rate and make her more approachable (she isn’t)&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Piper&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gadget Auto-Aimer: Slow effect removed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Adjusting Piper’s Gadget to still be defensive but not as debilitating to the opponent’s feelings&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Clancy&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Level 3 bonus movement speed decreased: 170 → 100&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Short legs shouldn&amp;#39;t move that fast&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rico&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Multiball Launcher damage decreased: 140 → 120&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Reduced damage to balance effectiveness, so imagine stepping on a less painful LEGO&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Maps, Game Modes &amp; Rotation Changes&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;Seasonal Games Modes&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;New: &lt;b&gt;Brawl Hockey&lt;/b&gt; (3v3 Trophy Mode) - Part of Pizza Planet Event&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brawl Ball with a slippery puck that can be shot to make it slide&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first team to score 3 goals wins&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;New: &lt;b&gt;Special Delivery&lt;/b&gt; (3v3 Trophy Mode) - Part of Pizza Planet Event&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;1 track Payload, first one to move it to their designated side wins&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stand near Payload to move it. Two friendlies can negate the presence of one enemy, so it will still be pushed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The cart will move faster on a track it already went through&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;In overtime, the payload moves much faster&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;New: &lt;b&gt;2v2 Game Modes&lt;/b&gt; for Pizza Planet Arcade event&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brawl Ball&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Knockout&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gem Grab&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hot Zone&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Basket Brawl&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brawl Hockey&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Special Delivery&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Returning game modes for Brawlidays Tree Club Event:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Present Plunder&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Carry the Gift&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bot Drop&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Paint Brawl&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Holiday Havoc&lt;/b&gt; (Redux of Jellyfishing game mode)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Soul Collector&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Spirit Wars&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Modifiers: Super Bushy, Unlimited Power, Ice Age, Timed Detonation, Quickfire, Big Friend, Instagib, Gotta Go Fast and Gadgets Galore&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;Environments&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Removed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mortis Mortuary&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Poco’s Band Stand&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ghost Metro&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mad Evil Manor&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oddities Shop&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Added&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sk8 Beats&lt;/b&gt; (New)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Brawl Hockey&lt;/b&gt; (New)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Starr Toons Studio&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fighting Game&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Starr Force&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr. P’s Snowtel&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Arcade&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Griff’s Gift Shop&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;Mode Rotation&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Slot: &lt;b&gt;Brawl Ball 5v5/Knockout 5v5&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Knockout 5v5 will be removed from rotation and replaced by Wipeout 5v5&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Slot: &lt;b&gt;Knockout 3v3 and Duels&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;We will re-introduce Wipeout 3v3 and Bounty 3v3 which will rotate with Duels in the same slot&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;Maps&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bounty&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;No Excuses&lt;/b&gt; (a REDUX of the map formerly known as “Purple Paradise”)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Canal Grande&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shooting Star&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Snake Prairie&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Layer Cake&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hideout&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brawl Ball&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Second Try&lt;/b&gt; (New)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trickey (New)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pinhole Punt&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Center Stage&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sneaky Fields&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pinball Dreams&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Triple Dribble&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beach Ball&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Backyard Bowl&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sunny Soccer&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Super Beach&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Penalty Kick&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Duels&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Petticoat Duel&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;No Surrender&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shrouding Serpent&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Warrior’s Way&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monkey Maze&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zen Garden&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gem Grab&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Forest Clearing&lt;/b&gt; (New)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;The cooler Hard Rock&lt;/b&gt; (New)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Crystal Arcade&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Deathcap Trap&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last Stop&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hard Rock Mine&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Double Swoosh&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gem Fort&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rustic Arcade&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Open Space&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Undermine&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Minecart Madness&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Heist&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Safe(r) Zone&lt;/b&gt; (New)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Great Lake&lt;/b&gt; (New)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;GG 2.0&lt;/b&gt; (a REDUX of G.G. Mortuary)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kaboom Canyon&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Safe Zone&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hot Potato&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hot Zone&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Watersport&lt;/b&gt; (New)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Noisy Neighbors&lt;/b&gt; (New)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Open Business&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dueling Beetles&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ring of Fire&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Parallel Plays&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Knockout&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;H for…&lt;/b&gt; (New)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Two Rivers&lt;/b&gt; (New)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Deep Forest&lt;/b&gt; (New)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Tiny Islands&lt;/b&gt; (New)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Temple of Vroom&lt;/b&gt; (New)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Overgrown Ruins&lt;/b&gt; (New)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Goldarm Gulch&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Out in the Open&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Belle’s Rock&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;New Horizons&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Flaring Phoenix&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Four Levels&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wipeout&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Layer Bake&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Quad Damage&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Great Open&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Infinite Doom&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Spice Production&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Slayer’s Paradise&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Showdown&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Acid Lakes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Island Invasion&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Skull Creek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dark Passage&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Flying Fantasies&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rockwall Brawl&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Safety Center&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Feast or Famine&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cavern Churn&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Double Trouble&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dried Up River&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Marksman’s Paradise&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Quality of Life Improvements&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The regular Brawl Pass can now be purchased from The Supercell Store&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Players can now adjust the volume of sound effects and music in the Settings&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Shop now has indicators for Seasonal and Exclusive Skins&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Players in inactive Clubs will occasionally receive suggestions to join more active Clubs&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;We replaced the Thumbs Up/Down button at the end of matches with an option to share the match replay with your Club&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Bug Fixes&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixed the placement of bushes in Sneaky Fields (Brawl Ball) and Safe Zone (Heist) to be symmetric on both sides of the map&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixed spawn locations in Pinball Dreams&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixed some iOS devices showing low-quality textures &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Continued improving the shop performance for low-end devices to reduce crashes and increase Shop opening speed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixed Otis’ Star Power not working after using his Hypercharge (it now correctly shoots 4 projectiles instead of 3)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixed a camera issue where sometimes one team could not see as far on the map as the other team&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixed Lily’s auto-attack animation not working correctly for her Basic Attack&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixed invisible Brawlers becoming visible when they came close to the ball in Brawl Ball&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixed texture issues with the Leon the Stray Skin&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixed the issue with Otis&amp;#39; shooting more projectiles than supposed after using his Hypercharge&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixed an issue causing Ranked Quests not being generated for some players after a new Brawl Pass season starts&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/#/en/news/49BuyTboQeye3O4NAEvQCR"/>
    <link href="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/2LBQvKwayb4uYmZPblV3VQ/f0ea403d91f1840b37582dc07a79b82d/1209_Loading_screen_Brawl_x_TS.png?w=800&amp;h=433&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"/>
    <category term="Release Notes"/>
    <published>2024-12-19T10:00:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>487FLwhfkGeqMP0Oq3dO65</id>
    <title>Starr Force Animation!</title>
    <updated>2025-01-02T09:20:01.043000+00:00</updated>
    <link href="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/#/en/news/487FLwhfkGeqMP0Oq3dO65"/>
    <link href="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/7BKZNH8mwGga5x99M19DJy/a68b15f9669e2f1b2b091f3bb50439dc/1230_Starr_Force_Animation_Launch_YT_thumb01.png?w=800&amp;h=433&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"/>
    <link href="https://youtu.be/T0Z9WsTuR04"/>
    <category term="Video"/>
    <published>2024-12-20T00:00:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>58PXswgjyh5AjJP1V5omDx</id>
    <title>EVERYTHING ABOUT THE PIZZA PLANET EVENT!</title>
    <updated>2025-01-03T02:39:13.007000+00:00</updated>
    <content>&lt;h1&gt;EVERYTHING ABOUT THE PIZZA PLANET EVENT!&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Pizza Planet event STARTS NOW, and you can get the Surge Lightyear Skin and the new Brawler Meeple FOR FREE! &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;b&gt;Your Mission: Collect Pizza Slices and use them on offers in the Pizza Planet Shop!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&amp;quot;How do I collect these tasty Pizza Slices?&amp;quot;&lt;/b&gt;
It&amp;#39;s easy! You can gather them from the following sources:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pizza Slices Calendar in the Shop (available daily)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Daily Offers in the Pizza Planet Shop&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Seasonal Quests&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scoreboard Contest&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Want more slices without grinding? You can also purchase them with Gems in the Shop!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&amp;quot;What can I do with Pizza Slices?&amp;quot;&lt;/b&gt;
Use your collected Pizza Slices in the Pizza Planet Shop on the left side of the lobby screen. There, you’ll find:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;A FREEBIE BUNDLE every day!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new Meeple Brawler&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Starr Force Skins&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Presents (It is still Brawlidays in our hearts!)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cosmetics (Skins, Profile Icons, Sprays, Pins, and Bling)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Progression Items (Coins, PowerPoints, Hypercharge Starr Drops)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Surge Lightyear Skin (For those who have Surge unlocked!)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&amp;quot;How do I get the Surge Lightyear Skin?&amp;quot;&lt;/b&gt;
If you’ve already unlocked Surge, you can get the &lt;i&gt;Surge Lightyear&lt;/i&gt; Skin for free!
If you haven’t unlocked Surge yet, here’s how you can do it:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Surge will be available in the Pizza Planet Shop throughout the entire event. As a Legendary Brawler, unlocking him will require a significant amount of Pizza Slices—but grind enough, and you can unlock a &lt;i&gt;free Legendary Brawler&lt;/i&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alternatively, you can unlock Surge with Credits. The skin will be available for free over the next 4 months—starting today!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you’d rather skip the grind, you can also purchase Surge from the Shop for a good Gem offer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&amp;quot;Did you say… Contest?!&amp;quot;
&lt;/b&gt;Yes, the Scoreboard Contest is back; this time, it’s all about 2v2 game modes! And you still earn points even if you lose!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;You’ll receive tickets to play each day. Unused tickets will reset after 3 days.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Every 3 days, a new 2v2 game mode will be featured.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Every action you take in a match—whether it&amp;#39;s taking down Brawlers, dealing damage, healing teammates, or completing objectives—will earn you points.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Win or lose, you’re still rewarded! Wins multiply your total points.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Enjoy Air Hockey and Special Delivery as available modes in the contest and 3v3 slots during the event!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&amp;quot;How many Pizza Slices can I get for free?&amp;quot;
&lt;/b&gt;There are plenty of ways to earn free Pizza Slices! Here’s the breakdown:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pizza Calendar: 12 Pizza Slices per day (360 total)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Daily Offer Reveals in the Pizza Planet Shop: 1 per reveal (around 120 total). It may vary if you buy some of the Pizza Planet offers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Seasonal Quests: 30 Pizza Slices per quest (330 total)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scoreboard Contest: Up to 150 Pizza Slices per contest (1650 total if you win all the matches. Or about 990 on average)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Random Freebies: 100 Pizza Slices, twice (200 total)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Max number of Pizza Slices you can earn for free: 2,660 (based on 100% win rate in the Contest)
Average number of Pizza Slices you can earn for free: 2,000 (based on average performance in the Contest)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&amp;quot;Does pineapple belong on pizza?&amp;quot;
&lt;/b&gt;That&amp;#39;s a question only &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; can answer... 🍍&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/#/en/news/58PXswgjyh5AjJP1V5omDx"/>
    <link href="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/4lGIQWFxIVHiF2VgPRr4D1/91e05c526a2cf0587312aabd3ec85888/0102_Pizza_Planet_Event_inbox_800x433.png?w=800&amp;h=433&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"/>
    <category term="News"/>
    <published>2025-01-02T08:59:34+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
