<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Brawlstars - News</title>
    <link>https://github.com/skrwo/supercell-inbox-rss/</link>
    <description>RSS wrapper of Brawlstars inbox News</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 10:39:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>To Brawl... AND BEYOND!</title>
      <link>https://youtu.be/PtutVHfyBx8</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">nSZBd0biUgnb3PpDzK4Z4</guid>
      <category>Video</category>
      <enclosure url="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/7KKm0NlixRWGcEeWKNFkOy/f0dc634d844448489a443c0ef395d516/1206_Toy_Story_Animation_Teaser_v2.png?w=800&amp;h=433&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill" length="0" type="image/png"/>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 13:14:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brawliversary and Brawlidays Events!</title>
      <link>https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/#/en/news/6ISdhQB8e5PcfijYIx42TB</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Happy Birthday to all of us! It’s Brawl Stars’ 6th birthday since our global launch! &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So as always, we’ll celebrate from today, until the Brawlidays! Which means… PRESENTS!
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here’s what you should know about it!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Buzz Lightyear is available FOR FREE now in the Brawlidays Calendar (available in the Shop).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Complete Buzz Lightyear’s Space Ranger Mastery Track before he leaves the game!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mega Tree event! Join a club, use your tickets, and collect Presents to open it on December 25th.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;BUZZ LIGHTYEAR HAS LANDED IN BRAWL STARS!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can collect Buzz Lightyear FOR FREE in the Brawlidays Calendar!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Buzz Lightyear is a temporary Brawler available from December 12th to February 4th.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;He has his own Space Ranger Mastery with unique items. Complete it before he leaves the game!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Buzz Lightyear starts at power level INFINITY with a Gadget and a Hypercharge (no Starr Power).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;He has 3 different modes, Wing, Laser, and Saber Mode. Each one of these changes Buzz Lightyear’s main attack and Super.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Every trophy you collect with Buzz Lightyear will already count towards the Trophy Boxes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;BRAWLIDAYS CALENDAR!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;From today until December 25th, you will get a freebie every day! Starting with Buzz Lightyear on day one! Here’s the list!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;DAY 1&lt;/b&gt; - Buzz Lightyear
&lt;b&gt;DAY 2&lt;/b&gt; - Player Icon
&lt;b&gt;DAY 3&lt;/b&gt; - 1 Present
&lt;b&gt;DAY 4&lt;/b&gt; - Pin
&lt;b&gt;DAY 5&lt;/b&gt; - 1 Present
&lt;b&gt;DAY 6&lt;/b&gt; - Player Icon
&lt;b&gt;DAY 7&lt;/b&gt; - 1 Present
&lt;b&gt;DAY 8&lt;/b&gt; - Pin
&lt;b&gt;DAY 9&lt;/b&gt; - 1 Present
&lt;b&gt;DAY 10&lt;/b&gt; - Pin
&lt;b&gt;DAY 11&lt;/b&gt; - 1 Present
&lt;b&gt;DAY 12&lt;/b&gt; - Player Icon
&lt;b&gt;DAY 13 &lt;/b&gt;- Legendary Starr Drop
&lt;b&gt;DAY 14&lt;/b&gt; - Spray and 1 Hypercharge Drop&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These Freebies will be available until December 31st, so collect ALL OF THEM!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;MEGA TREE CLUB EVENT&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you are not in a Club, JOIN A CLUB!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;From December 12th to 25th, everyone in your Club, including you, will receive 3 tickets every day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Use those tickets in the Mega Tree event to get WINS!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;For every 25 Club Wins, you and your Club will get one Present to be opened on December 25th.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;In Mega Tree you’ll play random Game Modes with random Modifiers (just as in Mega Pig)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;PRESENTS AND SKINS&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Toy Story Skins will only be available in the Shop!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Toy Skins is a different Skins group and will be first available inside Presents.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;From Presents, you can get resources, including Gems, Bling, Skins, Brawlers, Hypercharges, and the newly released Toy Skins! &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Toy Skins will also be available in the Shop on December 25th&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;THANK YOU!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thank you for being part of one more year of Brawl Stars and enjoy the freebies!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6ISdhQB8e5PcfijYIx42TB</guid>
      <category>Community</category>
      <enclosure url="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/4ivEQjVaH7P2JmezF0OKYC/ca4db0a89c8ba6675918825bb2b1b3ee/1212_Buzz_Lightyear_Event_inbox_800x433_v2.png?w=800&amp;h=433&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill" length="0" type="image/png"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GET BUZZ LIGHTYEAR &amp; BRAWLIDAYS PRESENTS FOR FREE!</title>
      <link>https://youtu.be/4KrSb74_C3k</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">K7TfOp3wt8dbNVjgWwuCc</guid>
      <category>Community</category>
      <enclosure url="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/1tsITpAQaZY3Uas8PvNh6H/b86a08802e0f118bf162f3235f265edb/BS_Brawliversary_Thumb_1.jpg?w=800&amp;h=433&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PATCH NOTES: Toy Story!</title>
      <link>https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/#/en/news/49BuyTboQeye3O4NAEvQCR</link>
      <description>&lt;h1&gt;Maintenance and Balance Changes - December 18th&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Balance Changes:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Buzz Lightyear 🚀&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Saber Mode:
Health points 4500 ➝ 4200
Super charge from basics 4 hits ➝ 5 hits&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Laser Mode:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Damage - 1160 ➝ 1080 (which also slightly decreased the Super charge)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Fixes&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixed the placement of the Hot Zone in the Watersports map&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Sk8 Beats environment now has the correct music&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jessie’s turret now appears in battle cards, and during her win animation&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixed some visual issues with Kenji’s lose animation&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Solved an issue with Kenji being able to knock the ball out of the map in Brawl Ball 5v5&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Buzz Lightyear Hypercharge description now has the correct icon for Speed stats (instead of the Health icon)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Winning with Buzz Lightyear no longer displays trophy loss or gains on the home screen. The trophy count will remain the same&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixed the crash error when Buzz Lightyear flies out of the map&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Janet no longer returns to the starting point of her first Super when using her Hypercharged Super just before landing&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gray’s Gadget &amp;quot;Walking Cane&amp;quot; now charges his Super&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first Puddle created by Berry&amp;#39;s Super no longer does 3040 damage at the first tick&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixed Melodie&amp;#39;s animation while and after Hypercharged&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nita and Dynamike Brawlidays recolor Skins are now correctly labeled&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Desert Scorpion Chuck poles are now correctly placed on the map&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Optional update for Android and iOS&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fixed the game crashing for the Arabic and Hebrew languages when selecting Buzz Lightyear on the Brawlers selection screen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;New Collab: Toy Story!&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The latest Brawl Stars collab is here with Disney and Pixar’s Toy Story! We’ll have Toy Story Skins inspired by movie characters like Colt Woody, Bo Beep Bibi, Jessie Jessie, and Surge Lightyear. But that’s not all—we will also have Buzz Lightyear as the first-ever Temporary Brawler in Brawl Stars!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;BUZZ LIGHTYEAR &lt;/b&gt;- Temporary Brawler&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Buzz Lightyear has landed in Starr Park! Featuring three different Brawling modes, you’ll be able to play with Buzz for FREE from December 12th until February 4th, 2025!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Basic Attack&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Laser: &lt;b&gt;SET TO STUN&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Buzz Lightyear fires a laser blast that deals damage on impact and applies a burn effect, causing additional damage over time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Saber: &lt;b&gt;SABER SLASH&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Buzz Lightyear skillfully swipes his saber dealing heavy melee damage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wing: &lt;b&gt;GALACTIC BLAST&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Buzz Lightyear fires two laser beams, dealing increased damage to targets at closer range.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Super&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Laser: &lt;b&gt;LASER FRENZY&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Buzz Lightyear fires a burst of lasers, dealing immediate damage and inflicting a burn that damages opponents over time&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Saber: &lt;b&gt;TO THE RESCUE!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Buzz Lightyear leaps into the air, charging forward with his saber, knocking back all opponents he strikes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wing: &lt;b&gt;FLYING WITH STYLE&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Buzz Lightyear leaps into the sky, swooping down on opponents while dropping a payload as he&amp;#39;s moving.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Gadget&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;All modes: &lt;b&gt;TURBO BOOSTERS&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Buzz Lightyear activates his turbo, sprinting forward in his current direction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Hypercharge&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;All Modes: &lt;b&gt;BRAVADO&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Buzz Lightyear gains a boost to all his base stats, increasing his speed and strength, while his Super remains unaffected.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mastery Title: &lt;b&gt;TO INFINITY AND BEYOND!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;
Important info about Buzz Lightyear&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Buzz will be unlockable as the first free reward of the Brawlidays calendar&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can choose the Brawling mode in the Brawler selection screen after clicking on Buzz&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Buzz Lightyear will &lt;b&gt;NOT &lt;/b&gt;be available in Ranked&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Buzz’s Trophies work the same as with standard Brawlers, EXCEPT all the Trophies you earn with Buzz will count towards the Trophy Box + on Season reset, all of his Trophies under 1000 will automatically be added to the new Season’s Trophy Box&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;When Buzz leaves the game before the January Season ends, his Season Trophies will still count towards that Season’s Trophy Box&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Brawlidays&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Brawlidays are back! This time with a new Daily Freebie Calendar, a Mega Tree Club Event, and PRESENTS!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Presents are similar to Starr Drops, but include the new Toy Skins (not the Toy Story Skins!), a selection of old Brawlidays Skins, Currency and Gems!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Brawlidays celebrations start on December 12th and end on December 25th!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;Brawlidays Calendar&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Brawlidays Calendar will have FREEBIES EVERYDAY and starts with the FREE temporary Brawler from the Toy Story collab, Buzz Lightyear! &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Remaining Freebies include the new Toy Skins, Brawlidays Cosmetics, progression and the new Presents!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even if you miss a day, you can still claim all your freebies until January 1st, 2025&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;Mega Tree Club Event&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Mega Pig has turned into a Mega Tree!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;takes place for a longer period and there’s no limit to how many rewards you can get!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;You will get Tickets to use everyday and even if you miss a day, those tickets will pile so you can use them anytime during the duration of the event&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;With the tickets you can play for your club, a win will count towards the overall score. The higher the score, the more rewards your Club will get at the end of the Mega Tree event&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Mega Tree will also feature a bigger pool Game Modes and Modifiers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Mega Tree Club ends on December 25th, and everyone in the Club will be able to open all their Presents that day&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Pizza Planet Event&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Pizza Planet event is coming in January and &lt;b&gt;you can get the Surge Lightyear Skin and the new Brawler Meeple FOR FREE! &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Your main objective in the event is to earn Pizza Slices and use them in the new Arcade Shop!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the Arcade Shop, you can spend Pizza Slices on special offers featuring the new Starr Force Skins, special cosmetics, currencies, Presents, Brawlers and, if you save enough Pizza slices, you’ll even be able to get the new Brawler, Meeple for FREE!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Every day in the Arcade Shop “The Claw” will also pick 1 free offer for you to claim!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;To collect Pizza Slices, you can complete Special Quests or play the new leaderboard event!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;This event plays similar to the Contests from the Angels VS Demons Event, with each leaderboard running for 3 days&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;You get tickets every day and then use them to play matches. If you win, then you get a score that increases your leaderboard ranking&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;On top of that, you can earn even higher scores by being good! So winning faster, doing a lot of damage, healing, completing the objectives, and taking down Brawlers will all add up to your score!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The total score of the match is attributed to the whole team, and if your team wins, you also get a score multiplier on top of that!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;This event will also feature several 2v2 variations of the standard game modes and the new Brawl Hockey and Special Delivery game modes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some of these modes will also be running as Trophy modes alongside the event&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There will also be a Daily Pizza Delivery in the regular Shop, where you can claim Pizza Slices every day, and at the end of the calendar, there will be Surge Lightyear for FREE!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Pizza Planet starts on January 2nd and ends on February 5th&lt;/b&gt;, together with the Starr Force Brawl Pass Season!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;New Brawlers&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;MEEPLE &lt;/b&gt;- Controller (Epic)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meeple knows the rules to every board game in existence, and if you break them… Well, let’s just say you don’t want to break them. They hate cheaters and those who don’t follow the rules, but there&amp;#39;s one exception to the rules… Meeple themselves!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Basic Attack: &lt;b&gt;BOOMHAVEN&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meeple shoots various projectiles that will slightly home towards the nearest enemy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Super: &lt;b&gt;CRITICAL SUCCESS&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meeple cheats, somehow rolling a NAT21 on a d20, allowing all team projectiles in the Super area to pierce through environments&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Star Power: &lt;b&gt;DO NOT PASS GO&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;When you shoot through the environment deal more damage&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Star Power: &lt;b&gt;RULE BENDING&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Critical success also increases allies&amp;#39; reload speed within the area by 20%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gadget: &lt;b&gt;MANSIONS OF MEEPLE&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meeple’s next attack creates dice towers around the impact area and deals damage on impact.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gadget: &lt;b&gt;RAGEQUIT&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meeple lashes out in rage at nearby enemies, stunning them. Ragequit stuns for a longer period of time the fewer hitpoints Meeple has.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mastery Title: &lt;b&gt;CHEATER&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;
OLLIE &lt;/b&gt;- Tank (Mythic)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ollie rides his customized hoverboard around Starr Park, grinding rails and causing trouble! A fan of old-school hip-hop, Ollie blasts his favorite tunes wherever he goes. His music is contagious… literally. Brawlers can’t help but dance when they hear it!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Basic Attack: &lt;b&gt;BRING THE RUCKUS&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ollie’s hoverboard fires soundwaves which deal damage and go through enemies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Super: &lt;b&gt;HYPNOTIZE&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ollie dashes forward with a gnarly hoverboard trick and starts charging a music blast, dealing damage and hypnotizing all enemies around him. While charging the music blast Ollie can’t attack. Enemies will move towards Ollie and cannot be controlled while being hypnotized. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Star Power:  &lt;b&gt;KICK, PUSH&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;While near walls Ollie kicks off his hoverboard and gains 20% extra movement speed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Star Power: &lt;b&gt;RENEGADE&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;After dashing forward with his super, Ollie gains a shield, decaying over time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gadget: &lt;b&gt;REGULATE&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ollie jumps and does a rad kickflip, hypnotizing all enemies where he lands. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gadget: &lt;b&gt;ALL EYEZ ON ME&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ollie’s next attack will hypnotize any enemies hit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mastery Title: &lt;b&gt;BASED&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;New Hypercharges&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gray&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;- &lt;b&gt;ANOTHER DIMENSION&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Summons a second pair of portals that also gives allies a shield when passing through&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Janet - &lt;b&gt;MAGNUM OPUS&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gives full movement control during her Super (and can even stay still in the air now!)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ash - &lt;b&gt;RAT KING&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Super now spawns double the amount of rats!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eve - &lt;b&gt;GENERATIONS&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Spawn an egg that continuously launches out hatchlings until it decays or gets destroyed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Berry - &lt;b&gt;DOUBLE SCOOPS&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Paint area is much wider and extends past Berry’s final Super position&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Melodie - &lt;b&gt;FLASH MOB&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Adds up to 3 additional hypercharged notes when using her Super (so you can have max 3 regular + 3 hypercharge notes = total of 6 notes maximum!)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;New Skins&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;TOY STORY&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Surge Lightyear&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Woody Colt&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bo Peep Bibi&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jessie Jessie&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;TOYS&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pop Penny&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cuddly Kit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Loopy Lola&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pop-up Darryl&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;BRAWLIDAYS&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reindeer Bonnie&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jolly Janet&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reinbear Nita&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sugar Bomb Mike
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;STARR FORCE&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hebi Kenji&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mamushi Kenji | Chroma #1&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aodaisho Kenji | Chroma #2&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Moon Driller Moe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gigantophis Gray&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Runner Nita&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Starr Horse Berry&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Extraterrestrial Eve&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;GOOD RANDOMS&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pop Melodie&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;REDWHITE Melodie | Chroma #1&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;BLACKGREEN Melodie | Chroma #2&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Quit Playing Poco&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bye Bye Buzz&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Woodriver Stu
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;BRAWLENTINES&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Romantic Dynamike&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cupid Bo&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;MISC&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jungle Gene&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Galactic Gale&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Maverick Crow&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Robo Penny&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ollie-G&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Strike Meeple&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;World Finals Leon&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Balance Changes&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;Buffs&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;El Primo&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;HP increased: 6000 → 6300&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;El Primo gains some extra durability to suplex opponents more effectively and just MORE&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Lou&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reload speed reduced: 1300 → 1100&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Lou&amp;#39;s hard-to-hit shots now benefit from faster reloads to improve overall effectiveness or so you can miss them more often&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Willow&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Increased Super projectile size: 50 → 150&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Increasing the projectile size enhances reliability and aligns better with her mind-control theme, if you still often miss after this, then the issue should be elsewhere (as in you)&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Griff&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Increased Super damage: 660 → 720&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;A raise for Griff to align with his money-centric views on life&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Maisie&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Increased main attack damage: 1400 → 1500&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;This buff should make her shots more rewarding and satisfying to hit! Unless you miss&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Charlie&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Increased HP: 3300 → 3500&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Additional durability to help Charlie be more effective in close quarters&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Mico&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Increased HP: 3000 → 3300&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;More HP for monke&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Nani&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hypercharge stats boosts:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Damage increased: 15% → 25%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Movement speed Increased: 15% → 25%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Nani?! Her Hypercharge should now feel more Hyperchargey!&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;
Nerfs&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Moe&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Main attack reload speed increased: 1500 → 2000&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Super damage: 800 → 600&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;While previous nerfs helped, This little $%t$’s Main attack and Super are still too strong, so these changes should make playing him require more brains&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Kenji&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reload speed increased: 800 → 1000&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Kenji was ALSO still quite strong after the prior nerfs so we reduced his reload speed to balance his DPS, Super charge, and general survivability&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Frank&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Star Power Power Grab damage decreased: 50% → 25%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Bonk - now with slightly less bonk&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Surge&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;HP decreased: 3300 → 3000&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Surge was getting too Alpha and really needed an HP reduction to encourage more strategic engagements and reduce his dominance&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Melodie&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Super charge rate decreased: 4 → 5 Ammo&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;We’re tuning her Super charge rate down to balance her already strong win rate and make her more approachable (she isn’t)&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Piper&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gadget Auto-Aimer: Slow effect removed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Adjusting Piper’s Gadget to still be defensive but not as debilitating to the opponent’s feelings&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Clancy&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Level 3 bonus movement speed decreased: 170 → 100&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Short legs shouldn&amp;#39;t move that fast&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rico&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Multiball Launcher damage decreased: 140 → 120&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Reduced damage to balance effectiveness, so imagine stepping on a less painful LEGO&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Maps, Game Modes &amp; Rotation Changes&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;Seasonal Games Modes&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;New: &lt;b&gt;Brawl Hockey&lt;/b&gt; (3v3 Trophy Mode) - Part of Pizza Planet Event&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brawl Ball with a slippery puck that can be shot to make it slide&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first team to score 3 goals wins&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;New: &lt;b&gt;Special Delivery&lt;/b&gt; (3v3 Trophy Mode) - Part of Pizza Planet Event&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;1 track Payload, first one to move it to their designated side wins&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stand near Payload to move it. Two friendlies can negate the presence of one enemy, so it will still be pushed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The cart will move faster on a track it already went through&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;In overtime, the payload moves much faster&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;New: &lt;b&gt;2v2 Game Modes&lt;/b&gt; for Pizza Planet Arcade event&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brawl Ball&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Knockout&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gem Grab&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hot Zone&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Basket Brawl&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brawl Hockey&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Special Delivery&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Returning game modes for Brawlidays Tree Club Event:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Present Plunder&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Carry the Gift&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bot Drop&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Paint Brawl&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Holiday Havoc&lt;/b&gt; (Redux of Jellyfishing game mode)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Soul Collector&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Spirit Wars&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Modifiers: Super Bushy, Unlimited Power, Ice Age, Timed Detonation, Quickfire, Big Friend, Instagib, Gotta Go Fast and Gadgets Galore&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;Environments&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Removed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mortis Mortuary&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Poco’s Band Stand&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ghost Metro&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mad Evil Manor&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oddities Shop&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Added&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sk8 Beats&lt;/b&gt; (New)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Brawl Hockey&lt;/b&gt; (New)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Starr Toons Studio&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fighting Game&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Starr Force&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr. P’s Snowtel&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Arcade&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Griff’s Gift Shop&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;Mode Rotation&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Slot: &lt;b&gt;Brawl Ball 5v5/Knockout 5v5&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Knockout 5v5 will be removed from rotation and replaced by Wipeout 5v5&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Slot: &lt;b&gt;Knockout 3v3 and Duels&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;We will re-introduce Wipeout 3v3 and Bounty 3v3 which will rotate with Duels in the same slot&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;Maps&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bounty&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;No Excuses&lt;/b&gt; (a REDUX of the map formerly known as “Purple Paradise”)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Canal Grande&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shooting Star&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Snake Prairie&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Layer Cake&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hideout&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brawl Ball&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Second Try&lt;/b&gt; (New)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trickey (New)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pinhole Punt&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Center Stage&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sneaky Fields&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pinball Dreams&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Triple Dribble&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beach Ball&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Backyard Bowl&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sunny Soccer&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Super Beach&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Penalty Kick&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Duels&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Petticoat Duel&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;No Surrender&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shrouding Serpent&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Warrior’s Way&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monkey Maze&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zen Garden&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gem Grab&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Forest Clearing&lt;/b&gt; (New)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;The cooler Hard Rock&lt;/b&gt; (New)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Crystal Arcade&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Deathcap Trap&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last Stop&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hard Rock Mine&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Double Swoosh&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gem Fort&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rustic Arcade&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Open Space&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Undermine&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Minecart Madness&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Heist&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Safe(r) Zone&lt;/b&gt; (New)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Great Lake&lt;/b&gt; (New)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;GG 2.0&lt;/b&gt; (a REDUX of G.G. Mortuary)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kaboom Canyon&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Safe Zone&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hot Potato&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hot Zone&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Watersport&lt;/b&gt; (New)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Noisy Neighbors&lt;/b&gt; (New)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Open Business&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dueling Beetles&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ring of Fire&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Parallel Plays&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Knockout&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;H for…&lt;/b&gt; (New)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Two Rivers&lt;/b&gt; (New)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Deep Forest&lt;/b&gt; (New)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Tiny Islands&lt;/b&gt; (New)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Temple of Vroom&lt;/b&gt; (New)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Overgrown Ruins&lt;/b&gt; (New)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Goldarm Gulch&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Out in the Open&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Belle’s Rock&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;New Horizons&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Flaring Phoenix&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Four Levels&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wipeout&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Layer Bake&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Quad Damage&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Great Open&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Infinite Doom&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Spice Production&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Slayer’s Paradise&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Showdown&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Acid Lakes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Island Invasion&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Skull Creek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dark Passage&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Flying Fantasies&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rockwall Brawl&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Safety Center&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Feast or Famine&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cavern Churn&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Double Trouble&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dried Up River&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Marksman’s Paradise&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Quality of Life Improvements&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The regular Brawl Pass can now be purchased from The Supercell Store&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Players can now adjust the volume of sound effects and music in the Settings&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Shop now has indicators for Seasonal and Exclusive Skins&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Players in inactive Clubs will occasionally receive suggestions to join more active Clubs&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;We replaced the Thumbs Up/Down button at the end of matches with an option to share the match replay with your Club&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Bug Fixes&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixed the placement of bushes in Sneaky Fields (Brawl Ball) and Safe Zone (Heist) to be symmetric on both sides of the map&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixed spawn locations in Pinball Dreams&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixed some iOS devices showing low-quality textures &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Continued improving the shop performance for low-end devices to reduce crashes and increase Shop opening speed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixed Otis’ Star Power not working after using his Hypercharge (it now correctly shoots 4 projectiles instead of 3)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixed a camera issue where sometimes one team could not see as far on the map as the other team&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixed Lily’s auto-attack animation not working correctly for her Basic Attack&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixed invisible Brawlers becoming visible when they came close to the ball in Brawl Ball&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixed texture issues with the Leon the Stray Skin&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixed the issue with Otis&amp;#39; shooting more projectiles than supposed after using his Hypercharge&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixed an issue causing Ranked Quests not being generated for some players after a new Brawl Pass season starts&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">49BuyTboQeye3O4NAEvQCR</guid>
      <category>Release Notes</category>
      <enclosure url="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/2LBQvKwayb4uYmZPblV3VQ/f0ea403d91f1840b37582dc07a79b82d/1209_Loading_screen_Brawl_x_TS.png?w=800&amp;h=433&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill" length="0" type="image/png"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Starr Force Animation!</title>
      <link>https://youtu.be/T0Z9WsTuR04</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">487FLwhfkGeqMP0Oq3dO65</guid>
      <category>Video</category>
      <enclosure url="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/7BKZNH8mwGga5x99M19DJy/a68b15f9669e2f1b2b091f3bb50439dc/1230_Starr_Force_Animation_Launch_YT_thumb01.png?w=800&amp;h=433&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill" length="0" type="image/png"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EVERYTHING ABOUT THE PIZZA PLANET EVENT!</title>
      <link>https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/#/en/news/58PXswgjyh5AjJP1V5omDx</link>
      <description>&lt;h1&gt;Maintenance and Pizza Slices Bug Fix - January 3rd&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Arcade Contests should now be working for everyone, including players who were stuck in the Arcade Contest reward screen&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Everyone&amp;#39;s Pizza Slices will be reset to 0 after maintenance ends&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;But there’s COMPENSATION for the players who started the event with 0 Pizza Slices before the maintenance&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The compensation is 300 Pizza Slices, and due to the high amount of players getting this compensation, it might take up to a few days to arrive in your account. It&amp;#39;ll be delivered directly to your account (in the inbox - on the top right side of your screen, you will see a notification appear when it arrives)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Players who bought Pizza Slices for Gems from the Shop will also be able to claim them again from the Shop&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;Additional information:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Players who started the event already with some Pizza Slices and have spent more than 300 of them in the Pizza Planet Shop won&amp;#39;t be compensated (as they already got a “head start” in the event)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;This issue happened because the Pizza Slices were replacing the Krusty Kash (a currency from a previous event), and, unfortunately, the unspent amount of currency earned in that event wasn&amp;#39;t reset for all the Players before the Pizza Planet event started&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;We might have another maintenance later on or next week to fix more minor issues related to the event&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are sorry about this experience, but hopefully, the event will run smoothly after today!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;EVERYTHING ABOUT THE PIZZA PLANET EVENT!&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Pizza Planet event STARTS NOW, and you can get the Surge Lightyear Skin and the new Brawler Meeple FOR FREE! &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;b&gt;Your Mission: Collect Pizza Slices and use them on offers in the Pizza Planet Shop!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&amp;quot;How do I collect these tasty Pizza Slices?&amp;quot;&lt;/b&gt;
It&amp;#39;s easy! You can gather them from the following sources:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pizza Slices Calendar in the Shop (available daily)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Daily Offers in the Pizza Planet Shop&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Seasonal Quests&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scoreboard Contest&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Want more slices without grinding? You can also purchase them with Gems in the Shop!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&amp;quot;What can I do with Pizza Slices?&amp;quot;&lt;/b&gt;
Use your collected Pizza Slices in the Pizza Planet Shop on the left side of the lobby screen. There, you’ll find:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;A FREEBIE BUNDLE every day!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new Meeple Brawler&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Starr Force Skins&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Presents (It is still Brawlidays in our hearts!)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cosmetics (Skins, Profile Icons, Sprays, Pins, and Bling)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Progression Items (Coins, PowerPoints, Hypercharge Starr Drops)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Surge Lightyear Skin (For those who have Surge unlocked!)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&amp;quot;How do I get the Surge Lightyear Skin?&amp;quot;&lt;/b&gt;
If you’ve already unlocked Surge, you can get the &lt;i&gt;Surge Lightyear&lt;/i&gt; Skin for free!
If you haven’t unlocked Surge yet, here’s how you can do it:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Surge will be available in the Pizza Planet Shop throughout the entire event. As a Legendary Brawler, unlocking him will require a significant amount of Pizza Slices—but grind enough, and you can unlock a &lt;i&gt;free Legendary Brawler&lt;/i&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alternatively, you can unlock Surge with Credits. The skin will be available for free over the next 4 months—starting today!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you’d rather skip the grind, you can also purchase Surge from the Shop for a good Gem offer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&amp;quot;Did you say… Contest?!&amp;quot;
&lt;/b&gt;Yes, the Scoreboard Contest is back; this time, it’s all about 2v2 game modes! And you still earn points even if you lose!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;You’ll receive tickets to play each day. Unused tickets will reset after 3 days.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Every 3 days, a new 2v2 game mode will be featured.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Every action you take in a match—whether it&amp;#39;s taking down Brawlers, dealing damage, healing teammates, or completing objectives—will earn you points.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Win or lose, you’re still rewarded! Wins multiply your total points.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Enjoy Air Hockey and Special Delivery as available modes in the contest and 3v3 slots during the event!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&amp;quot;How many Pizza Slices can I get for free?&amp;quot;
&lt;/b&gt;There are plenty of ways to earn free Pizza Slices! Here’s the breakdown:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pizza Calendar: 12 Pizza Slices per day (360 total)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Daily Offer Reveals in the Pizza Planet Shop: 1 per reveal (around 120 total). It may vary if you buy some of the Pizza Planet offers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Seasonal Quests: 30 Pizza Slices per quest (330 total)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scoreboard Contest: Up to 150 Pizza Slices per contest (1650 total if you win all the matches. Or about 990 on average)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Random Freebies: 100 Pizza Slices, twice (200 total)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Max number of Pizza Slices you can earn for free: 2,660 (based on 100% win rate in the Contest)
Average number of Pizza Slices you can earn for free: 2,000 (based on average performance in the Contest)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&amp;quot;Does pineapple belong on pizza?&amp;quot;
&lt;/b&gt;That&amp;#39;s a question only &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; can answer... 🍍&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">58PXswgjyh5AjJP1V5omDx</guid>
      <category>News</category>
      <enclosure url="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/4lGIQWFxIVHiF2VgPRr4D1/91e05c526a2cf0587312aabd3ec85888/0102_Pizza_Planet_Event_inbox_800x433.png?w=800&amp;h=433&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill" length="0" type="image/png"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 08:59:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BSC 2025 Season Kickoff! </title>
      <link>https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/#/en/news/KGSI4D1pOtE3jxfjHDISs</link>
      <description>&lt;h1&gt;Welcome to the Brawl Stars Championship 2025!&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check out the &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%25253A%25252F%25252Fyoutu.be%25252FgRUCqKw65fo%25253Fsi%25253DZDHaxGeydqP3QYsJ')"&gt;Roadmap Video&lt;/a&gt; or read on for more information below:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;SIX MONTHLY SEASONS - THREE OFFLINE EVENTS

&lt;/b&gt;That’s right, this year, we’ll have more Brawl Esports action than ever before. BSC will feature offline events on three different continents! &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;b&gt;BRAWL CUP&lt;/b&gt; is a new offline event in which players can earn an additional LCQ or World Finals spot for their home region! The event is slated for Q2 2025 and has the potential to shape the rest of the competition year. 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;
&lt;b&gt;South Asia and Southeast Asia&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Based on your feedback we are making changes on how to compete in APAC. Aside from &lt;b&gt;East Asia&lt;/b&gt;, comprising Japan and Korea, players in &lt;b&gt;Southeast Asia&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;South Asia&lt;/b&gt; will be able to compete for LCQ spots through a series of tournaments hosted by &lt;b&gt;letsplaylive&lt;/b&gt;! Read all the information at &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=http%25253A%25252F%25252Flplgg.co%25252F3EnMS4w')"&gt;lplgg.co/3EnMS4w&lt;/a&gt;&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;and follow their &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%25253A%25252F%25252Fx.com%25252FletsplayliveGG')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;socials&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; for updates.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Road To Redemption Documentary&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our 2025 documentary, following three teams during last year’s World Finals, will be released soon! You’ll get an inside look into their stories and the preparation they took for the 2024 Brawl Esports postseason. Grab your popcorn, and we will see you at the premiere on &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=http%25253A%25252F%25252Fyoutube.com%25252FBrawlStarsEsports')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;youtube.com/BrawlStarsEsports&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; in the coming weeks!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;BSC Season Breakdown&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For 2025, there are six monthly Seasons that you’ll need to tackle before fighting at the Last Chance Qualifier on your way to the World Finals! Each Season consists of the Championship Challenge, Monthly Qualifier, and Monthly Final!

&lt;b&gt;Championship Challenge

January 31&lt;/b&gt; is the first Championship Challenge of the year! It will be following the 2024 Season format. Fifteen wins earns you a spot in the Monthly Qualifier, but four losses knocks you out of the running. Play with a team to increase your chances of making it all the way. Can’t let the Bad Randoms know you’re trying to be an esports legend!

&lt;b&gt;Monthly Qualifiers

February 8 - 9&lt;/b&gt; is the first Monthly Qualifier during which your team can compete in your home region for a spot in the Monthly Finals! Now with brand new seeding changes that allow top teams to make it further without being stuck in randomly seeded brackets. BSC Partner Organizations will also automatically be granted a spot in the Day Two bracket. For more information and details, please check out the&lt;b&gt; 2025 Rulebook&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=http%25253A%25252F%25252Fsupr.cl%25252Fbscrules')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;supr.cl/bscrules&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;!

&lt;b&gt;Monthly Finals&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This year, we will break down the Monthly Finals by region to ensure you see ALL of the action - watch and earn rewards on &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=http%25253A%25252F%25252Fevent.brawlstars.com')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;event.brawlstars.com&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;! 

Each MF for February will take place on:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;East Asia - &lt;b&gt;February 15, &lt;/b&gt;3PM JST&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;EMEA - &lt;b&gt;February 16, &lt;/b&gt;2PM CET&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;South America - &lt;b&gt;February 22, &lt;/b&gt;3PM BRT&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;North America - &lt;b&gt;February 23,&lt;/b&gt; 3PM EST&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Looking for the schedule for this whole year? Check the &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%25253A%25252F%25252Fsupr.cl%25252Fbscrules')"&gt;Rulebook&lt;/a&gt;! &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Ranked Tie-in&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One aspect of Brawl Stars that we believe goes hand in hand with esports is Ranked. This year, we will explore integrating Ranked into the esports viewing and competitive experience. We’ll share more details later in the year, so keep an open ear for what’s to come.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We look forward to an amazing 2025 Season and can’t wait to share even more exciting moments with you! Get ready because it’s going to be a BLAST!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Signed,&lt;/i&gt;
&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Mr. Brawl Esports&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/6pGlSZ1XTz7v1GD0mlzNvQ/9c798ab905ea8c76e2ac3cc11d10a8a1/Footer.png?w=3000&amp;h=1055&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">KGSI4D1pOtE3jxfjHDISs</guid>
      <category>Esports</category>
      <enclosure url="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/5SVlOoMXobm5o65fbJPQ67/7bb6c7d24faa2df13c61710ac3846b0c/Thumb_800x433.png?w=800&amp;h=433&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill" length="0" type="image/png"/>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 11:06:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brawl Stars merch is back! Pre-order NOW!</title>
      <link>https://youtooz.com/collections/brawl-stars</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">63228Ho6yAQqw4uPk2ZyZR</guid>
      <category>News</category>
      <enclosure url="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/4BRPbRNvhHmV4JehBjlKg9/1f1ed3160bb5180f0c1b87bea0554f0b/0210_Youtooz_Launch__BS_Collectibles__800x433.png?w=800&amp;h=433&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill" length="0" type="image/png"/>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 21:31:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW PARTNER TEAMS | ARE SPRAYS GOING AWAY FOREVER!?</title>
      <link>https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/#/en/news/6Ab2QvT3v8gYYJbXYouxzL</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We have some incredibly exciting news on the 2025 &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%25253A%25252F%25252Fsupercell.com%25252Fen%25252Fgames%25252Fbrawlstars%25252Fblog%25252Fesports%25252Fbsc-2025season-kickoff%25252F')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Brawl Esports&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; Partner Program. We are welcoming &lt;b&gt;brand new&lt;/b&gt; teams to the program, and retiring the current set of team sprays FOREVER. That’s right - make sure you get them while you still can - more info below!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Firstly, we’re thrilled to announce that &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%25253A%25252F%25252Fx.com%25252Fzetadivision')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;ZETA&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%25253A%25252F%25252Fx.com%25252Fnatusvincere')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;NAVI&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%25253A%25252F%25252Fx.com%25252FSKGaming')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;SK Gaming&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%25253A%25252F%25252Fx.com%25252FTribeGaming')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Tribe Gaming&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%25253A%25252F%25252Fx.com%25252FReply_Totem')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Reply Totem&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%25253A%25252F%25252Fx.com%25252FSpacestation')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Spacestation Gaming&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%25253A%25252F%25252Fx.com%25252FFUTesportsgg')"&gt;&lt;u&gt; FUT Esports&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; will all be returning to Brawl Stars Championship this year, alongside &lt;b&gt;three new additions:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%25253A%25252F%25252Fx.com%25252FLOUDgg')"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;LOUD Esports&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;from Brazil, &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%25253A%25252F%25252Fx.com%25252FGenG')"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Gen.G Esports&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;from South Korea and &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%25253A%25252F%25252Fx.com%25252FTeamHeretics')"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Team Heretics&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;from Spain - let’s give them a warm welcome! The new team cosmetics will be added to the game with the next update!

The Partner Program is a collaboration between Supercell and select partner teams, bringing their competitive prestige to &lt;i&gt;Brawl Stars Championship.&lt;/i&gt; By purchasing their pins, profile icons, sprays or skins, you&amp;#39;re not only supporting your favorite teams but also contributing to the growth of Brawl Esports!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/6kS5RBlGagJmSjXJx1eYvk/fa55115d77597f21e1d21f21244d4d68/0206_WF_pins_800x300.png?w=800&amp;h=300&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;WELCOME TO THE NEW TEAMS!&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/FwCW01MS62VytHVLljfYG/f29384ca860dfda88a0a3a95da9bddce/player_icon_loud.png?w=800&amp;h=800&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bem-vindo – LOUD Esports&lt;/b&gt;

&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%25253A%25252F%25252Fx.com%25252FLOUDgg')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;LOUD Esports&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; has rapidly become a Brazilian powerhouse, celebrated for its vibrant fan culture and stellar performances in titles like Free Fire and Valorant—where they were crowned 2022 World Champions!

#goLOUD&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/6NPsiH0E3jWLPIkWgYKtQ0/5d432d79163592de433c0445c472ae33/player_icon_geng.png?w=800&amp;h=800&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;안녕하세요 – Gen.G Esports

&lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%25253A%25252F%25252Fx.com%25252FGenG')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Gen.G Esports&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; has earned global renown for its competitive excellence in League of Legends, while fostering a unique bridge between Eastern and Western gaming through diversity and education initiatives!

#GENGWIN&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/4j2rurMvMh0nnFoCtLkSsc/2b846b4d552151aea6585889c02699ef/player_icon_heretics.png?w=800&amp;h=800&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bienvenidos – Team Heretics

&lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%25253A%25252F%25252Fx.com%25252FTeamHeretics')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Team Heretics&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; is known for its competitive spirit and commitment to excellence across multiple titles — notably League of Legends, Valorant, and Rainbow Six Siege. Their vibrant brand shines through their creators and collaborations, reflecting a bold vision for esports and gaming!

#VamosHERETICS
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Partner sprays going away forever!?&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will soon be dropping a &lt;i&gt;brand new &lt;/i&gt;set of sprays for all the partner teams, meaning the current spray design will become an exclusive collector’s item! This will be the LAST chance to get your hands on them, as they will disappear from the shop FOREVER with the next game update coming soon. Make sure you grab yours now!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/3kyBEWrZ67tix2naSXwDj/e08a8b562ff48434c80916a1d858ebd8/0206_WF_sprays_800x470_FINAL.png?w=800&amp;h=470&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Keep an eye on our partner teams, and the official &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%25253A%25252F%25252Fx.com%25252FBrawl_esports')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Brawl Stars Esports&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; social media channels where we will be revealing more about the new sprays soon!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;WHERE CAN I FIND THE COSMETICS?&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When the partner Sprays, Pins and Profile Icons aren’t featured on the shop front page, you can always find them in the &lt;b&gt;Shop -&amp;gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;b&gt;Catalog -&amp;gt; Themes &lt;/b&gt;and clicking the icon shown here:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/7iBeZdaJ5mIy0Jy8DJtext/c6374e128c95f6a244d0b44572878c0e/catalog-esports-items-v2.png?w=2112&amp;h=1179&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;HOW TO BECOME PARTNER?&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you’re running a successful esports organization that can create exciting content around your Brawl Stars Team on par with the existing partner teams and is interested in joining the Program, look no further! We keep a close eye on applications coming through &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%25253A%25252F%25252Fforms.gle%25252FQQUcXto798ZZR7KP8')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;this form&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, and if your application catches our eye, we’ll contact you!

That said, the Brawl Stars Championship is &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%25253A%25252F%25252Fevent.supercell.com%25252Fbrawlstars%25252Fen%25252Fhow-to-compete')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;open to everyone&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, and all teams have the same opportunity to compete and win their part of the $2,000,000 prize pool!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;WHERE CAN I WATCH BSC!?&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our first Monthly Finals broadcast of the year lands on February 15th, and you can predict matches, watch, interact, and earn FREE rewards on &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=http%25253A%25252F%25252Fevent.brawlstars.com')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;event.brawlstars.com&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And just so you don’t miss any of the action - here are each of the broadcast dates for February:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;East Asia - &lt;b&gt;February 15, &lt;/b&gt;3PM JST&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;EMEA - &lt;b&gt;February 16,&lt;/b&gt; 2PM CET&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;South America - &lt;b&gt;February 22, &lt;/b&gt;3PM BRT&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;North America - &lt;b&gt;February 23,&lt;/b&gt; 3PM EST&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can find the BSC roadmap video &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%25253A%25252F%25252Fwww.youtube.com%25252Fwatch%25253Fv%25253DgRUCqKw65fo')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;here&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, and the rest of this season’s dates and lots more details in the &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=http%25253A%25252F%25252Fsupr.cl%25252Fbscrules')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;2025 Rulebook&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;LET’S BRAWL!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6Ab2QvT3v8gYYJbXYouxzL</guid>
      <category>Esports</category>
      <enclosure url="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/E2SHWzrm0tz7HkACSERsV/ed95419af0921aa6d6df410c14c0e1d1/0206_WF_Leon_800x433.png?w=800&amp;h=433&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill" length="0" type="image/png"/>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All about the Brawlentine's Community Event!</title>
      <link>https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/#/en/news/6QlDnXW1alykSncWh03MII</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the newest, most cursed community event in Brawl Stars history, Bo is on the hunt for his sweet Brawlentine, and YOU get to pick who he takes out on a date!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;HOW TO PARTICIPATE&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You just have to go to the News Tab and VOTE between 2 Brawler contestants competing for Bo’s affection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Together with each poll, you will also accumulate rewards into a pool that will be unlocked when the event ends on February 20th!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But that’s not all! If the whole community achieves a certain number of votes in a poll, the rewards associated with that poll will be DOUBLED! Each poll will have a specific target visible in the poll itself!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new poll will take place every 2 days, and between those days, a different bonus event will begin, such as Double XP, Mastery Madness, and Double Daily Starr Drops!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the last day of the event, the last poll with all the finalists will take place, and everyone in the community must come together to finally pick WHO GETS TO PASSIONATELY KISS BO! &lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;FULL SCHEDULE AND POSSIBLE REWARDS&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Day 1&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jacky VS Charlie&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;3 Presents OR 6 Presents (doubled)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Day 2&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Double XP	&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Day 3&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mandy VS Lola&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;500 Coins OR 1000 Coins&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Day 4&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;50% Mastery Madness&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Day 5&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Angelo VS Amber&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;2500 Bling OR Romantic Dynamike (and 2500 Bling)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Day 6&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Double Starr Drops&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Day 7&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rico VS Piper &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;10 Starr Drops - 20 Starr Drops&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Day 8&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;100% Mastery Madness&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Day 9&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mortis VS Melodie&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;1 Hypercharge Starr Drop OR 2 Hypercharge Starr Drops!!!!!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Day 10&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Final poll between the finalists&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Additionally, we’ll be bringing back the most played 2v2 modes throughout the whole event! &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The final set of rewards will then be delivered after the final poll on February 20th!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;THE CONTESTANTS&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Angelo&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amber&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Charlie&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jacky&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lola&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mandy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Melodie&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mortis&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Piper&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rico&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;GIVEAWAYS&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This time, you’ll get a chance to win 1 million Gems and split them with your best buddy!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To enter the giveaway, just post a Brawlentine’s message to your other Brawl-half! It can be on any social media. Just make sure to use the #Brawlentines and #BrawlStars hashtags!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We’ll pick 5 winners on the last day of the event, and they will share their prize with their special someone!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That’s all! The event starts now and will end on February 20th, so start voting!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6QlDnXW1alykSncWh03MII</guid>
      <category>Community</category>
      <enclosure url="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/4wCk2anfRwmirgess0zMZB/5ce0c5c86d13a65bed42c60c65155522/0207_Brawlentines__Community_Event__inbox_800x433_v2.png?w=800&amp;h=433&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill" length="0" type="image/png"/>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RANKED IS DEAD, AND RANKED IS BACK!! </title>
      <link>https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/#/en/news/1gnTAfjmERTS5QmTUzZKOL</link>
      <description>&lt;h1&gt;RANKED IS DEAD, AND RANKED IS BACK!! &lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;IMPORTANT NOTES:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The current Good Randoms Ranked Season is going to be shorter. The new Ranked Season starts with the next update on the 25th of February&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The changes below should be final, but things might still change when the new Ranked is released &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;ANYWAY, Big changes are coming, so let&amp;#39;s break them down!
&lt;b&gt;
Our main goals with the Ranked rework are: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Making Ranked more competitive for skilled players&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Encouraging more players to engage with Ranked and spark their interest in becoming better at Brawl&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rewarding players more for their time and effort&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Keeping every season fresh and exciting&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monetizing the game better and having a consistent source to sustain Brawl esports activities &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Pro Pass - the new Ranked progression system&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/7ibZbGSm6z6clpTbWStQwd/a2dd2f451b30d238e83503ddacbdf63f/0212_Pro_Pass_Icon_800x300.png?w=800&amp;h=300&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ranked is getting a Brawl Pass-like progression system called &lt;b&gt;Pro Pass.&lt;/b&gt; It also has a free track and a paid track, but unlike the Brawl Pass, the Pro Pass is 4 months long!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The reason why it is 4 months long is because it’s going to be tied to major esports events in the year. The first is the &lt;b&gt;Brawl Cup &lt;/b&gt;in May, the Last Chance Qualifier in September, and the World Finals in November.  The Current plan is to have 3 Pro Passes per year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/sKUdtOco8rU6j8kLgVpcD/fa91bba30f98315ca4b1c9ca3a3c015a/0212_Pro_Pass_XP_800x300__1_.png?w=800&amp;h=300&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To progress in the Pro Pass, you must collect Pro Pass XP, and it can be collected from:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Winning Ranked matches (similar to daily Brawl Pass XP for Brawl Pass, but the Pro Pass XP refreshes Weekly, and you have to win the match)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ranking up&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Watching and interacting with esports broadcasts on event.brawlstars.com throughout the year&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;You are not REQUIRED to watch Esports to complete the Pass, but it can speed up your progression (especially if you don’t reach higher ranks) and grant you more of the tail reward&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Purchasing the Pro Pass, which grants instant progression and 2x Pro Pass XP (and double the weekly limit)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The free track includes better rewards than the old Ranked system and a Legendary Starr Drop as the tail Reward!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;See the graphic below: &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/0kLAnuHzyFuMfBPk0Zome/3ebfdd02ffa2184f09943e91447a2e14/0212_Comparison_free_vs_old_free_800x880.png?w=800&amp;h=880&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s important to mention that Master Players are not receiving much of a buff in the free track (still a buff, though). But considering around 1% of the players who engage with Ranked get to Masters, and around 5% get to Legendary, this is going to be a more significant buff for 95%(ish) of the current Ranked players and hopefully more attractive for all the rest of the community as well. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The paid track costs $24.99* for the 4-month duration ($6.25 per month) and includes the following:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/3Zu8SwySfrJV309SnudfoY/3d393540f5800a9b63222f8946dd5ddd/0212_new_Paid_pro_800x485.png?w=800&amp;h=485&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* &lt;i&gt;Price may vary depending on your country/region.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;New Skin Rarity - Pro&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As you saw above, we&amp;#39;re introducing a new Skin Rarity: Pro!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pro Skins can be upgraded up to 11 times by collecting “Skin upgrade” items from the Pro Pass (or in Ranked Drops 8 months after the Skin release)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Each upgrade will give you either a visual improvement for the Skin, including a new Spawn VFX, or other cosmetics, including a new animated Brawler Battle Card&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;For every Season, you can get a Legendary-level Skin in the Free Track of the Pass!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The list of upgrades is as follows:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;1st Upgrade - Free Track: [Base Skin]
2nd Upgrade - Free Track: Pin x1, Profile Picture x1, and Spray x1
3rd Upgrade - Free Track: Special Attack effects
4th Upgrade - Free Track: [Upgraded Skin Model] 
5th Upgrade - Free Track: Pins x8
6th Upgrade - Free Track: Special Takedown effects
7th Upgrade - Paid Track: Animated Brawler Card - NEW COSMETIC!
8th Upgrade - Paid Track: Special Spawn &amp;amp; Respawn effects - NEW COSMETIC!
9th Upgrade - Paid Track: [Hypercharge form]
10th Upgrade - Paid Track: [Chroma 1]
11th Upgrade - Paid Track: [Chroma 2]&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first Pro Skin will be for Colt (because he obviously doesn’t have enough skins).
Check out the sneak peek for the Base Skin and some concepts!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/28q3mN5xjxty8U57JK0BoQ/7c2ae2a03925b2b1cb7bdbac4a45a004/RankedColt.png?w=4000&amp;h=1382&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Ranked is now more competitive!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our initial goal with the Ranked mode was to make it more receptive to casual players - which we reached! Ranked has around 10 times more players than its previous version (Power League)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, it became TOO casual for players who were looking for a challenge.
So, in this new rework:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;1. We added a new Tier for the highest level of play&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;New Rank above Masters: Pro&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pro Tier will also unlock the esports button (a special button unlocked for players who want to compete in Brawl Stars esports events)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Masters now has 3 Tiers, Masters I, II, III, which takes 1000 Elo each to advance&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Legendary now takes 750 Elo to advance each Tier&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;2. We are tackling Elo inflation from multiple angles&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Removed Floor Protection for Mythic and up (you can now be demoted back to Diamond if you lose more than you win in Mythic)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elo gain is increased, but Elo loss is more punishing for Legendary and above&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reduced Rank Boost values dramatically (Boost is still only until Mythic)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trio and Duo team-up is more restrictive as you increase Ranks (you can’t team up with a friend if their Rank is too low compared to yours)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;3. Improved Matchmaking&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;At lower Ranks, matchmaking time should become faster&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;At higher Ranks, matchmaking will become much more restrictive to your current Rank&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Searching will no longer increase Elo search range outside of your Rank restriction&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rank reset no longer puts everyone in Bronze I every month. If you’re Diamond 1 and above, it&amp;#39;s always -6 minor ranks from your ending rank. (If you’re Gold 3 and below, you get reset to Silver I and so on)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mythic and above will now require 12 Power Level 11 Brawlers to play&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;4. Removed modifiers &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;We felt modifiers were complex for casual players to understand and it restricted the viable Brawlers meta too much, so we’re scrapping it and will make Ranked Seasons feel fresh in other ways!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;5. Big change to Gadgets&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gadgets can now be used unlimited times but with a cooldown&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Each Gadget has its own cooldown based on how strong they are (starting from 7 seconds up to 30 seconds)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;+1 Gadget Gear has now been changed to a reduced cooldown Gear&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;(This change is not exclusive to Ranked, but the competitive Players would be the ones more interested in it)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;New Game Modes in Ranked&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To keep things fresh, we’ll be experimenting with a new game mode every month in Ranked&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;First, the mode will be tested in Trophies&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;If competitive, it will be added to Ranked&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;If not competitive, it may be adjusted or reworked before being added&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first game mode added will be CLEANING DUTY (same as Jelly Catch but reskinned)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brawl Hockey is the next candidate, but it still needs discussion and maybe some changes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Try Maxed out Brawlers every Season!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you don’t own all the Brawlers and are struggling with maxing them all out for Ranked, we have something for you&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Each season, 3 fully maxed-out Brawlers will be available for everyone to use ONLY in Ranked&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;These trial Brawlers will rotate each season&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;This will allow players to try out new Brawlers, experience max power levels, and fill in team gaps when needed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;These 3 maxed Brawlers will count towards the Brawler requirements for each Rank &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Changes to the Ranked Drop&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since Pro Skins are now guaranteed in the Pro Pass, we are changing Ranked Drops. We:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kept all previous Ranked Skins that were available in Ranked Drops&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Added more cosmetics such as Profile Pictures, Pins, and Sprays that can only be obtained from Ranked Drops&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Added Skin Upgrade item (but it’s only available in Ranked Drops 8 months after the release of the Pro Skin)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Added Pro Pass XP as one of the possible rewards to progress faster and get to the Legendary Starr Drop tail reward &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;New Paint Job for Ranked 2025&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We’re visually refreshing Ranked all together!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Battle Cards no longer decay and are permanently collected&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;New Ranked Tier visuals for all Ranks&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;New Battle Card visuals to collect&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can now customize which Battle Card to display in your profile&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/3PuahCdhflXRwJXISuC6Ua/1af1740684219871b9ac944f2943cf83/0207_ranked_cards_1920x1080.png?w=1920&amp;h=1080&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Other Ranked Improvements&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ranked 2.0 Seasons timing will be changed to start on the 3rd Thursday of each month, with the first Ranked 2.0 starting immediately after the update on February 25th, running until April 16th. The 2nd Ranked 2.0 Season will start April 17th, the 3rd Thursday of April&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The ranked emblem is now always shown in Ranked (instead of Brawler Mastery)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can now “Heart” Brawlers to favorite them!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Favorite Brawlers will be filtered to the front during the Ranked Pick phase&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Red and Blue side spawn viewing distance fixed to match&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, Ranked is expected to be more competitive, have better rewards, and provide a smoother progression with the &lt;b&gt;Pro Pass&lt;/b&gt;! Things can still change, but we expect to release everything above with the upcoming update. &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1gnTAfjmERTS5QmTUzZKOL</guid>
      <category>News</category>
      <enclosure url="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/5ic9rIkAFMdwIYoE9wCFoe/d75887a45a2a20d41432534ae5acc54c/0210_New_Ranked_Pass__In-game_Article__800x433.png?w=800&amp;h=433&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill" length="0" type="image/png"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 08:50:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It's here: Brawl's First Kiss!</title>
      <link>https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/#/en/news/38geLV5ddjaOAq6jFiArJJ</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">38geLV5ddjaOAq6jFiArJJ</guid>
      <category>Community</category>
      <enclosure url="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/5HfpqStWcW1cukZkzHQsUl/4eb20817a209b40d03396fda73e2acb6/Brawlentine_BoCharlieKiss_Final_copy__1_.jpg?w=800&amp;h=433&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 11:01:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RELEASE NOTES: RANKED REWORK, LUMI &amp; FINX!</title>
      <link>https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/#/en/news/2Oy5L9l7Wvv07s1oy7DgbF</link>
      <description>&lt;h1&gt;NEW PRO PASS, TWO NEW BRAWLERS, UNO COLLAB, GADGET CHANGES, AND MORE!&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;NEW BRAWLER: FINX!&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MYTHIC CONTROLLER&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The owner of Starr Park&amp;#39;s escape room, Finx is meant to help visitors complete their tasks. Instead, he uses his time controlling abilities to cause mischief and havoc! &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Also, he LOVES cats.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/5p57HyJtCkeAPIRfy7SLPX/4aa03a65f97880f13b10da237d4099fe/Finx_Final_extended.png?w=1500&amp;h=901&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;MAIN ATTACK: CHRONOCAST&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finx fires 3 long range projectiles, with the outer ones dealing 50% damage of the center projectile.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;SUPER: TIME WARP&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finx warps time in an area, decreasing the projectile speed of enemy Brawlers caught in the Super, while increasing the projectile speed of any teammates and himself. Finx&amp;#39;s projectiles will also get a damage buff.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/2vx6Efrk1ckPngnuE7T0Av/85a76cb208b7da841e0c6b01b6593161/brawler_finx_render_bg.png?w=900&amp;h=900&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;STAR POWER: PRIMER&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/1MXsJbXmpP35aDtNqfNeRB/df1e96c2b7d1131f476bc3fdc3728a0e/PRIMER.png?w=277&amp;h=289&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Damage dealt from Finx&amp;#39;s projectiles that are sped up by Time Warp, will increase the duration of his Super.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;STAR POWER: HIEROGLYPH HALT&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/4Zs2mRnk2xn78MdhVgaFT6/fdeb73efbff92a7b19b2fcf408135729/HIEROGLYPH_HALT.png?w=277&amp;h=289&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finx reduces the reload speed of any enemy Brawlers hit by his main attack for a short duration.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;GADGET: BACK TO THE FINXTURE&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/6T7O3nGiI39nxMBCisVBu6/1312d986355ffb166ee9d81a68207d76/BACK_TO_THE_FINXTURE.png?w=264&amp;h=278&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finx steps back in time, returning to the position and ammo he had a few seconds ago.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;GADGET: NO ESCAPE&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/3Oa9An5kEW094eu9FOfFDa/54a202ab51b837345f8d0bb1909dc02f/NO_ESCAPE.png?w=264&amp;h=278&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finx&amp;#39;s next center projectile from his main attack temporarily freezes the enemy in time, making them unable to take actions, but also making them immune to any damage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;NEW BRAWLER: LUMI&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MYTHIC DAMAGE DEALER&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A passionate metalhead and a talented drummer, Lumi traded her drumsticks for morning stars when she got her job at Starr Park. She controls elements of ice and fire, which reflects her shy nature and her burning passion for music!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/29pxLjOWt4FFcEDhYQPpWZ/1069a1bb16351333001176f913cc6bbd/Supercell_Lumi.png?w=900&amp;h=537&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;MAIN ATTACK: GOOD MORNING... STAR&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lumi throws one of her morning stars. She can throw both of her weapons, with her third attack recalling them, dealing damage to any enemies caught in their path!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;SUPER: BLAST BEAT&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lumi pounds the ground three times, causing explosions that deal area damage. The third explosion briefly snares enemies, making them unable to move but still able to attack.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/6C0S4YsCR6YtPUuRzPTLsI/78746d1f7b683f1095874ec070c0c694/brawler_lumi_render_bg_Pose2.png?w=900&amp;h=900&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;STAR POWER: 42% BURNT&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/aeOTMQ4HJP3NQerc0UkhL/6cdfad3d861f0ed82539ac30d57b8421/42__BURNT.png?w=277&amp;h=289&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The explosions from Lumi&amp;#39;s Blast Beat also set the area alight for a few seconds. This fire damage also scales with explosion damage. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;STAR POWER: HALF-TIME&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/6BaFdNQN13QRLjKx3GOhLp/f417d552ba56dd8d02b39b419b4b696c/HALF-TIME.png?w=277&amp;h=289&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lumi temporarily slows enemies hit by her recalled morning stars.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;GADGET: HIT THE LIGHTS&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/7jqon2aXGI1OAFbowbxUg7/ff8d4c6b6ecbd6ae3c9119ecfaabc90d/HIT_THE_LIGHTS.png?w=264&amp;h=278&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lumi iginites her morning stars on the ground, producing flames which damage nearby enemies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;GADGET: GRIM AND FROSTBITTEN&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/G9ZvzKExFpUQuFH8cZmZW/59bad1105f514b22612639926f85b63a/GRIM_AND_FROSTBITTEN.png?w=264&amp;h=278&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lumi creates freezing winds around her morning stars on the ground, creating a slippery surface.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/6LlSU6o2d6tV4r9JzgG9Av/f2a9b5ced3a301555ede360cf301d0e1/0210_New_Ranked_Pass__In-game_Article__1600x443.png?w=1600&amp;h=443&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;RANKED REWORK: PRO PASS, PRO SKINS, MORE REWARDS!&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;PRO PASS: NEW RANKED PROGRESSION&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/477KWwFPD89b5OWANZ1xHS/fa9018acbec402b6108c1711da8b177a/pro_pass_icon.png?w=3183&amp;h=4000&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ranked is getting a Brawl Pass-like progression system called &lt;b&gt;Pro Pass.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Pro Pass&lt;/b&gt; also has a free progress track and a paid progress track, but unlike the Brawl Pass, the Pro Pass is 4 months long!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why is it 4 months long? Each Pro Pass Season is going to be tied to major esports events throughout the year. In 2024, these are the &lt;b&gt;Brawl Cup &lt;/b&gt;in May, the &lt;b&gt;Last Chance Qualifier&lt;/b&gt; in September, and the &lt;b&gt;World Finals&lt;/b&gt; in November. The Current plan is to have 3 Pro Pass Seasons per year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;BETTER REWARDS&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The free track includes better, more achievable rewards than the old Ranked system and even has a Legendary Starr Drop as the tail Reward!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;#39;s break it down:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/0kLAnuHzyFuMfBPk0Zome/3ebfdd02ffa2184f09943e91447a2e14/0212_Comparison_free_vs_old_free_800x880.png?w=800&amp;h=880&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;PROGRESS AND GET REWARDS...&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/5nJbHYCk6G5lbTHueghlVH/ba7ba349e9f98a3d6895110a4fe6d5bc/ranked_point.png?w=228&amp;h=269&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With &lt;b&gt;Pro Pass XP&lt;/b&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To progress in the &lt;b&gt;Pro Pass&lt;/b&gt;, you must collect &lt;b&gt;Pro Pass XP&lt;/b&gt; by:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Winning Ranked matches (similar to daily Brawl Pass XP for Brawl Pass, but the Pro Pass XP refreshes Weekly, and you have to win the match)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ranking up&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Watching and interacting with esports broadcasts on event.brawlstars.com throughout the year&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Purchasing the Pro Pass, which grants instant progression and double Pro Pass XP (which also doubles the weekly Pro Pass XP limit)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;PAID PRO PASS REWARDS&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The paid track costs $24.99* for the 4-month duration ($6.25 per month) and includes all of the rewards listed above!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;* &lt;i&gt;Price may vary depending on your country/region.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/3Zu8SwySfrJV309SnudfoY/3d393540f5800a9b63222f8946dd5ddd/0212_new_Paid_pro_800x485.png?w=800&amp;h=485&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;NEW SKIN RARITY: PRO&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pro Pass comes with a new unique &amp;amp; upgradeable &lt;b&gt;Skin Rarity: Pro&lt;/b&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Pro Skins&lt;/b&gt; are upgradeable Skins, which can be upgraded as you progress through the Pro Pass!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/2F0Wl4juhimwxkyLhewPwc/bd5ac0bada7a0c148c13deb5184276b1/0224_Update_Release__Ranked_Colt_Skin__192x1080.png?w=1920&amp;h=1080&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;GOOD TO KNOW&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pro Skins can be upgraded up to 11 times by collecting “Skin upgrades” from the Pro Pass (or in Ranked Drops 8 months after the Skin release)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Each upgrade will give you either a visual improvement for the Skin, including the brand new spawn VFX, or other cosmetics, like the new animated Brawler Battle Cards!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Every Season, you can get a Legendary-level Skin in the Free Track of the Pro Pass!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;The first Pro Skin is ASTRAL COLT!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/2ZeTJetmX78N7VvAgonTOg/b051f1cda7824c01a158bdf3891906ea/ranked_colt_hc_render_bg.png?w=1000&amp;h=1000&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;A MORE COMPETITIVE RANKED EXPERIENCE&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/3YyTZFlkPwzIcZKHAOeDxF/8d517cd51a81aa7c46da41959bb9a821/icon_rank_sticker_pro.png?w=663&amp;h=586&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1. We added a new Tier for the highest level of play - PRO&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;2. We are tackling Elo inflation from multiple angles&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;3. Improved Matchmaking&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;4. Removed modifiers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;New Game Modes in Ranked&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To keep things fresh, we’ll be experimenting with a new game mode every month in Ranked. These will be tested for competitiveness in regular Trophy game modes before making their way to the big leagues!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;WOULD YOU LIKE TO KNOW MORE?&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are SO many more changes coming with the Ranked rework. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So many in fact, that it has it&amp;#39;s own release notes article! Here you will find all of the detailed changes coming to the Ranked rework (there&amp;#39;s a lot).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;a href="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/#/en/news/1gnTAfjmERTS5QmTUzZKOL"&gt;👉TAP HERE FOR MORE RANKED INFO👈&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;HYPERCHARGES&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;12 Brawlers are getting Hypercharges this update!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They will be released in 2 stages, with each release containing 6 Hypercharges.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;RELEASE 1&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;CARL: FLAMESPIN&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/38UmkfMIhPxYPyuNhC7iOy/5ca58d94d16e4cb54089644f1acf1d0b/FLAMESPIN.png?w=201&amp;h=244&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Carl’s Super now leaves a blazing trail of rocks that scorch the earth wherever he goes, burning enemies that touch them!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;MANDY: SUGAR FOR ALL!&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/3Q7MlXVUhyV1buRSXAZ6id/667304dbcc6a17aad2341368f7fa1081/SUGAR_FOR_ALL_.png?w=201&amp;h=244&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mandy fires her Super in three different directions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;HANK: HOMING FISH-ILES&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/70lR2jHrHsIs8NCxAOECKQ/783d329bfb31dde29ca957f6bf6db1ac/HOMING__FISH-ILES.png?w=201&amp;h=244&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Fish Torpedoes that Hank fires with his Super have been upgraded to home in on targets!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;BO: CATCH A BEAR&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/521XKFEJFUPPg2SlIBhB4B/6ec4f95310c1f463e0fb1c050d91bb8f/CATCH__A_BEAR.png?w=201&amp;h=244&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bo’s Super deploys 5 mines instead of 3. These do not override any mines already placed by his Super, so it is possible to have more than 3 mines on the map!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;BEA: PROTECT THE QUEEN&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/3zHGisMlNmxcDdPLVkjlCP/8690d04adbb549aa2a0f576fa5ea5846/PROTECT__THE_QUEEN.png?w=201&amp;h=244&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bea’s Super projectiles split into 2 when at max distance (and on hit), increasing her Super’s distance and spread even more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;MR. P: PORTERS, ASSEMBLE!&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/3m94tetwxqxkhzbq2XyHbS/db801d7de381c77ac3a7153dc494fbdd/SUPER_PORTERS___ASSEMBLE_.png?w=201&amp;h=244&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mr. P’s home base now spawns much stronger porters and he can have two active ‘Super Porters’ at the same time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;RELEASE 2&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;MEG: TUNGSTEN TOUGHNESS&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/222kBeNqIibR8yRpxHgqP6/238413cd62fd287063a321989e9005ce/REAL_STEEL.png?w=201&amp;h=244&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meg&amp;#39;s Mecha has an increased swipe range when activating it&amp;#39;s Super. While out of the Mecha, Meg pops a defensive shield for protection.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;CHESTER: CRUNCHY, CHEWY, GOOEY&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/6EfVuG3vSZyrWjvbEZyYfJ/e436eb6b43e4e7bd5574a7248dc6faf3/CHESTER_S.png?w=201&amp;h=244&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Chester combines several of his Super abilities into one. He throws a sweet that explodes and deals damage, spreads a poison cloud, and then leaves a slowing area for a few seconds afterwards.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;LOLA: INFLATED EGO&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/6jyoIkvobKrf8RVQe4CTh0/fa79cd592347b11e5e6e942be01b8f29/INFLATED_EGO.png?w=201&amp;h=244&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Spawns a mega inflated Ego with increased health and damage!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;GROM: GROM BOMB GOES BOOM!&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/1CZEO0GRefVzlOutdApQQw/31828385451559906db4d4677ca2932f/GROM_BOMB__GOES_BOOM_.png?w=201&amp;h=244&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Grom’s Super gains a secondary explosion after the first, in an X-pattern. This explosion also deals damage, breaks walls and knocks enemies back.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;BUSTER: PLOT ARMOR&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/6OrAoprXkkkgopeTOOTxiV/ca6d61d585c10569fb8a952b0bee3c73/FILM_REEL.png?w=201&amp;h=244&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Buster&amp;#39;s shield is now 360 degrees around him and reflected projectiles deal more damage!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;SAM: HYPER FIST&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/6QQCpEYJrGR0prRb4VMWii/69d1f41f4950fdd9e4aaf453727519fa/SAM_S.png?w=201&amp;h=244&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sam’s Knuckle Busters travel faster and will fully charge his Super if they hit an enemy Brawler during the Hypercharge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;SEASON 34: DARK SANDS&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Sands of Time have been corrupted by Finx&amp;#39;s chronomancy and replaced by Dark Sands that have awakened ancient evils!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/0r7NrYttJj6YknbG59Fiz/d518ccda050d5e1aee936875b43727de/DarkSands.png?w=1500&amp;h=901&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;SKINS&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mummified Frank | Brawl Pass&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Charcoal Frank | Chroma #1 | Brawl Pass Plus&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Papyrus Frank | Chroma #2 | Brawl Pass Plus&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ruffesses II | Super Rare&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Queen Juju | Super Rare&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pharaollie | Epic&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mystic Meeple | Epic&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scarab Squeak | Epic&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;SEASON 35: SUPER BRAWL&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The evil Insector and his sidekick Electroid have made Starr Park the next target of their crime spree.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Can Spectaculor and his heroes handle the threat? Or will they need help from a mysterious vigilante...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/1QJYOqadBl44go3v2h5ZXu/9f1377878e39cb5a0537b53845a9164c/MakeHeroes_LoadingScreen-_1_.png?w=1500&amp;h=966&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;SKINS&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Justice Smasher Bibi | Brawl Pass&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Injustice Smasher Bibi | Chroma #1 | Brawl Pass Plus&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Virtue Smasher Bibi | Chroma #2 | Brawl Pass Plus&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;The below Skins were designed by artists in our community that won the &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%25253A%25252F%25252Fmake.supercell.com%25252Fen%25252Fcampaign%25252F7LN7eOAgpUwRCHUVN0NSx7%25253Fsort%25253Drandom%252526status%25253Dfinalist')"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Supercell MAKE competition: Brawlers, Assemble!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Spectaculor Sam | Epic&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;by FinnyShow&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Firewing Janet | Epic&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;by WarpWave&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Protector Grom | Epic&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;by J-Y Jacky&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Insector Carl | Epic&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;by Artho_Max&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Electroid Chuck | Epic&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;by Gedi-Kor&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Equilibrium Buster | Epic&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;by Vinuui&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;BRAWL STARS x UNO&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ever wanted to UNO reverse someone in Brawl? Well now you can!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/7wrTn6ZrQlAJQKbv59XIF5/4108b5771e7aef97a203a41adf9a4598/BS_Uno_WIP8.png?w=1500&amp;h=902&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;NEW GAME MODE&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/3DYNIzAKuUqn3fka2mACvP/9a6cab402a214d1f5ff25534833a60fc/spray_uno3.png?w=513&amp;h=513&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We&amp;#39;re releasing a brand new UNO game mode, but with a classic Brawl twist! &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this game mode, each team starts with a hand of UNO cards, which must all be thrown into the discard pile to win the game!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The winning team is the first to empty their hands and have no UNO cards left.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;THROWING CARDS = SPECIAL POWERS&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/6J70d3bOlx5ALPEPiLANDJ/53e9189b8cc2ac61f6f90dd81cbe0ba5/spray_uno2.png?w=513&amp;h=513&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By throwing specific UNO cards, Brawlers will activate certain special powers!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;+2&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gives you and your teammates 2 Power Cubes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Skip&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Silences the entire enemy team&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reverse&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Destroys any cards the enemy team are currently holding and respawns them at their base&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;GOOD TO (U)KNOW&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brawlers can body block flying enemy cards&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;UNO cards can be carried while using a jump pad&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;UNO COSMETICS&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/3HqkNRsHrEjyFN3u7FdRi5/23ba4af0bfec679bc6578f84f92650a6/spray_uno1.png?w=513&amp;h=513&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alongside the new game mode, Chester is getting a unique UNO Skin, which is perfect to UNO reverse enemy Brawlers with.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are also a bunch of other UNO cosmetics coming, so keep your eyes open!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;GADGET CHANGES&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Gadgets&lt;/b&gt; no longer have charges but are now based on &lt;b&gt;cooldowns&lt;/b&gt;! &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This means that you can use Gadgets whenever they are charged, and &lt;b&gt;can be used an&lt;/b&gt; &lt;b&gt;unlimited amount of times in a match&lt;/b&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;GOOD TO KNOW:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gadgets will have different cooldown times depending on how powerful they are. For example, Lily&amp;#39;s &amp;#39;Vanish&amp;#39; Gadget has a 22 sec cooldown, compared to Rosa&amp;#39;s &amp;#39;Grow Light&amp;#39; Gadget, which has a 10 sec cooldown.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Gear that added +1 Gadget charge now reduces the cooldown of a Gadget by 15%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;DAILY STREAK - DAILY REWARDS!&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;(NOTE: The Daily Streak feature will be launching a few days after the update goes live - not on update day!)&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
Log in daily and get rewards! Keep the streak going and watch the number go higher and on fire!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Also, open a mystical fortune cookie. Oooh! Mystical.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;OTHER SKINS&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rare Skins&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dark Knight Lumi&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jurassic Finx&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fiendish Amber&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beach Belle&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;First Mate Fang&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cored Eve&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;True Gold &amp;amp; True Silver&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Juju&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meeple&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shade&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ollie&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Misc.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Carnaval Mandy | Mythic&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;P.E.K.K.A.S.H | Supercell ID Rewards&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/6CghG0ptuM9Lzwafl75NW1/2071a5e26d4080be2b366f4356e65ae5/Screenshot_2025-02-24_at_13.52.41.png?w=2552&amp;h=1406&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;BALANCE CHANGES&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;BUFFS&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;OLLIE&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/2pKffsIfaAESH4bVYg6ZAq/dc044d9f59e717a769e031a26d3c477c/ollie_clap_pin.png?w=240&amp;h=221&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Increased Main Attack Damage: 850 → 1000&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Super: Ollie will not silence himself anymore, now uses 50% of his max ammo&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;MEEPLE&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/41aKNMWp6HUr9K2qrqtqvk/6f68e93724b96116dfd7b7f1b5587cb5/meeple_clap_pin.png?w=232&amp;h=221&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Increased Main Attack reload speed: 2 sec → 1.9 sec&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;RUFFS&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/5qSu3iQAUMkNyhoCshWlHB/7b657b4bdf8dbafd14c5fa386630ce70/ruffs_clap_pin.png?w=221&amp;h=221&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Increased Hypercharge Damage &amp;amp; Shield: 10 → 15%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;NERFS&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;GUS&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/2c6H4GPCR2jlcuVEBVNIAY/6f2fc69361061fa724ada7e807d5e3b6/gus_sad_pin.png?w=221&amp;h=221&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Decreased Main Attack Damage: 1120 → 1080&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Decreased Gadget ‘Kooky Popper’ Damage: 2240 → 2160&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;STU&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/1EfMRDKyKooKrjrkkDEFBs/8d550e4a4be33e27c998be1efe71220b/stu_facepalm_pin.png?w=221&amp;h=221&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Decreased Star Power Gaso-Heal max health: 10% → 8%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;PENNY&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/3mDpg3asHmujRTFdvNpruN/f5acbb3b1b706a794dff8e772a10f1a2/emoji_penny_sad.png?w=221&amp;h=221&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Decreased Hypercharge charge rate: 35 → 30&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;JUJU&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/V70Z7FffXijTVgbR7j7xO/72304e35ab0a705a402c9661bd242095/juju_sad_pin.png?w=222&amp;h=221&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Decreased Super charge rate: 90 → 72 &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;(5 → 6 Earth attack hits, 6 → 7 Grass/Water attack hits)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;MAX&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/4JXDw18tZ5uHCCUBeW5Yl2/5c7aebd9227c147ef8a4efb0dbafbb7a/max_sad_pin.png?w=221&amp;h=221&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Decreased Hypercharge charge rate: 40 → 35&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;RICO&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/6Zon0LviWajY2yAG9vdtSh/32ef33094ea4e5dffcaf738ca5ae0653/rico_sad_pin.png?w=221&amp;h=221&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Decreased Hypercharge charge rate: 40 → 35&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;LOU&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/4MHWKid2GnvxJKJRtcIKaX/87104df082f7ac6902748d9c0253adfc/lou_sad_pin.png?w=221&amp;h=221&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Decreased Hypercharge charge rate: 40 → 30&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;OTHER CHANGES&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;KENJI&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;img src="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/37p36iGNXpOlz78JHfrYSd/ce2db1119e1514185cb0991d035e9448/kenji_happy_pin.png?w=221&amp;h=221&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now accurately shows return location when using his Super&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;TRIO SHOWDOWN IS HERE TO STAY!&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;This game mode ended up being a fan favorite, so we decided to add it to the game permanently, because... why not!?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;To keep things as fair as possible, we decided to make major changes to the current Trio Showdown map pool, to provide a more balanced gameplay experience. We made adjustments for Trio Showdown to some of the most iconic Showdown maps and and ALSO added completely new maps created by the community that follow the same rationale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;MAPS, GAME MODES &amp; ROTATION CHANGES&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;Ranked Game Modes &amp;amp; Maps&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Season 1 (3 Maps each)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brawl Ball&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Knockout&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gem Grab&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hot Zone&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brawl Hockey&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Season 2  (3 Maps each)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brawl Ball&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Knockout &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gem Grab&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Heist&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cleaning Duty&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;Environments&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Removed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Snowtel&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Starrforce&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Giftshop&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Toons&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fighting Game&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Added:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dragon Forge&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Retropolis&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tara’s Bazaar&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Egypt&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;Maps&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Showdown&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Skull Creek (Modified)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rockwall Brawl (Modified)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Feast or Famine (Modified)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cavern Churn (Modified)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Acid Lakes (Modified)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Flying Fantasies (Modified)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Island Invasion (Modified)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Double Trouble (Modified)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;UNO&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wild Greens (New)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reverse Crossing (New)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Skipyard (New)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wipeout 5v5/Knockout 5v5&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Big Battle Basin (New)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unhappy Arena (New)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Survival Of The Meanest (New)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mirages Of Madness (New)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Courtyard Clashers (New)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brawl Ball 5v5&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Polar Park (New)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stockpile Stadium (New)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Siberian Stand Off (New)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gem Grab 5v5&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shimmering Forest (New)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Arctic Ambush (New)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Treasure Island (New)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brawl Hockey 3v3&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Below Zero&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cool Box&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Starr Garden&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cleaning Duty&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rubbish Rampage&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trash Bash&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dumpster Drive&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Waste Haven&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;In The Bins&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Garbage Yard&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Litterbug Lane&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Treasure Hunt&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Middle Management&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Excellent Excavations&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brawl Starrgate&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;OTHER IMPROVEMENTS&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;GENERAL&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Battle Cards &amp;amp; Fame Frames are now part of your collection and you can choose which ones you want to equip and show off!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can now Favorite Brawlers in the Brawler screen by clicking the heart icon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Favorited Brawlers will be placed at the start of the Brawler select screen in Ranked/Mega Pig picks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Favorite Brawlers can be toggled to show at the top of the Brawler list (the same way as Brawlers with Quests etc).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Re-ordered Quick Chat messages to put the most frequently used ones first&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;True Gold &amp;amp; True Silver Skins have been given a polish by Gale, and now have a new updated shiny look!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Added missing VFX to Demon Emz Skin&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt; Kenji’s Super return location VFX has been improved to be more accurate and visible&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;PERFORMANCE&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reduced game’s memory consumption overall, so lower end devices should crash less.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Starr Road has reduced memory usage, improved responsiveness and sees the return of fully animated Brawlers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Performance improved for Mad Evil Manor maps&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;BUG FIXES&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixed an edge case where Sam’s gauntlet &amp;amp; Gus&amp;#39; attacks sometimes went in a strange angle when shooting over water or certain objects&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixed Kit exploit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixed Brawler textures appearing in low resolution on high-end devices&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixed Pop Melodie Skin accidentally playing Poco&amp;#39;s attack sound (s&lt;i&gt;he writes her own music, we promise!)&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixed Angelo&amp;#39;s &amp;quot;Master Fletcher&amp;quot; Gadget cancelling his Super&amp;#39;s Damage over Time&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixed Byron&amp;#39;s Main Attack not triggering Haptic Feedback&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixed Rosa&amp;#39;s base Skin using the Main Attack VFX of another Skin during her Hypercharge&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixed Willow&amp;#39;s Star Power &amp;quot;Love is Blind&amp;quot; not reducing the reload speed of enemies&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixed the Brawl Hockey puck passing through certain obstacles on the Air Sports Arena map&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixed a crash that could occur when claiming rewards from past Events&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixed Brawlers being unable to pick up the Air Hockey puck as soon as it bounces from a pinball bumper&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixed Sam briefly losing upper body animation if his Super was activated when moving &lt;i&gt;(he&amp;#39;s old and his back gets stiff sometimes)&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixed 3 Pins not being able to be sent in Club Chat&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;GLOBAL PRICING CHANGES&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;As part of our efforts to find affordable pricing for different regions of the world, we&amp;#39;re starting to roll out global pricing with this update&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;We still need to do some tests before doing a full rollout to all the target regions, so these local price changes will first be live in a few select countries only, and more regions will be gradually added in the coming months&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since we&amp;#39;re still testing things, different players might also see different prices even within the same region&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brawl Pass donations will also be temporarily deactivated in the regions where testing is taking place and will be reactivated once these are completed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2Oy5L9l7Wvv07s1oy7DgbF</guid>
      <category>Release Notes</category>
      <enclosure url="https://brawlstars.inbox.supercell.com/xdjcscmv3zo3/ON2j8fOwN2vnF8wND6gRC/886e8f910ba3d76168b51f722e36889a/finx800.png?w=800&amp;h=433&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill" length="0" type="image/png"/>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 05:54:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
