<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Boombeach - News</title>
    <link>https://github.com/skrwo/supercell-inbox-rss/</link>
    <description>RSS wrapper of Boombeach inbox News</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 01:43:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>This January on Boom Beach</title>
      <link>https://boombeach.inbox.supercell.com/#/en/news/5GCSOabeKZsHs0OndBjGSp</link>
      <description>&lt;h1&gt;This January in Boom Beach&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As we kick off the new year, prepare for an exhilarating month filled with thrilling events and opportunities to showcase your strategic prowess on the battlefield.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;3 - 5: Warrior &amp;amp; Zooka Mania: Combine the lightning-fast strikes of Warriors with the explosive power of Zookas for a devastating offensive duo!

6 - 8: Cryo Bomb: Freeze your enemies in their tracks with this chilling Gunboat Ability, perfect for creating tactical advantages.

6 - 12: Cryo Tank: Deploy these icy behemoths to slow enemy defenses and pave the way for your troops.

10 - 12: Grenadier &amp;amp; Laser Ranger Mania: Unleash a barrage of explosives and precision laser fire with this formidable long-range combination!

17 - 19: Heavy &amp;amp; Mech Mania: Bring the brawn to the battlefield with the unbeatable duo of Heavies and Mechs, creating an unstoppable frontline.

20 - 22: Explosive Drones: Take Explosive Drones to the battlefield and devastate your opponent!

24 - 26: Lunar Mega Crab: Celebrate the Lunar New Year with this special edition of Mega Crab, offering unique challenges and rewards!

27 - Feb 16: Warships Season 70: Set sail for a new season of Warships featuring fresh layouts, exciting strategies, and exclusive rewards.

27 - Feb 2: Turret Engineer: Upgrade your offensive game with this proto troop, perfect for your attacks.

31 - Feb 2: Bombardier &amp;amp; Medic Mania: Close out the month with a bang by pairing the long-range devastation of Bombardiers with the healing support of Medics.
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5GCSOabeKZsHs0OndBjGSp</guid>
      <category>Blog</category>
      <enclosure url="https://boombeach.inbox.supercell.com/cf7umh1jvp53/4VOqufY8ReD1ae4W29QNSq/1b0cd83e09953a42880abfe8380270c1/BlogPost_Thumbnail.png?w=900&amp;h=493&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill" length="0" type="image/png"/>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>January update</title>
      <link>https://boombeach.inbox.supercell.com/#/en/news/5fo3uezLnUznDOFIF4ugEV</link>
      <description>&lt;h1&gt;January Update&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the January mid-life update, “So small it does not even get a name”. 
In addition to the usual bug fixes, we have some balancing done for the Engraver. 

&lt;b&gt;Fixes and improvements &lt;/b&gt;
●  Fixed persistent bases (Ops and MegaCrab) not getting correctly destroyed if Sabotage engraving is active. 
●  Missing spaces have been added to battle-end resource rewards. 
●  Fixed Squad Leaders not getting saved correctly when assigned to the first Landing Craft. 
●  Fixed an issue with Warships character unlock choice node not always unlocking correctly. 
●  Ground units once again do damage to Sky Shield structure HP instead of shield HP.  Air units still attack the shield. 
●  Some info text in Mystical Monument has been resized to be more legible. 
●  Immobile units do not show &amp;quot;Slow&amp;quot; movement speed on the unit stats page anymore. 
●  Progression for Warrior health restore on attack has been smoothed, upgrades will not show negative increases anymore. 
●  Battle log will show which engravings were active during battle. 
●  If Hero ability spawns critters, tapping the info now shows their stats. 

&lt;b&gt;Balancing &lt;/b&gt;
●  Engraving logic has been changed. Engravings are now activated instantly at the cost of 2 Power Powder. Engravings stay active for 12 hours instead of being permanently activated. 
●  Armor engraving logic change; At first level, the base damage per shot is reduced by 100 damage or 40% of the shot’s damage, whichever is less. Upgrading the engraving will increase the percentage up to 80% reduction, while the fixed reduction is always 100 damage. 
●  Leech engraving values reduced from [5% --&amp;gt; 25%] to [5% --&amp;gt; 15%] 
●  Squad Leaders can no longer be resurrected, the base unit is resurrected instead. 
●  Prevent buying trader offers if the resource type is capped. 
●  Hidden Warrior barracks numbers doubled in WS. 

&lt;b&gt;Other features &lt;/b&gt;
●  Some old accounts do not have an age set. Age popup will be shown for these accounts after the update. 
●  Auto Fast Forward After Battle has been added. Once the HQ has been destroyed, time speedup is automatically applied for the automatic destruction of the remaining base. This feature can be toggled on or off in the gameplay settings page.

Engraver cost reduction and time reduction:
The main reason for reducing the cost of the Engraver is to encourage players to experiment with different engravings and swap them out as needed. Please note that this feature is still in development and will continue to expand. We plan to further tune the Engraver system in future updates.

Engraving Balance:
We need to rebalance various engravings to ensure they are equally desirable. For now we have decided to nerf one and change the mechanics of another.

Leech Nerf
The Leech engraving has proven to be particularly strong, so it will receive a significant nerf to bring it in line with other options.

Armor Nerf
We have redesigned the armor system to account for the lower-level defenses in Operations while ensuring it remains useful at all levels of play.

We appreciate your understanding and continued support as we work to improve the game experience for all players.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5fo3uezLnUznDOFIF4ugEV</guid>
      <category>Blog</category>
      <enclosure url="https://boombeach.inbox.supercell.com/cf7umh1jvp53/2Dxd96hhDvi4t6YzbmZ85D/6c8646478246d71cf84273addd018c1b/BlogPost_Thumbnail.png?w=900&amp;h=493&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill" length="0" type="image/png"/>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This February in Boom Beach</title>
      <link>https://boombeach.inbox.supercell.com/#/en/news/1X3TW2OY4bVfaMHY7P5iCu</link>
      <description>&lt;h1&gt;This February in Boom Beach&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As we dive into February, get ready for an action-packed month filled with intense battles and strategic opportunities! Here’s what’s coming up:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;3 - 5: Super Warrior: Unleash these mighty warriors onto the battlefield, striking with immense power and durability to turn the tide in your favor!

7 - 9: RifleZooka Mania: Combine the rapid-fire might of Riflemen with the explosive precision of Zookas for a well-balanced offensive force.

10 - 16: Protector: Deploy Protectors to keep your troops alive longer, shield them from incoming fire, and ensure your advance remains unstoppable.

14 - 16: GrenCryo Mania: Pair the explosive chaos of Grenadiers with the freezing power of Cryoneers for a devastating crowd-control combo!

17 - 19: Crystal Critters: These healing critters enhance your tactical plays and provide valuable support to your advancing troops.

21 - 23: Cryo Crab: Brace yourself for the icy challenge of Cryo Crab, a chilling edition of Mega Crab packed with frosty obstacles and exciting rewards!

24 - Mar 2: Warships Season 71: Set sail for a fresh Warships season featuring new layouts, tactical innovations, and exclusive prizes!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1X3TW2OY4bVfaMHY7P5iCu</guid>
      <category>Blog</category>
      <enclosure url="https://boombeach.inbox.supercell.com/cf7umh1jvp53/1s86FJnMNwBfGUIobP5Cw8/229a29424cd433bba4c81997b4f04e4f/BlogPost_Thumbnail.png?w=900&amp;h=493&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill" length="0" type="image/png"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This March on Boom Beach</title>
      <link>https://boombeach.inbox.supercell.com/#/en/news/1OI06LJ7kFUQpwa5Q5GaUH</link>
      <description>&lt;h1&gt;11 incredible years of Boom Beach&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;March is here, and it’s time to celebrate&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;with epic battles, powerful troop combinations, and exciting events! 
Get ready to dominate the battlefield with these upcoming events:

1 - 6: All Troop Mania – Unleash the full might of every troop with reduced training costs, allowing you to experiment with powerful army compositions!

3 - 16: Warships Season 72 – Set sail for a brand-new season of Warships, featuring fresh layouts, innovative strategies, and rewards!

3 - 9: Heavy Choppa – Bring in the aerial reinforcements with the Heavy Choppa, delivering nonstop firepower and frontline dominance!

7 - 9: Bombardier &amp;amp; Scorcher Mania – Pair the explosive long-range firepower of Bombardiers with the relentless charge of Scorchers for devastating battlefield control!

10 - 16: Rain Maker – Rain destruction on your enemies with these powerful long-range artillery units, outranging most defensive buildings!

10 - 16: Gunboat Ability Week – A special week featuring rotating Gunboat Abilities to enhance your attacks! Each day brings a new ability:

March 10: Speed Serum
March 11: Tiny Shock
March 12: Remote Hack
March 13: Remote Defibrillator
March 14: Cryo Bomb
March 15: Crystal Shield
March 16: Super Warrior

17 - 19: Cryoneer &amp;amp; Medic Mania – Keep your enemies frozen and your troops alive with this powerful support-based troop combination!

21 - 23: Anniversary Crab – Celebrate 11 years of Boom Beach with this special Mega Crab!

24 - 26: Heavy &amp;amp; Warrior Mania – Charge into battle with an unstoppable frontline force, combining the brute strength of Heavies with the fast-striking Warriors!

28 - 30: Joker Crab – A mysterious and unpredictable Mega Crab event with wild twists! Are you ready for the challenge?

31 - Apr 2: Deployable Turret – Take your offensive strategy to another level with Deployable Turrets!

31 - Apr 6: Critter Engineer – Bring the mechanical swarm to battle with the Critter Engineer, perfect for overwhelming enemy defenses!

31 - Apr 20: Warships Season 73 – A new Warships season sets sail with fresh challenges and strategic opportunities!

Get ready for an unforgettable anniversary month, Commanders! Strategize, battle, and claim your victories as we celebrate 11 years of Boom!

&lt;b&gt;Don&amp;#39;t forget to claim your diamonds daily!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1OI06LJ7kFUQpwa5Q5GaUH</guid>
      <category>Blog</category>
      <enclosure url="https://boombeach.inbox.supercell.com/cf7umh1jvp53/5YsWb0CDaWqkuqHxphbwpG/b82d4daa9951e933f6a39ae38c761a9b/BlogPost_Thumbnail__1_.png?w=900&amp;h=493&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill" length="0" type="image/png"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 13:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
