<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>boombeach-newsEntries-en</id>
  <title>Boombeach - News</title>
  <updated>2024-08-23T08:36:15.458127+00:00</updated>
  <link href="https://github.com/skrwo/supercell-inbox-rss/"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="1.0.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <subtitle>RSS wrapper of Boombeach inbox News</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>4gPvm1zq9tkN6LCZf48MB0</id>
    <title>June events</title>
    <updated>2024-06-11T09:52:50.106000+00:00</updated>
    <content>&lt;h1&gt;June events&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rocket Choppa: 3 - 9

Tank &amp;amp; Warrior Mania: 7 - 9
&#13;Explosive Drones: 10 - 12
&#13;Rifleman &amp;amp; Laser Ranger Mania: 14 - 16
&#13;Rain Maker: 17 - 23
&#13;Zooka Mania: 21 - 23
&#13;Remote Hack: 24 - 26
&#13;Life Leech Crab: 28 - 30&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://boombeach.inbox.supercell.com/#/en/news/4gPvm1zq9tkN6LCZf48MB0"/>
    <link href="https://boombeach.inbox.supercell.com/cf7umh1jvp53/2RdqgNwFKYc1TN9aipfcme/5f8a6c850dc7dd871173baf37aceb48f/BlogPost_Thumbnail.png?w=900&amp;h=493&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"/>
    <category term="Blog"/>
    <published>2024-05-31T23:00:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>64naIV3DLezw7ezu3QvGXi</id>
    <title>Summer Skies</title>
    <updated>2024-06-25T10:27:19.454000+00:00</updated>
    <content>&lt;h1&gt;Welcome to our Summer update: Summer Skies&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;UI fixes and improvements&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Increased vertical camera movement in player bases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixed not showing boost header in WS UI if the only active boost is GBE.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;When a resource base is captured from the player, the message no longer erroneously shows VP being lost, as resource bases no longer cause VP gain or loss.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixed CoE banners not showing on the map in certain cases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Landing Craft unit positioning has been tuned to prevent units falling overboard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixed Sculptor, Prototype Factory and daily chest rewards closing their respective parent windows. Now the parent windows should stay open (e.g. shop doesn&amp;#39;t close when claiming daily box).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Seasonal Campaign mission progress message position adjusted so that UI doesn&amp;#39;t get blocked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;When using custom skins for units, the correct icons are now used as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Warships leaderboard now shows player position for all players.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Bunker and Garrison&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bunker tutorial will no longer trigger in an enemy base in certain situations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shield Generator cables are no longer going into Bunkers during attacks if there are units in the Bunker.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Units are ejected from Bunkers if their team does not match the Bunker (this occurs when the Bunker is hacked).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Units from Bunkers no longer get resurrected by the attacker.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Garrison UI has a new icon for upkeep to differentiate it from gold costs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are several small tweaks to make the Garrison UI clearer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Garrison units are now automatically applied after the popup is closed. Previously changes were discarded on exiting unless specifically applied first.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Resource production logic was changed to fix issues with upkeep handling. Gold is no longer automatically collected when changing garrisoned units.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Other fixes &amp;amp; improvements&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Improved shooting positions for Gunboats. Boats with two turrets will now shoot from both of them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixed units getting stuck targeting hidden defenses (Hot Pot, Boom Surprise) if their range is higher than the turret.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed players to get an additional turret in Warships if they upgraded a node after a negative node caused their turret count to go to 0.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unit vs. unit retargeting logic was adjusted: Slow-firing units (e.g. Bombardiers) were sometimes skipping every other shot when other units (e.g. Critters) were between them and their target.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Players are now shown a warning message if leaving a TF would cause intel they have collected to be lost.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Earned VP is applied to the next VP chest if the current chest is full.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the Seasonal Campaign reward track the Buy Pass Point button is now situated under the free rewards. This was changed to clarify that the purchase does not award the actual rewards, only the points.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Having the Boom Pass reduces the cost of switching nodes in Warships. This affects both the cost and the cost cap.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Mystical Monument Leaderboard&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;A leaderboard has been added to the Mystical Monument&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Only players active in the last two weeks are visible on the leaderboard&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ties are resolved by whichever player got to the level first
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Path of Glory&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Path of Glory is an informational feature that indicates at which stage of a player’s journey various features are unlocked. It lists buildings, troops and game features.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Path of Glory is accessed from the Building Suggestor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;
Invasion logic changes&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The logic for determining when an invasion on the Archipelago Map occurs has been adjusted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Blackguard (PvE) and mercenary (PvP) invasions are now on separate timers and are no longer random.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;These timers are visible in the Radar info screen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The tooltips for these timers will give additional information.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The timing for when an invasion occurs has changed:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Instead of a potential invasion, there will be an invasion at the time displayed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The base time for the invasions increases based on player level. This indicates the shortest time the timers can have.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Base time is capped at 2 hours at level 60.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Timer duration depends on the amount of discovered and liberated islands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is a minimum number of islands that need to be liberated for the timer to start.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;This number depends on the total number of islands discovered.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;These numbers are separate for Blackguard and mercenary invasions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The more islands beyond the required amount of islands are liberated, the shorter the time to the next invasion. If all islands are liberated, the timer uses the base time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The timer is recalculated when liberated or total island count changes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The timers still have the current 14 hour inactivity cutoff. If the player has not logged in for 14 hours, the timers pause. The timers resume when the player again logs in.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://boombeach.inbox.supercell.com/#/en/news/64naIV3DLezw7ezu3QvGXi"/>
    <link href="https://boombeach.inbox.supercell.com/cf7umh1jvp53/2ALDbweNM640LW8xNcug9l/09632f0b0ba164312868d5e7a7e94a5c/BlogPost_Thumbnail.png?w=900&amp;h=493&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"/>
    <category term="Blog"/>
    <published>2024-06-24T23:00:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>4L1rMvONilFGdK1kSV3kPj</id>
    <title>Summer Skies - hotfix</title>
    <updated>2024-06-28T21:32:29.664000+00:00</updated>
    <content>&lt;h1&gt;Hotfix list and Matchmaking changes&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hello, Commander!
On June 28th, we released fixes for the following issues:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Troops retargeting while following a flare has been fixed;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wrong text in Path of Glory Hammerman Strikes Back card has been changed;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Critter GBA again spawns the correct amount of critters;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;If a player does not have a country code, they will not appear in Monument leaderboard; this will only happen to really old players and they can contact support to add country code to their account;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;New matchmaking has been fixed;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Win with Unique Troops mission has been fixed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;
New matchmaking system:
&lt;/b&gt;
Matchmaking is now based on player level, adjusted by VP.

In the basic case, the player is matched against a same level opponent. There can be a difference of a few levels in either direction.

If a player not at max level starts pulling ahead in VP, the game tries to offer harder opponents. The player&amp;#39;s VP is divided by ten and compared to their level. The higher number is then used for matchmaking. For example, if a player at level 40 has 600 VP, they will be matched as if they were at level 60.

At max level and high VP, there is a further check that prevents high-VP players from getting matches with much lower VP (several hundred points) players. This is to preserve competition at high VP. Preference is still given for opponents with equal VP, this check is meant to catch any odd situations.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://boombeach.inbox.supercell.com/#/en/news/4L1rMvONilFGdK1kSV3kPj"/>
    <link href="https://boombeach.inbox.supercell.com/cf7umh1jvp53/6UzadJJlwkPiWpIFgAzTB4/59662aef7b1633b7b71d9f42c7cc2e7d/BlogPost_Thumbnail.png?w=900&amp;h=493&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"/>
    <category term="Blog"/>
    <published>2024-06-27T23:00:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>1Ib7KpTvfFXCIuH4fdlg77</id>
    <title>July Events</title>
    <updated>2024-08-06T09:46:30.918000+00:00</updated>
    <content>&lt;h1&gt;July Events&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Warships Season 63: 1 - 28&#13;
Heavy Choppa: 1 - 7&#13;
TankMech Mania: 5 - 7&#13;
Deployable Turret: 8 - 10&#13;
BombarCryo: 12 - 14&#13;
Melon Bombardier: 15 - 21&#13;
LaserMedic: 19 - 21&#13;
Crystal Critters: 22 - 24&#13;
Grenadier Mania: 26 - 28&#13;
Tiny Shock: 29 - 31&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://boombeach.inbox.supercell.com/#/en/news/1Ib7KpTvfFXCIuH4fdlg77"/>
    <link href="https://boombeach.inbox.supercell.com/cf7umh1jvp53/19ShNa9jgJacJZjJUVI2uN/7a2706d36cd1df3f2238a4ddf3f0c10e/BlogPost_Thumbnail.jpg?w=900&amp;h=493&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"/>
    <category term="Blog"/>
    <published>2024-06-30T23:00:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>4y8A9gq6Wk4KOPfwrqFJmx</id>
    <title>August Events</title>
    <updated>2024-08-06T10:03:17.249000+00:00</updated>
    <content>&lt;h1&gt;August events&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Scorched Crab: 2 - 4&#13;
MegaScorcher: 5 - 11&#13;
Warships Season 64: 5 - 25&#13;
RifleScorcher Mania: 9 - 11&#13;
Heavy Mania: 16 - 18&#13;
Super Warrior: 19 - 21&#13;
Rain Maker: 19 - 25&#13;
Gunboat Crab: 30 - 1 Sep&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://boombeach.inbox.supercell.com/#/en/news/4y8A9gq6Wk4KOPfwrqFJmx"/>
    <link href="https://boombeach.inbox.supercell.com/cf7umh1jvp53/7DoF6h4y0QvN7UCsiWVDui/3b341facad4adba3e67fd0e62a66af5b/BlogPost_Thumbnail.jpg?w=900&amp;h=493&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"/>
    <category term="Blog"/>
    <published>2024-07-31T23:00:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
