<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>boombeach-newsEntries-en</id>
  <title>Boombeach - News</title>
  <updated>2024-07-18T20:30:21.223260+00:00</updated>
  <link href="https://github.com/skrwo/supercell-inbox-rss/"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="1.0.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <subtitle>RSS wrapper of Boombeach inbox News</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>6gFWymbUMWlfTjhx8GWHWT</id>
    <title>New Supercell game</title>
    <updated>2024-05-15T11:50:01.797000+00:00</updated>
    <content>&lt;h1&gt;New milestone unlocked! &lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In order to THANK YOU all for supporting the Squad Busters launch, we&amp;#39;ve added a new milestone to the pre-registration reward track!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If we reach 40M pre-registrations before May 29, this beautiful Deco will be available at launch, and claimable for only a month!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://boombeach.inbox.supercell.com/cf7umh1jvp53/3Xz7bcdi0xyNgPYAPJQvqH/967106dbd78dd6e4d53998604389ed22/deco-900.png?w=900&amp;h=900&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To celebrate the global release of &lt;b&gt;Squad Busters&lt;/b&gt;, all Supercell games are giving away &lt;b&gt;free and exclusive rewards&lt;/b&gt; for the community to achieve.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;How it works&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pre-Register for Squad Busters on the App Store or Google Play before the global release on the &lt;b&gt;29th of May&lt;/b&gt;. By pre-registering you will get the game right away when it becomes globally available on the App Store or Google Play.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Follow the progress of the community effort on the reward tracker and don&amp;#39;t forget to claim the rewards as they unlock.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Progress updated daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Squad up and make sure to tell your friends!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;a href="htps://apple.com"&gt;👉App store link👈&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;What is Squad Busters?&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Squad Busters is a game where you can play with your favorite Supercell characters in fun and action-packed matches. Travel through different worlds, collect new characters, and evolve them to take down massive monsters as you continually build your ultimate squad. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;a href="https://youtu.be/cDCCpWJRWak"&gt;📺 [EMBEDDED VIDEO]&lt;/a&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://boombeach.inbox.supercell.com/#/en/news/6gFWymbUMWlfTjhx8GWHWT"/>
    <link href="https://boombeach.inbox.supercell.com/cf7umh1jvp53/17r3C14FGN1u9b96kdXQTx/e0fbec2e4aed7dfe9cfa135de02890c9/Boom_Beach-thumbnail.png?w=900&amp;h=493&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"/>
    <category term="News"/>
    <published>2024-04-26T09:03:18+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>2bvnrvCc19PAdLbfNrvPeT</id>
    <title>HQ 26</title>
    <updated>2024-04-30T09:37:30.311000+00:00</updated>
    <content>&lt;h1&gt;Welcome to the April update "Take Cover"&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;HQ 26 &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;HQ can now be upgraded to level 26. After the upgrade, the following will become available: 

● An additional Wood Storage can be built.
● Three mines and one shock mine can be added.
● The following buildings can be upgraded: Sawmill, Vault, Weapon Lab, Gunboat, Landing Craft, and Armory.
● The following defenses can be upgraded: Sniper Tower, Machine Gun, Mortar, Cannon, Flamethrower, Boom Cannon, Rocket Launcher, Critter Launcher.
● Once the armory has been upgraded, the following units and abilities can be upgraded: Rifleman, Heavy, Zooka, Warrior, Tank, Medic, Grenadier, Scorcher, Laser Ranger, Cryoneer, Bombardier, Mech, Artillery, Medkit, Barrage, Critters, Mines, Boom Mines.
● All heroes can be upgraded one level.
● After the upgrade, Kavan’s Crystal Critters and Bullit’s Taunt can be upgraded to level 7.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;New feature: Proto Module Conversion&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt; After upgrading the Weapon Lab, players can convert proto modules for a small sum in gems. The building UI has a new tab for this conversion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;New feature: Garrisons&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;● The Bunker is a new defensive building.
● Players can build two bunkers at HQ 26.
● At HQ 26, the bunkers can be upgraded to level 8.
● The bunker has a feature called &amp;quot;Air Defense&amp;quot;, which reduces the damage the bunker takes from Artillery and Barrage abilities from the gunboat. &lt;i&gt;Damage from troops is unaffected&lt;/i&gt;. 
● The bunker has no offensive capabilities on its own. The player must garrison troops in the bunker.
● The bunker has a housing limit, which determines how many troops it can hold. The bunker can not hold large troops like Tanks, Mechs, or Scorchers. The bunker will also not hold prototroops.
● The bunker can hold four different types of troops at the same time. Units can be freely mixed within the housing limit.
● Units inside the bunker fire at attacking enemies with their current stats. Units are affected by defender’s boosts from offensive statues or tribes.
 ● Some troops have an improved range while garrisoned inside the bunker. Riflemen, Heavies: +50%. Zookas, Cryoneers, Laser Rangers: +20%. For Cryoneers and Laser Rangers, this extends the distance at which the laser is fired, not the length of the laser.
● When the bunker is destroyed, the garrison exits and continues to fight the attackers.
● The garrison is restored after each battle. Even if a base is raided multiple times, the garrison will always defend the base.


Garrison upkeep:

● Garrisoning troops does not cost resources. Instead, the troops require a constant upkeep in gold. This cost per hour is indicated in the UI.
● This upkeep is automatically deducted from the gold produced by the Residences. Island gold production and existing gold reserves do not affect upkeep.
● Troops can not be placed in bunkers if their upkeep would exceed base gold production. Base gold production is affected by green statues and other bonuses. This allows the player to put costlier troops in the garrison. If base gold production drops below current upkeep, troops are removed from the garrison.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Warships&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;● Added icons to the various choice nodes when inactive.
● Negative nodes now check that the player has unlocked enough defenses before allowing a reduction in those defenses.
● Choice nodes now allow selecting defenses even if a negative node choice has caused their available count to be 0. Previously, the choice nodes would have treated such defenses as locked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;b&gt;Fixes &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;● Fixed icon and text overlapping in info/speed up popup.
● Fixed door animation for Fortified Residence skin.
● Fixed rank up screen info button not opening rank popup.
● Fixed wrong rank shown in daily reward ad popup.
● Fixed erroneously showing player resources when visiting other player’s islands from warships.
● Fixed a crash if player receives ER state updates from previous WS battle while in island battle.
● Fixed an error that caused submarine rewards always to be shards. Now, shallower dives give fragments, while deeper dives give crystals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Seasonal Campaign &amp;amp; Boom Pass&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;● Sounds have been added to the Seasonal Campaign UI.
● Challenge missions now have a different icon background color.
● All missions now have a progress bar.
● Added functionality that prevents buying the Boom Pass if too little time remains in the Season.
● There are now indicators for mission progress in the home base and on the archipelago map.
● Missions can now be pinned to appear first on the list.
● All players can now purchase season points with gems to progress the reward track. Previously, only Boom Pass holders had this option.
● Missions can now be rerolled with gems. The cost increases after each reroll. The button is in the information popup.
● Campaign Missions will now award intel at a rate of one per 50 points. This intel reward is doubled for Boom Pass holders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Improvements&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;● Hero ability upgrades can now be finished with Attack Plan.
● To fix the various player XP errors over the years, a function that recalculates player XP and player level was added. This will be run for every player the first time the game is opened after the update. There will be a popup showing the change if your XP was adjusted.
● Supply chests (“VP chests”) now stack up to 8, with a new one added every 6 hours.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Balancing&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;● Player level requirements for HQ levels 4-7 were reduced to make the early game faster. 
● Rifleman build time is reduced to 10 seconds to reduce early game wait times.
● Attacking troops will prioritize engaging defending troops, including critters, that come in range, even if the attackers are firing at buildings at the time. Units will not retarget if the defending unit is already targeted by two or more attacking units.
● Removed VP gains and losses from resource base battles.
● Task Force intel cap has been increased by 50%.
● Classified items cap has been increased to 5.
● At HQ 25, Brick’s Iron Will and Everspark’s Critter Swarm can be upgraded to level 7.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://boombeach.inbox.supercell.com/#/en/news/2bvnrvCc19PAdLbfNrvPeT"/>
    <link href="https://boombeach.inbox.supercell.com/cf7umh1jvp53/6LaoJqlzg7aA3NJl42gVtP/b28e02384b09389838f1de16d7d025af/BlogPost_Thumbnail.png?w=900&amp;h=493&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"/>
    <category term="Updates"/>
    <published>2024-04-29T23:00:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>1ngy1Ey1Rr3NE7ZKXA0RGm</id>
    <title>May events</title>
    <updated>2024-05-02T14:31:41.799000+00:00</updated>
    <content>&lt;h1&gt;May events:&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hasty Crab: 3 - 5&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Melon Bombardier: 6 - 12&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Warships Season 61: 6 - 26&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;ZookaGren Mania: 10 - 12&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Speed Serum: 13 - 15&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;CryoLaR Mania: 17 - 19&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lazortron: 20 - 26&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;RifleMech Mania: 24 - 26&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Super Warrior: 27 - 29&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tribal Crab: 31 - Jun 2&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://boombeach.inbox.supercell.com/#/en/news/1ngy1Ey1Rr3NE7ZKXA0RGm"/>
    <link href="https://boombeach.inbox.supercell.com/cf7umh1jvp53/4ySdstnZiNWQdTPFxuqGAx/3e13849417f6dbbef437fe12284014d5/BlogPost_Thumbnail.png?w=900&amp;h=493&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"/>
    <category term="Blog"/>
    <published>2024-04-30T23:00:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>4gPvm1zq9tkN6LCZf48MB0</id>
    <title>June events</title>
    <updated>2024-06-11T09:52:50.106000+00:00</updated>
    <content>&lt;h1&gt;June events&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rocket Choppa: 3 - 9

Tank &amp;amp; Warrior Mania: 7 - 9
&#13;Explosive Drones: 10 - 12
&#13;Rifleman &amp;amp; Laser Ranger Mania: 14 - 16
&#13;Rain Maker: 17 - 23
&#13;Zooka Mania: 21 - 23
&#13;Remote Hack: 24 - 26
&#13;Life Leech Crab: 28 - 30&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://boombeach.inbox.supercell.com/#/en/news/4gPvm1zq9tkN6LCZf48MB0"/>
    <link href="https://boombeach.inbox.supercell.com/cf7umh1jvp53/2RdqgNwFKYc1TN9aipfcme/5f8a6c850dc7dd871173baf37aceb48f/BlogPost_Thumbnail.png?w=900&amp;h=493&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"/>
    <category term="Blog"/>
    <published>2024-05-31T23:00:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>64naIV3DLezw7ezu3QvGXi</id>
    <title>Summer Skies</title>
    <updated>2024-06-25T10:27:19.454000+00:00</updated>
    <content>&lt;h1&gt;Welcome to our Summer update: Summer Skies&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;UI fixes and improvements&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Increased vertical camera movement in player bases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixed not showing boost header in WS UI if the only active boost is GBE.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;When a resource base is captured from the player, the message no longer erroneously shows VP being lost, as resource bases no longer cause VP gain or loss.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixed CoE banners not showing on the map in certain cases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Landing Craft unit positioning has been tuned to prevent units falling overboard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixed Sculptor, Prototype Factory and daily chest rewards closing their respective parent windows. Now the parent windows should stay open (e.g. shop doesn&amp;#39;t close when claiming daily box).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Seasonal Campaign mission progress message position adjusted so that UI doesn&amp;#39;t get blocked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;When using custom skins for units, the correct icons are now used as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Warships leaderboard now shows player position for all players.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Bunker and Garrison&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bunker tutorial will no longer trigger in an enemy base in certain situations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shield Generator cables are no longer going into Bunkers during attacks if there are units in the Bunker.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Units are ejected from Bunkers if their team does not match the Bunker (this occurs when the Bunker is hacked).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Units from Bunkers no longer get resurrected by the attacker.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Garrison UI has a new icon for upkeep to differentiate it from gold costs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are several small tweaks to make the Garrison UI clearer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Garrison units are now automatically applied after the popup is closed. Previously changes were discarded on exiting unless specifically applied first.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Resource production logic was changed to fix issues with upkeep handling. Gold is no longer automatically collected when changing garrisoned units.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Other fixes &amp;amp; improvements&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Improved shooting positions for Gunboats. Boats with two turrets will now shoot from both of them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixed units getting stuck targeting hidden defenses (Hot Pot, Boom Surprise) if their range is higher than the turret.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed players to get an additional turret in Warships if they upgraded a node after a negative node caused their turret count to go to 0.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unit vs. unit retargeting logic was adjusted: Slow-firing units (e.g. Bombardiers) were sometimes skipping every other shot when other units (e.g. Critters) were between them and their target.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Players are now shown a warning message if leaving a TF would cause intel they have collected to be lost.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Earned VP is applied to the next VP chest if the current chest is full.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the Seasonal Campaign reward track the Buy Pass Point button is now situated under the free rewards. This was changed to clarify that the purchase does not award the actual rewards, only the points.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Having the Boom Pass reduces the cost of switching nodes in Warships. This affects both the cost and the cost cap.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Mystical Monument Leaderboard&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;A leaderboard has been added to the Mystical Monument&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Only players active in the last two weeks are visible on the leaderboard&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ties are resolved by whichever player got to the level first
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Path of Glory&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Path of Glory is an informational feature that indicates at which stage of a player’s journey various features are unlocked. It lists buildings, troops and game features.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Path of Glory is accessed from the Building Suggestor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;
Invasion logic changes&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The logic for determining when an invasion on the Archipelago Map occurs has been adjusted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Blackguard (PvE) and mercenary (PvP) invasions are now on separate timers and are no longer random.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;These timers are visible in the Radar info screen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The tooltips for these timers will give additional information.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The timing for when an invasion occurs has changed:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Instead of a potential invasion, there will be an invasion at the time displayed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The base time for the invasions increases based on player level. This indicates the shortest time the timers can have.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Base time is capped at 2 hours at level 60.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Timer duration depends on the amount of discovered and liberated islands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is a minimum number of islands that need to be liberated for the timer to start.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;This number depends on the total number of islands discovered.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;These numbers are separate for Blackguard and mercenary invasions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The more islands beyond the required amount of islands are liberated, the shorter the time to the next invasion. If all islands are liberated, the timer uses the base time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The timer is recalculated when liberated or total island count changes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The timers still have the current 14 hour inactivity cutoff. If the player has not logged in for 14 hours, the timers pause. The timers resume when the player again logs in.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://boombeach.inbox.supercell.com/#/en/news/64naIV3DLezw7ezu3QvGXi"/>
    <link href="https://boombeach.inbox.supercell.com/cf7umh1jvp53/2ALDbweNM640LW8xNcug9l/09632f0b0ba164312868d5e7a7e94a5c/BlogPost_Thumbnail.png?w=900&amp;h=493&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"/>
    <category term="Blog"/>
    <published>2024-06-24T23:00:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>4L1rMvONilFGdK1kSV3kPj</id>
    <title>Summer Skies - hotfix</title>
    <updated>2024-06-28T21:32:29.664000+00:00</updated>
    <content>&lt;h1&gt;Hotfix list and Matchmaking changes&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hello, Commander!
On June 28th, we released fixes for the following issues:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Troops retargeting while following a flare has been fixed;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wrong text in Path of Glory Hammerman Strikes Back card has been changed;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Critter GBA again spawns the correct amount of critters;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;If a player does not have a country code, they will not appear in Monument leaderboard; this will only happen to really old players and they can contact support to add country code to their account;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;New matchmaking has been fixed;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Win with Unique Troops mission has been fixed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;
New matchmaking system:
&lt;/b&gt;
Matchmaking is now based on player level, adjusted by VP.

In the basic case, the player is matched against a same level opponent. There can be a difference of a few levels in either direction.

If a player not at max level starts pulling ahead in VP, the game tries to offer harder opponents. The player&amp;#39;s VP is divided by ten and compared to their level. The higher number is then used for matchmaking. For example, if a player at level 40 has 600 VP, they will be matched as if they were at level 60.

At max level and high VP, there is a further check that prevents high-VP players from getting matches with much lower VP (several hundred points) players. This is to preserve competition at high VP. Preference is still given for opponents with equal VP, this check is meant to catch any odd situations.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://boombeach.inbox.supercell.com/#/en/news/4L1rMvONilFGdK1kSV3kPj"/>
    <link href="https://boombeach.inbox.supercell.com/cf7umh1jvp53/6UzadJJlwkPiWpIFgAzTB4/59662aef7b1633b7b71d9f42c7cc2e7d/BlogPost_Thumbnail.png?w=900&amp;h=493&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"/>
    <category term="Blog"/>
    <published>2024-06-27T23:00:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
