<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Boombeach - News</title>
    <link>https://github.com/skrwo/supercell-inbox-rss/</link>
    <description>RSS wrapper of Boombeach inbox News</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 23:30:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>September events</title>
      <link>https://boombeach.inbox.supercell.com/#/en/news/3QeMDPZIaclJf6dxI0eNdb</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Season 65: 2 - 22
All Troop Mania: 2 - 8
Melon Bombardier: 2 - 8
Rifleman Mania: 13 - 15
Remote Defib: 16 - 18
Mega Scorcher: 16 - 22
LaserZooka Mania: 20 - 22
Cryo Bomb: 23 - 25
Beastly Crab: 27 - 29
Heavy Choppa: 30 - Oct 6
Season 66: 30 - Oct 20 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3QeMDPZIaclJf6dxI0eNdb</guid>
      <category>Blog</category>
      <enclosure url="https://boombeach.inbox.supercell.com/cf7umh1jvp53/37R4XgeZRQMzNyw5l0uMNI/027af096ebb389eafcb1e4f16cf4f430/BlogPost_Thumbnail.png?w=900&amp;h=493&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill" length="0" type="image/png"/>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Calm Before the Storm</title>
      <link>https://boombeach.inbox.supercell.com/#/en/news/38nrtXrEs0uUjgEuzQ8wAf</link>
      <description>&lt;h1&gt;The Calm Before the Storm&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This time we focus on fixes and QoL additions, as we gear up for bigger things towards the end of the year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Balance changes&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Prototroop upgrade costs are now capped at 1500;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ruddero’s Wingmen now cost 3+3 GBE. Seeker shot costs 7+7 GBE and deploys 4 seekers;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Seeker Shot’s seeker count is now properly shown in the info screen;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Life Leech is now calculated using a percentage of the damage done instead of constant value per hit. Area attacks can now also trigger life leech. Mitigating damage with shields or abilities reduces the amount of life gained;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gunboat Energy now supports partial energy gain. For example, if a sector boost increases GBE gains from destruction by 10%, previously these energy gains would have been rounded down and the boost would have had no effect. Now no rounding will be done. For example: 
If we destroy 4 buildings with 10% boost players will get the following energy for each building;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;OLD: 3 - 3 - 3 - 3 ( 3.3 rounded down to 3, total is 12);&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;NEW 3 - 3 - 3 - 4 ( 3.3+3.3+3.3+3.3, total 13.2, at the fourth building the decimals added up to a full energy point).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bugfixes&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;b&gt;UI and base&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixed centering issue with some icons (mainly proto defence icons);&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixed an UI issue with Kavan&amp;#39;s Galvanizing Presence perk that showed it affected by troop boosts;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixed a bug where landing crafts could go out of position if the player swapped their position while constructing them;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixed Combat HUD showing gunboat ability being available too early and displaying &amp;quot;Not enough energy&amp;quot; if player immediately pressed it;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixed queued statues sometimes handling sculptor optimizer incorrectly and starting with full sculpt time instead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Battle&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Spawned units from destroyed choppers now move to active flare;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bunker&amp;#39;s damage reduction no longer affects the neighbouring buildings if they both are hit with the same projectile;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixed various situations where units might ignore flares;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bullit&amp;#39;s Shock Knuckles will no longer quickly move him over long distances;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixed Ruddero&amp;#39;s Bombing Run freeze caused by hidden proto defenses;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Prevent Ruddero&amp;#39;s Bombing Run from extending beyond the gameplay area borders;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixed Shock Knuckles not destroying mines;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixed unit vs. unit retargeting causing issues in situations where the unit causing retargeting does not get selected as the new target. For example, Seekers are unable to target anything but the Engine Room and would stutter due to Critters causing retargeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Improvements&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Numerous UI fixes, mostly text/placement issues and adding darkening to backgrounds (warship, shop, creator support popup...);&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Improved performance when applying certain status effects (such as Speed Serum) to large amounts of troops;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Removed friends tab from MM leaderboards;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Button for MM leaderboard is shown when visiting other players through MM leaderboard;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;If resources in the inventory are at or over the cap, these resources are shown with orange text;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;New Landing Craft troop UI. In addition to showing when all troops are ready, shows when the next troop is ready;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Submarine dives can now be sped up with diamonds or time savers by tapping the buoy on the Archipelago map.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;New features&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mystical Monument can now be built to level 500. Two new visual upgrades have been added;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Event Sidebar: A new UI element has been added that shows all currently active events and how to unlock them;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;This sidebar is accessed from the calendar button at the right side of the screen in the home base;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;If there is an arrow icon next to the event, tapping it takes the player to the event;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Added an extra troop loadout slot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Helper&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The building suggestor has been replaced with a helper icon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;If there are outstanding tasks, the helper will remind the player of this.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tapping the icon takes the player to the Standing Orders list.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tapping the go button will take the player to that task.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The building suggestor and Path of Glory can be accessed via this screen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The task suggestion text can be toggled on or off in the Gameplay Options menu.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">38nrtXrEs0uUjgEuzQ8wAf</guid>
      <category>Updates</category>
      <enclosure url="https://boombeach.inbox.supercell.com/cf7umh1jvp53/K2a9WEG1QJQQDwiOLSEy3/659784917d786ab1e43162a24966e56e/BlogPost_Thumbnail.png?w=900&amp;h=493&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill" length="0" type="image/png"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>October Events</title>
      <link>https://boombeach.inbox.supercell.com/#/en/news/6RtP3WFYbl5sUeFNTpzIur</link>
      <description>&lt;h1&gt;This October in Boom Beach&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Welcome, Commanders, to an eerie month in Boom Beach! As the leaves change color and the air grows crisp, our tropical paradise is heating up with spine-tingling surprises. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;#39;s what you can expect:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;4 - 6: Mech &amp;amp; Warrior Mania: &lt;i&gt;Unleash your mechanized troops and warriors for a fierce showdown.&lt;/i&gt;

7 - 9: Deployable Turret:&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Deploy them strategically on the battlefield. &lt;/i&gt;

11 - 13: Rifle &amp;amp; Tank Mania: &lt;i&gt;Combine firepower and mobility for an unstoppable force.&lt;/i&gt;

14 - 20: Rain Maker:&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Make it rain with the Rain Maker.&lt;/i&gt;

18 - 20: Laser Ranger Mania: &lt;i&gt;Engage in high-tech battles with the Laser Ranger.&lt;/i&gt;

21 - 23: Remote Hack: &lt;i&gt;A hack at the right moment can decide the course of the battle.&lt;/i&gt;

25 - 27: Halloween Crab: &lt;i&gt;Prepare for a special edition of Mega Crab with special defenses.&lt;/i&gt;

28 - Nov 3: Vampire Zooka: &lt;i&gt;Embrace the Halloween spirit with Vampire Zooka.&lt;/i&gt;

28 - Nov 17: Season 67: &lt;i&gt;Dive into the new season filled with fresh challenges.&lt;/i&gt;

As we gear up for these exciting events, don’t forget to strategize and prepare your troops. October in Boom Beach is set to be an unforgettable experience filled with battles, rewards, and a touch of Halloween magic! &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Are you ready to take command? &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6RtP3WFYbl5sUeFNTpzIur</guid>
      <category>Blog</category>
      <enclosure url="https://boombeach.inbox.supercell.com/cf7umh1jvp53/5bxN6RzF9Qjg07gfjA49lP/b7ea20bf883c27064e8937a3e3f9b5ba/BlogPost_Thumbnail.png?w=900&amp;h=493&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill" length="0" type="image/png"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This November on Boom Beach</title>
      <link>https://boombeach.inbox.supercell.com/#/en/news/1Z8znZwM4I4dcGDtYTXJDw</link>
      <description>&lt;h1&gt;This November on Boom Beach&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Welcome, Commanders, to an action-packed month in Boom Beach! As we embrace the changing tides of November, our tropical battleground is set to explode with thrilling events!.

Here’s what you can expect:

1 - 3: Heavy &amp;amp; Bombardier Mania: Unleash the power of Heavy and Bombardier troops for a fierce showdown!

4 - 6: Crystal Shield: Protect your troops with Crystal Shield.

8 - 10: Tank Mania: Combine firepower and resilience for an unstoppable armored force.

15 - 17: Laser Ranger &amp;amp; Heavy Mania: Engage in high-tech battles with the Laser Ranger alongside your Heavies.

18 - 20: Speed Serum: Boost your troops’ speed and unleash chaos on the battlefield!

18 - 24: Rainmaker: Experience the power of the Rainmaker, a unique mix of Tank and Mortar with enhanced range!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;22 - 24 Proto Crab: Prepare for a special edition of Mega Crab featuring the Rain Maker as an optional Troop!

25 - 27: Explosive Drones: Deploy Explosive Drones for devastating attacks on enemy defenses. 

25 - Dec 22: Warships Season 68:  Set sail into a new season filled with fresh challenges and rewards!

28 - 30: Rifleman &amp;amp; Grenadier Mania:  Bring the heat with a powerful combination of Riflemen and Grenadiers!

As we gear up for these exciting events, don’t forget to strategize and prepare your troops. November in Boom Beach is an unforgettable experience filled with battles, rewards, and plenty of action! &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1Z8znZwM4I4dcGDtYTXJDw</guid>
      <category>Blog</category>
      <enclosure url="https://boombeach.inbox.supercell.com/cf7umh1jvp53/5LLTj9iE4rxN6U3KrhA22D/c1310cdc6ae0a487e68ae6b1b60ce7bc/BlogPost_Thumbnail.png?w=900&amp;h=493&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill" length="0" type="image/png"/>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
