<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>clashofclans-newsEntries-en</id>
  <title>Clashofclans - News</title>
  <updated>2024-11-06T04:37:41.977722+00:00</updated>
  <link href="https://github.com/skrwo/supercell-inbox-rss/"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="1.0.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <subtitle>RSS wrapper of Clashofclans inbox News</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>6X40Xvo0Vz6voo6gG7kCvh</id>
    <title>Anime Medal Event &amp; New Hero Equipment!</title>
    <updated>2024-08-09T07:58:49.165000+00:00</updated>
    <content>&lt;p&gt;Available for players in Town Hall 6 and up, you will collect &lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Magical Crystals&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt; by doing in-game activities and progressing through the Event track. These &lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Magical Crystals&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt; can be converted into &lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Magic Medals&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt; and unlock special rewards, such as the new &lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Archer Queen Equipment: Magic Mirror&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;b&gt;When?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Event Starts:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;August 9, 8 AM UTC&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Event Ends:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;August 30, 8 AM UTC&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;After the event ends on &lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;August 30&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;, you can still access the Trader’s Event tab and the Medal Event Building for two more days, until September 1st, 8 AM UTC.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;New Temporary Troops: M.E.C.H.A and Broom Witch!&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;img src="https://clashofclans.inbox.supercell.com/lqe2co20rkhw/TggQNyj02GzKqXNizU5Cm/c77215090f0919f655af9804a0fac227/MECHA1.png?w=700&amp;h=700&amp;f=center"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;M.E.C.H.A:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Available for players in Town Hall 6 and above.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ground troop, defense targeting, damage multiplier against walls!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://clashofclans.inbox.supercell.com/lqe2co20rkhw/2XnUdIraESTbEcuZHfHJZ7/8f044ae96db15e8df14cc5be79a9e558/Broom_Witch1.png?w=700&amp;h=700&amp;f=center"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Broom Witch:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Available for players in Town Hall 6 and above.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Air unit, the favorite target is Wizard Tower, flies fast and spawns something when taking damage! Take a look! They are ground units and target defenses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Event Resources!&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;img src="https://clashofclans.inbox.supercell.com/lqe2co20rkhw/30qtGUlZehMvOhGcEf3EV5/a06f8133aa90e16a11d52af55d6f2784/crystal_token.png?w=700&amp;h=700&amp;f=center"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Medal Event Resource: Magical Crystals&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Magical Crystals are obtained by attacking and destroying your opponents&amp;#39; Wizard Towers in the Multiplayer attacks! Gather Crystals to get yourself Ores, Decorations, and more!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://clashofclans.inbox.supercell.com/lqe2co20rkhw/1xl7GMe8AzYMM584ysSAJt/54369ba040a2b4dcd2c83733720d4a42/magic_medal_multiple.png?w=700&amp;h=700&amp;f=center"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Magic Medals&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This event’s currency that you can spend at the Trader’s Shop. Use your Medals to purchase a unique seasonal Decoration, resources such as Ores for your Hero Equipment, Magic Items and more. The top-tier item is Magic Mirror, the new Epic Hero Equipment!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;New Hero Equipment &amp; Other Rewards!&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;img src="https://clashofclans.inbox.supercell.com/lqe2co20rkhw/62EMdWCxbzvuXOyBecLW07/c76edaf9acc651475ee7c5b839971d81/HeroGear_AQ_Clone0000.png?w=700&amp;h=700&amp;f=center"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;New Archer Queen Epic Hero Equipment: Magic Mirror:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This equipment summons a clone of the Archer Queen with a certain percentage of her hp and dmg and lasts for a few seconds. In addition, Archer Queen is initially invisible for 1 second after using the Mirror.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And, of course, there will be fun decorations available for you to obtain during the event!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://clashofclans.inbox.supercell.com/lqe2co20rkhw/3wpXzhVLmcdqbzosVhR2tH/141c8a0b033376ad0c147b15868d2cff/Untitled-1.png?w=1000&amp;h=652&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is time to suit up and take it to the skies! The Medal Event awaits!&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://clashofclans.inbox.supercell.com/#/en/news/6X40Xvo0Vz6voo6gG7kCvh"/>
    <link href="https://clashofclans.inbox.supercell.com/lqe2co20rkhw/7klptLdOhebuOvv84pDwxV/9302c4c524c4502d01e73cf197f8a4c4/anime_medal_thumbnail.jpg?w=900&amp;h=506&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"/>
    <category term="News"/>
    <published>2024-08-09T07:58:49+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>AzAw1Bvpuzbr4Hn4anS68</id>
    <title>The Battle for Magical Crystals! </title>
    <updated>2024-08-09T08:01:02.520000+00:00</updated>
    <link href="https://clashofclans.inbox.supercell.com/#/en/news/AzAw1Bvpuzbr4Hn4anS68"/>
    <link href="https://clashofclans.inbox.supercell.com/lqe2co20rkhw/6RilQjlMCJRRaPEK0LswOe/04b7508a361d7c69d56d58ee7e8a400a/SUP3913_Anime_Clash_Thumbnail_Witch_1080x1920.jpg?w=900&amp;h=506&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"/>
    <link href="https://youtu.be/jti-IFsPKEc"/>
    <category term="News"/>
    <published>2024-08-09T08:01:02+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>5UdEn5EMcqr17xPEEK4d3m</id>
    <title>Spesial ultah ke-12 Clash of Clans🎉 Klaim Voucher Diskon 16% &amp; top up Clash of Clans pakai DANA di Google Play!</title>
    <updated>2024-08-22T08:00:14.338000+00:00</updated>
    <link href="https://clashofclans.inbox.supercell.com/#/en/news/5UdEn5EMcqr17xPEEK4d3m"/>
    <link href="https://clashofclans.inbox.supercell.com/lqe2co20rkhw/qMIWIlOajdhWafM1Zg4XK/f029a34f9151560858bf03f475dc804e/image0__7_.jpeg?w=900&amp;h=506&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"/>
    <link href="https://u.alipay.cn/_6hmpPQZOwRDFyGqKh2EHgW"/>
    <category term="News"/>
    <published>2024-08-22T08:00:05+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>1dTCTk4XyUjDjJQ5wETequ</id>
    <title>Notice Regarding Upcoming September Balance Changes!</title>
    <updated>2024-08-30T07:22:51.305000+00:00</updated>
    <content>&lt;p&gt;As we are approaching another major update in early September, we would like to give you an early heads-up on the upcoming balance changes affecting a wide range of Town Hall levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please find this in-depth post &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%253A%252F%252Fwww.reddit.com%252Fr%252FClashOfClans%252Fcomments%252F1f2daw4%252Fseptember_update_balance_changes_breakdown%252F')"&gt;&lt;b&gt;HERE&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; with all the detailed changes coming with this update!&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://clashofclans.inbox.supercell.com/#/en/news/1dTCTk4XyUjDjJQ5wETequ"/>
    <link href="https://clashofclans.inbox.supercell.com/lqe2co20rkhw/8-4iIDr2ExmJQcIxcV2R2CptZ4-Kjj4fasbqlTT3Xkk/cb3cd66437384a7e637bc180818a5357/tw_20200619_Qol_-Balance-Changes-thumb_2.jpg?w=900&amp;h=506&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"/>
    <category term="News"/>
    <published>2024-08-27T11:12:39+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>5rPsn18ofKjFBIu1zjPE09</id>
    <title>Tabletop RPG Adventure Awaits!</title>
    <updated>2024-09-16T10:48:38.284000+00:00</updated>
    <content>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the realm of fantasy, adventure, and mystery!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What you can expect from this Season is:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Tabletop RPG-inspired Skins&lt;/b&gt;: Barbarian Orc, Archer Satyr, Grand Dwarf, and Paladin Champion!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Season Challenges&lt;/b&gt; are on and will last until September 30th!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Challenge Level #1&lt;/b&gt;: “Just Roll With it!” is already available until September 9th, while &lt;b&gt;Challenge #2&lt;/b&gt; will become available on September 10th!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are also excited to reveal a &lt;b&gt;brand-new event &lt;/b&gt;for you to try involving lots of Treasure on September 11th, and more information will be shared in the upcoming episode of Clash On!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;But that is not all for Events this month! We will also run a &lt;b&gt;Mini Spotlight&lt;/b&gt; on September 14-19th, which will be available to players Town Hall 10 and higher.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;There will also be, of course, &lt;b&gt;Clan Games&lt;/b&gt; on September 22-28th, as you have already come to expect from us.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;And that is not everything… oh not at all. We have many features coming out with a &lt;b&gt;major update on September 9&lt;/b&gt;, so get ready for an epic Clash On episode!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;b&gt;Changes to the Gold Pass&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;We will be making some changes to the Clash of Clans Gold Pass. Starting September 1st, the Gold Pass will feature a new cosmetic item on its premium track, replacing the usual Hero Skin from the season&amp;#39;s Skin set. The main reason for this change is to introduce a cosmetic item that is accessible and usable by all players, regardless of your Town Hall level. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;We understand that this change may not be satisfactory for everyone, and we are committed to listening to your feedback on these changes, as well as your thoughts on the new cosmetic items. We are also exploring new ways for you to obtain Skins in the game!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;#39;re curious about the new decoration that will replace the seasonable Hero Skin in September’s Gold Pass, we&amp;#39;ve shared a sneak peek of this new cosmetic item below for you to see!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://clashofclans.inbox.supercell.com/lqe2co20rkhw/6wvIWRN4dqfVhXQYfahatM/4fe6da00f0625994fe5cd74d390baf93/TTRPG_SuperDeco_Die_Roll_goldpass.png?w=4000&amp;h=4000&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://clashofclans.inbox.supercell.com/#/en/news/5rPsn18ofKjFBIu1zjPE09"/>
    <link href="https://clashofclans.inbox.supercell.com/lqe2co20rkhw/5ZGtVeWtauBingooi39CPw/e3758d2fda248af9d3e794591c03717b/ttrpg_thumbnail.jpg?w=900&amp;h=506&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"/>
    <category term="News"/>
    <published>2024-09-01T07:40:03+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>0TLlBag5uFhL9uh29HDPe</id>
    <title> Important Message - Changes to Gold Pass</title>
    <updated>2024-09-05T05:30:27.976000+00:00</updated>
    <content>&lt;h1&gt; Important Message - Changes to Gold Pass&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hey Chief,&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We&amp;#39;re here to discuss the recent change made to the Gold Pass. First, we would like to apologize for your negative experience. It was clear that our approach was not the right one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We intended to offer a more diverse cosmetic that all players could enjoy, and we do believe the Decisive Dice is a high-quality and unique Decoration. However, the current Decoration storage issue many players face, as well as the high perceived value of skins, are things we failed to anticipate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This being said, we heard you and &lt;b&gt;we will be reverting this change in the Gold Pass&lt;/b&gt;. &lt;b&gt;This means that the September Gold Pass will have a Hero skin added back&lt;/b&gt; but at the end of the premium track instead due to technical reasons. The referred skin will be the TableTopRPG Grand Warden skin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, Gold Passes in the following months will still have an exclusive seasonal Skin in the track. In the future, any planned changes to the Gold Pass will be communicated in advance and discussed with you, the players, in a more transparent way.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Additionally, we will be adding 20 Starry Ores to everyone on the free track of the Gold Pass next week, and you can claim right now 2 Builder&amp;#39;s Potions once you reach the last tier. &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thank you again for being so vocal and sharing your feedback with us.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;-The Clash of Clans Team&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://clashofclans.inbox.supercell.com/#/en/news/0TLlBag5uFhL9uh29HDPe"/>
    <link href="https://clashofclans.inbox.supercell.com/lqe2co20rkhw/wXk-93KQ1bLgJeG99yov9PC8e_JZu8eDyqTNr4JPC4Y/af2ceba4b81252b4d5837f3355a6327b/cococtupd_social_thumb_190222_084631.jpg?w=900&amp;h=506&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"/>
    <category term="News"/>
    <published>2024-09-04T14:11:44+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>44K4goqHSvbLuq1uDWTDOa</id>
    <title>September Update: Full Patch Notes</title>
    <updated>2024-09-10T10:33:54.549000+00:00</updated>
    <content>&lt;h2&gt;&lt;b&gt;Clan Notice Board and Search!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Have you ever dreamed of a better way to recruit new members for your Clan or find a perfect Clan that feels just like home? Worry no more, Chief! Clans can now post on the Notice Board, which will be a much more detailed and fun way to browse Clans. Here are the details:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Clan Leader and Co-leaders can write a custom message on the Notice Board or use Clan Description as the text of the Notice. In addition, the background image of the notice can be customized.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Players looking for Clans will be presented with Notices from the Clans that fit them the most, including criteria of other Clan members’ activity and other various aspects that the game will take into consideration automatically.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Changing Language or Family-Friendly Clan Settings will unpublish the Clan Notice, and the Notice will have to be re-published. There will be a confirmation dialog before settings are changed and the Notice gets unpublished.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Players can still search for Clans with their name or Clan Tag and with Advanced Options.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;b&gt;Magic Snacks Are Here!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Available during the September Treasure Hunt Event, we are introducing a new, more fun way to reward players with temporary boosts to their builders, heroes, troops, equipment, and research!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Magic Snacks will only be available during the Treasure Hunt Event for now, and can only be won through the Event&amp;#39;s Chests. During this Event, players can win up to 3 Magic Snacks every 48 hours.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Magic Snacks expire within 24 hours and cannot be accumulated or sold like magic items, so you better use them fast!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;They are stored in their own dedicated storage, which will become available when the very first Magic Snack is obtained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;There will be a total of six Magic Snacks in this update: Builder Bite, Study Soup, Mighty Morsel, Power Pancakes, Training Treat, and Clan Castle Cake.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;b&gt;Treasure Hunt: Coming on September 11-30!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is a new, fun way to obtain more rewards from your Multiplayer attacks!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the upcoming Treasure Hunt, we will introduce players to a new concept of looking for Chests in their attacks and obtaining those for extra rewards!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Players will be hunting down Chests, which, after attacking, can be opened up for extra rewards containing Resources, Decorations, Skins, Hero Equipment, Magic Snacks, and Magic Items, including Hammers!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Players can encounter four different types of Chests while trying to open them: Common, Rare, Epic, and Legendary.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, not all highlighted treasure locations will contain a Chest! Some will contain a decoy, and players must search for the real one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Up to three Chests will be available at the event&amp;#39;s start and will refresh every 48 hours.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;b&gt;It is time to SUPERCHARGE!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Are you done with all your building upgrades? Then it&amp;#39;s time to SUPERCHARGE! Push your buildings to the limit by upgrading them further to reach their maximum level!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Starting in Town Hall 16, Supercharges are new optional extra buffs for some buildings. They differ from normal upgrades in a few ways:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Small - They are shorter, cost less, and give smaller stat buffs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Max Level Only - They can only be done when the building has reached its maximum level.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Temporary - When a new level for a building is released, all previous supercharges made at that level are depleted, and those buildings lose their buffs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Each building can be Supercharged up to three times, each time buffing a different stat adding a more powerful lightning visual effect to your building!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;To Supercharge your buildings you need to employ one of your Builders and spend a few resources.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;There&amp;#39;s a currently an known bug with Supercharges: When you start a Supercharge upgrade, the building is not disabled. This mean that the upgrading Defense will still defend while upgrading and both Collectors &amp;amp; Mines will still generate Resources We will be releasing in the future an optional update to fix this.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Enjoy the extra power and become a Supercharger!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;b&gt;Introducing Legendary Scenery: Clash of Dragons!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;This scenery will feature incredibly detailed large-scale regions and elements that have never been seen before in Clash of Clans. Some additional details and visual features are transition animations, and cut scenes that are hand-made for these sceneries to make them extra special and unique. We will also roll out a behind-the-scenes video explaining the process of creating such detailed and elaborate cosmetic content. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;These kinds of scenery will only come out occasionally as they take an order of magnitude more time than the regular-size Sceneries that players have come to expect in the game. In terms of the physical size of Legendary Sceneries, they are over six times the size of the previous sceneries that we released in the game.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;b&gt;Hard Mode Changes&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Common Hero Equipment levels are now capped at level 15.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Epic Hero Equipment levels are now capped at level 21.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Attacking Hero DPS -5% (from -15%).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Attacking Hero HP -5% (from -10%).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Defense building DPS +5% (no change).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;b&gt;Quality of Life improvements&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tactical Overview is now enabled in Village Edit Mode, as well as while scouting in Wars.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;All Puppet Equipment now has a button to see the troop that will be summoned.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;When trying to purchase something for gems, the pop-up prompting you to purchase gems will now detail how many gems you were missing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The War Map will now display the donated amount and total capacity of each player&amp;#39;s Clan Castle troops instead of the word “Donate“.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Single Player and Practice tabs will now display your progress on the tab itself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;A pop-up will now ask you to confirm your signing up for the Legend League.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Seasonal Obstacles are now bundled by the corresponding season in the layout editor inventory.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;A confirmation popup is now shown if trying to exit Clan settings with unsaved changes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Clan popup is no longer closed after editing settings. ‘My Clan’ tab is shown instead with updated settings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;ZZZ playing from Worker Huts is now consistent with whether or not that builder is actively working.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;b&gt;Balance Changes&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;As previously noted in our notice post, the September Balance Changes are now here, along with the update! If you forgot what they were, you can find them right &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%253A%252F%252Fclashofclans.inbox.supercell.com%252F%2523%252Fen%252Fnews%252F1dTCTk4XyUjDjJQ5wETequ%252Fnotice-regarding-upcoming-september-balance-changes')"&gt;HERE&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;b&gt;Economy Balance Changes&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;We would like to give players more rewards for battling! So, to do that, we increased the Dark Elixir rewards in the League bonus for most Leagues, and we increased the percentage of resources that players can loot from storages! This means that you can steal more from Storages from others, but be careful - this also applies to your own Storages!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bug Fixes&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Magic Mirror Clones no longer receive damage boost from Invisibility vials or any equipment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Clones from Magic Mirror no longer affect the re-deployment time of Archer Queen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Clones from Magic Mirror no longer receive passive DPS buffs from equipment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixed an issue where some player names could contain invisible characters. These characters are no longer allowed to be used.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixed an issue where performing an attack that completes the Star Bonus consumes Shield twice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Google Play Games PC: Clan Castle and Siege Machines now share the same shortcut key.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://clashofclans.inbox.supercell.com/#/en/news/44K4goqHSvbLuq1uDWTDOa"/>
    <link href="https://clashofclans.inbox.supercell.com/lqe2co20rkhw/47BDcpJVHrq01DJBmvQgva/679588eeaff403c0b2f4d43caeceb884/Thumb-PatchNotes.png?w=900&amp;h=506&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"/>
    <category term="Game Updates"/>
    <published>2024-09-09T09:01:39+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>3hYQCg8Q892FuthrHSvkL2</id>
    <title>The LEGENDARY Scenery!</title>
    <updated>2024-09-14T09:58:10.244000+00:00</updated>
    <content>&lt;h1&gt;Introducing: The new Legendary Scenery!&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On September 11th, we will introduce the biggest piece of cosmetic content yet: The Legendary Scenery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This scenery will feature incredibly detailed large-scale regions and elements that have never been seen before in Clash of Clans. Some additional details and visual features are; transition animations and cutscenes in different spots on the map that will tell a story from our Heroes&amp;#39; point of view.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We will also roll out a behind-the-scenes video explaining the process of creating such detailed and elaborate cosmetic content. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://clashofclans.inbox.supercell.com/lqe2co20rkhw/tQEEDCffZT4pJOaYjV7OH/7a32911995acc9e91ad6264225d6ea0a/CoC_LegendaryScenery_04.jpg?w=2850&amp;h=2110&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This new tier of sceneries will only come out occasionally as they take an order of magnitude, at least 6x more times than the regular-size Sceneries that players have come to expect in the game. In terms of the physical size of Legendary Sceneries, they are over six times the size of the previous sceneries that we released in the game.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Regular Sceneries will still be released in the game, during months where Legendary Sceneries are not released. Therefore you can expect that most of the future seasons will still have Regular Sceneries.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://clashofclans.inbox.supercell.com/lqe2co20rkhw/5UGvg6mnykYT4jgKzwKhkr/0cc8792b0fca31dcf88d06664ab0849b/legendaryscenerycrop2.jpg?w=2692&amp;h=2093&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;#39;s now discuss the pricing for our latest cosmetic addition. The Legendary Scenery cost will be $32,99 (Tax is not included), and the price might vary depending on your region. It represents our most premium offering to date. We want to be fully transparent about the reasoning behind the high price. We are committed to diversifying our monetization, with a focus on cosmetics. We believe a game that is more cosmetics focused, when it comes to monetisation, is much fairer and player friendly. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The legendary scenery is designed to be the pinnacle of exclusivity and aspiration within our game, and hence the higher price tag. In the future, we will also introduce lower price cosmetic type for those that see this cosmetic as too expensive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We look forward to your feedback and first impressions about the Legendary Scenery in September! We are super excited about this new cosmetic, and we hope you enjoy it as much as we did!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;- The Clash of Clans Team&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://clashofclans.inbox.supercell.com/#/en/news/3hYQCg8Q892FuthrHSvkL2"/>
    <link href="https://clashofclans.inbox.supercell.com/lqe2co20rkhw/6WC0XuZViPmnCqSjujjKMc/cf5e5d4861c825513d656c1015ff9ef9/scenery-comms-thumb.png?w=900&amp;h=506&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"/>
    <category term="News"/>
    <published>2024-09-09T17:36:43+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>779okptngIJG7llXLUms9F</id>
    <title>Turn Your Village Into a Kingdom!</title>
    <updated>2024-09-11T08:42:48.643000+00:00</updated>
    <link href="https://clashofclans.inbox.supercell.com/#/en/news/779okptngIJG7llXLUms9F"/>
    <link href="https://clashofclans.inbox.supercell.com/lqe2co20rkhw/Wob1kJp1aY7oV77qeGfSF/d5ac79242c1b3138ded54a34255bd710/CoC_SC018_Dragons_EN_1920x1080_Still_Thumbnail_v03_RB_eyestorm.jpg?w=900&amp;h=506&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"/>
    <link href="https://youtu.be/ybJPLeMa2lM"/>
    <category term="News"/>
    <published>2024-09-10T08:00:04+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>6o2RlXowHsNVXPuac7pMZg</id>
    <title>NEW: The Treasure Hunt Event!</title>
    <updated>2024-09-12T10:28:36.335000+00:00</updated>
    <content>&lt;h1&gt;Introducing the new Treasure Hunt Event!&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hey Chief, in the September update, we plan to release a new feature coming to Clash: the Treasure Hunt Event!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;What is the Treasure Hunt Event?&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;img src="https://clashofclans.inbox.supercell.com/lqe2co20rkhw/2jkBjdW5tarmyJqgIniplW/776fde7599099845d721a2d6823e9361/NEW.png?w=700&amp;h=700&amp;f=center"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Treasure Hunt Event will be available for TH6 and above players and will last for 20 days. In this event, players will destroy certain Buildings and Defenses for a chance to find Chests that will contain random rewards!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;During this event, it will be possible to get 3 Treasure Chests every 2 days (48 hours). You can get a maximum of 1 Chest per Home Village attack, and after you have found three (so completed 3 successful Home Village attacks), you will have to wait until the Event timer (48h) refreshes to get more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;What are Treasure Chests?&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Chests are only available during the Treasure Hunt Event, and they contain a random set of rewards corresponding to the players’ Town Hall &amp;amp; Builder Hall levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Chests are not purchasable. During this event, they can only be obtained by destroying key Buildings in Multiplayer attacks in the Home Village.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are 4 different rarity types of Chests: &lt;b&gt;Common, Rare, Epic&lt;/b&gt;,&lt;b&gt; &amp;amp; Legendary. &lt;/b&gt;What are the chances of getting each? Well, let’s say that some luck is needed if you want to get Legendary Chests all the time!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After you’ve found a Chest, a new screen will appear where you will have to hit the Chest with a Hammer 4 times to see what type of rarity you will get in the Chest. After that, the Chest will open automatically.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Additionally, you will be able to see what the drop rates will be for each Chest when this feature goes live!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://clashofclans.inbox.supercell.com/lqe2co20rkhw/4XyCbrdOgnOxzsXNqFmOAk/30db1576ee4176643d28c1f2e5a64002/chessts.png?w=4000&amp;h=4000&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Why are we releasing this feature?&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We wanted to bring something new and exciting to players by introducing the Chest system. It offers extra rewards through attacking, and thereby adds a fun and unexpected twist to the gameplay.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the same time, we wanted to fix one issue with the game which is the inability to distribute rewards to players evenly depending on their Town Hall level. This feature now allows us to give you rewards based on your Town Hall level which means that you can have the maximum profit on the rewards that you can get.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Additionally, this feature provides a way for players to get rewards from every existing game mode, such as Home Village, Builder Base, and Clan Capital, as well as all different types of resources for players such as Magic Items &amp;amp; Cosmetics. Now that we have such a feature that allows a good reward distribution, how would we make it fun for players to unlock it? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Adding a Random factor felt like the best option for that whilst making it interesting &amp;amp; exciting at the same time when getting the Chests.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We hope this gives you a clear perspective and understanding of how this new feature works and the reasoning behind its release. As always, we are open and excited to hear your feedback!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Clash ON!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;-The Clash of Clans team&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://clashofclans.inbox.supercell.com/#/en/news/6o2RlXowHsNVXPuac7pMZg"/>
    <link href="https://clashofclans.inbox.supercell.com/lqe2co20rkhw/3oUL1g6ERVGnLWhEA9c9yn/b98ecc0130366fded9e73f97c8dfd5fc/thumbnail-th.png?w=900&amp;h=506&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"/>
    <category term="News"/>
    <published>2024-09-10T13:12:16+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>7giBNIxPM9Dcbkh8jx5scm</id>
    <title>Important Announcement!</title>
    <updated>2024-09-16T02:46:44.286000+00:00</updated>
    <content>&lt;h1&gt;Important Announcement!&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hey Chief,&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As you know, we&amp;#39;ve been facing several issues these past few days. We&amp;#39;re really sorry about that. Our team has been working against the clock to tackle all the major bugs, and we released an optional update and maintenance to fix most of them. However, that created another issue, and once again, we had to go into maintenance. We&amp;#39;re now working to get all these issues fixed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That being said, we will have to postpone the Treasure Hunt event until we are 100% certain that your experience is the best one possible. We don&amp;#39;t have a date to share yet but rest assured, we will keep communicating with you, and as soon as we know more, so will you. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now let&amp;#39;s talk about compensation. Due to the bugs faced and the delayed event, this is what we have planned:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Star Bonus X2 for 7 Days:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Start: Saturday, September 14th, 08:00 AM UTC &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;End: Saturday, September 21st, 08:00 AM UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Free Chests&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;We will also give more free Chests as compensation. However, we must wait until the event starts so you can all have a good experience opening them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;This time, the free Chests will be available in the game, and you can claim them as soon as you log in when the event starts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Coming soon: The Mini Spotlight Event!&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We just want to remind everyone that the event starts tomorrow, Saturday, September 14th at 08:00 AM UTC. You will be able to earn a lot of loot from this event, and it should be a great experience for everyone!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We will keep sharing updates with you. Thank you for all the feedback and bug reports these past few days. They&amp;#39;ve been incredibly helpful!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;-The Clash of Clans Team&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://clashofclans.inbox.supercell.com/#/en/news/7giBNIxPM9Dcbkh8jx5scm"/>
    <link href="https://clashofclans.inbox.supercell.com/lqe2co20rkhw/9arMp1KRgg0Gky1dNUELWz7M_90XEcZcx-Eov_-7dFg/b9fe59c6083bcf52e9ae6f9f6e6cfd28/giant_builder900x506.png?w=900&amp;h=506&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"/>
    <category term="News"/>
    <published>2024-09-13T18:14:34+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>53iW9CiupeQNrbHIclFLx1</id>
    <title>Missed your free Chests? Claim it here!</title>
    <updated>2024-09-22T19:33:12.401000+00:00</updated>
    <link href="https://clashofclans.inbox.supercell.com/#/en/news/53iW9CiupeQNrbHIclFLx1"/>
    <link href="https://clashofclans.inbox.supercell.com/lqe2co20rkhw/1pdRNCzXCPNSfkAasDsMTi/fc21b3483c3d08719f4b9517fa1c2244/treasure_event_popup.png?w=900&amp;h=506&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"/>
    <link href="clashofclans-inbox://action=voucher&amp;code=53a84a01-ac52-4502-a7a0-0a0b70a7cd93"/>
    <category term="News"/>
    <published>2024-09-19T08:02:48+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>1iYDyqIj8X7Zdn6UFMXXQA</id>
    <title> Clash-O-Ween is back!</title>
    <updated>2024-10-01T08:58:33.595000+00:00</updated>
    <content>&lt;h1&gt;Something spooky has awakened in this manic Mashup Season!&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;#39;s what awaits you, Chief...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Mashup Season &lt;/b&gt;is here from&lt;b&gt; October 1-31st! &lt;/b&gt;Featuring Spooky Trio of Archer Queen (available in the Gold Pass), Barbarian King, and Grand Warden - you can take a peek at these new skins below!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;As expected,&lt;b&gt; Clan War League &lt;/b&gt;will happen on&lt;b&gt; October 1-11th.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;From &lt;b&gt;October 1-9th&lt;/b&gt;, take on the &lt;b&gt;&amp;quot;Doom and Gloom!&amp;quot; Challenge&lt;/b&gt; and unleash Dark Minion Heroes into the fight!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;11-31st October: &lt;/b&gt;Help the Builder&amp;#39;s Apprentice in Mashup Mania! A manic Clash-O-Ween Medal Event! - Take to the skies with Lavaloons in the &lt;b&gt;&amp;quot;No Strings Attached&amp;quot; Challenge&lt;/b&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;And on &lt;b&gt;October 22-28th Clan Games&lt;/b&gt; return!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://clashofclans.inbox.supercell.com/lqe2co20rkhw/4YkM6h68AIWtzISKnS0Rnk/dc388e2950a20841f0ffa6fb347cd8df/ArcherQueen_Clashoween_500x500.png?w=500&amp;h=500&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;img src="https://clashofclans.inbox.supercell.com/lqe2co20rkhw/5zTBHyNdhQOq4mzjj7OmFA/e487f2b80bed9eacd18945ecc9bc5c91/BarbarianKing_Clashoween_500x500.png?w=500&amp;h=500&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;img src="https://clashofclans.inbox.supercell.com/lqe2co20rkhw/6p4kWjiV350qYgdPMhZe2q/fd1660cd181b7750f72b9fbdbb85076d/GrandWarden_Clashoween_500x500.png?w=500&amp;h=500&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Upcoming Test Regarding Seasonal Challenges&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Starting October 1st, we are going to run a test related to completing Seasonal Challenges more smoothly for some players. The reason for doing this test is to observe what pacing motivates players more to complete the Seasonal Challenges and the Gold Pass in its entirety, if any. This testing will be applied for TH7 and above players and will include three different potential versions of the Seasonal Challenges, given at random to players:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;One group of players will receive the same set of Challenges and pace as any previous set from previous Seasons.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another group of players will receive a set of Challenges that will require fewer points to complete 2,000 total instead of 2,600)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;And lastly, the third group of players will receive have additional Challenge Tasks every week, allowing them to score more points overall from various activities&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;We hope these variations of the Challenges will yield positive results for the overall community down the road and to further improvements toward more players completing more Seasonal Challenges every month.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;- The Clash team&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://clashofclans.inbox.supercell.com/#/en/news/1iYDyqIj8X7Zdn6UFMXXQA"/>
    <link href="https://clashofclans.inbox.supercell.com/lqe2co20rkhw/S9rTaZkEU1jfxeo6EbYm6/ca80c4d19ceabbdf92566a5cc79889b7/CLASHOWEEN_SPLASH_CLEAN_CHARA_AND_BG_.jpg?w=900&amp;h=506&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"/>
    <category term="News"/>
    <published>2024-10-01T08:00:04+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>178guTA1qsWC4Z5RzlEWN3</id>
    <title>Upcoming Balance Changes to Druid</title>
    <updated>2024-10-10T06:26:57.362000+00:00</updated>
    <content>&lt;h1&gt;Druid Balance Changes!&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hello Chief! We wanted to give you a heads-up that we are planning on making some Balance Changes to Druid. We&amp;#39;re aiming to implement those changes as fast as possible in a future game maintenance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We know that Clan War Leagues are starting this week so we are trying as much as possible to get this done either before CWL starts or right at the beginning, in order to avoid impacting your Clan&amp;#39;s performance during CWL. Also with this, we want to give you as much time as we can for you to prepare and be aware that we are implementing those changes soon. You can see below the planned list of changes for the Druid!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;List of Balance Changes&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;table&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Troop&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Troop&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Level&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Healing per second&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Healing per second NEW&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Evolve time sec&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Evolve time sec NEW&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;HP&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;HP NEW&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Druid&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;1&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;110&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;65&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;30&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;25&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Druid&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;2&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;120&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;70&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;30&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;25&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Druid&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;3&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;130&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;75&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;30&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;25&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Druid&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;4&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;140&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;80&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;30&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;25&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bear&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;1&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;3800&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;1900&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bear&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;2&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;4000&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;2000&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bear&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;3&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;4200&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;2100&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bear&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;4&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;4400&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;2200&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Why are we making these changes?&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We&amp;#39;ve noticed an amazing trend in how players are using the Druid. Mass Druid attacks have become incredibly powerful, outperforming other strategies. This was brought to our attention through player feedback and confirmed by our battle balance data. The Druid&amp;#39;s ability to enable these overpowered tactics is the main factor, so we’re making adjustments to keep the Druid balanced but still viable. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We&amp;#39;ll continue monitoring game data and appreciate your feedback as we consider further balance changes if needed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;- The Clash of Clans team&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://clashofclans.inbox.supercell.com/#/en/news/178guTA1qsWC4Z5RzlEWN3"/>
    <category term="News"/>
    <published>2024-10-01T14:25:58+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>aOzruYqjRbEXxuw43AzZu</id>
    <title>Mashup Mania Event!</title>
    <updated>2024-10-24T01:53:34.831000+00:00</updated>
    <content>&lt;h1&gt;Mashup Mania Event &amp; New Hero Equipment! &lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Available for players in Town Hall 6 and up, you will collect &lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sour Elixir&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt; by doing in-game activities and progressing through the Event track. &lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sour Elixir&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt; can be converted into &lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Mashup Medals&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt; and unlock special rewards, such as the new &lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Grand Warden Epic Hero Equipment: Lavaloon Puppet&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;When?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Event Starts:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;October 11th, 8 AM UTC&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Event Ends:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;November 1st, 8 AM UTC&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;After the event ends on &lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;November 1st&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;, you can still access the Trader&amp;#39;s Event tab and the Medal Event Building for two more days, until November 3rd, 8 AM UTC.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;New Temporary Troop: Ice Minion&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;img src="https://clashofclans.inbox.supercell.com/lqe2co20rkhw/01gaFKj92UlTAaacMZHniO/8c1ef237b8b97885b47daa3df88da68e/iceminion.png?w=700&amp;h=700&amp;f=center"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Available for players in Town Hall 6 and above.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Air Unit, favourite target are defenses, and it freezes surrounding buildings and enemies upon death&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Returning Temporary Troops: &lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Barcher&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hog Wizard&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Golem Witch&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lavaloon&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://clashofclans.inbox.supercell.com/lqe2co20rkhw/7IHasMcc7txh5Ndjif5Og/e1380a21deac1a1b26cddc992dbe27db/temptroops.png?w=1473&amp;h=700&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Event Resources!&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Medal Event Resource: Sour Elixir&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;img src="https://clashofclans.inbox.supercell.com/lqe2co20rkhw/2z7G8EQYI1CxxCbcmh9dYz/7e15fb7ab9254ecbcf50036282a09cae/newsour.png?w=700&amp;h=700&amp;f=center"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sour Elixir is obtained by attacking and destroying your opponents&amp;#39; buildings containing Sour Elixir! Gather Elixir to get yourself Ores, Decorations, and more!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Mashup Medals&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;img src="https://clashofclans.inbox.supercell.com/lqe2co20rkhw/4tXAYvI0sjwQkVhoxDeqd/58e6a08d55d9d5ee0951f65d2dad118e/MEDALS-NEW.png?w=700&amp;h=700&amp;f=center"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event&amp;#39;s currency that you can spend at the Trader&amp;#39;s Shop. Use your Medals to purchase unique seasonal Decorations, resources such as Ores for your Hero Equipment, Magic Items and more. The top-tier item is the new Epic Hero Equipment - Lavaloon Puppet!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;New Hero Equipment &amp; Other Rewards!&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;New Grand Warden Epic Hero Equipment: Lavaloon Puppet&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;img src="https://clashofclans.inbox.supercell.com/lqe2co20rkhw/MOfkArQ51GLaKjDTqvWCd/08abbbf7711ff5ce1e82c8c34e1489ce/HeroGear_LavaloonDoll0000.png?w=700&amp;h=700&amp;f=center"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This Equipment summons spooky Lavaloons to fight alongside you. The number of units summoned varies depending on the Equipment&amp;#39;s level.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And, of course, there will be fun decorations available for you to obtain during the event!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://clashofclans.inbox.supercell.com/lqe2co20rkhw/6zlcH1Z89YjOUS33tehQL3/2de16d0fac4e7df6988671b76cef28c1/3decos_mashup.png?w=1580&amp;h=700&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://clashofclans.inbox.supercell.com/#/en/news/aOzruYqjRbEXxuw43AzZu"/>
    <link href="https://clashofclans.inbox.supercell.com/lqe2co20rkhw/kX4nkZYeIUgM4h07SZWQI/eb7faedbe59d8cc0c5c39773d8921b84/thumb_mashup.png?w=900&amp;h=506&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"/>
    <category term="News"/>
    <published>2024-10-11T07:45:45+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>4fysCLQTRGgHdqYotEFW7m</id>
    <title>Clash-A-Rama: The Weird Woods </title>
    <updated>2024-10-14T10:09:25.593000+00:00</updated>
    <link href="https://clashofclans.inbox.supercell.com/#/en/news/4fysCLQTRGgHdqYotEFW7m"/>
    <link href="https://clashofclans.inbox.supercell.com/lqe2co20rkhw/6q612aLkzBoPw9P0glXTeM/4ff0059c189d609b6ddd40244a5a21df/thumb_clasharama_mashupmania.png?w=900&amp;h=506&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"/>
    <link href="https://youtu.be/HqEN1h1z8sU?si=jqJZHs89rwhPGEii"/>
    <category term="News"/>
    <published>2024-10-11T09:05:45+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>73e4HgoCgXTxKmryk6FAb0</id>
    <title>Hammer Jam Is at Stake!</title>
    <updated>2024-11-04T11:55:30.712000+00:00</updated>
    <link href="https://clashofclans.inbox.supercell.com/#/en/news/73e4HgoCgXTxKmryk6FAb0"/>
    <link href="https://clashofclans.inbox.supercell.com/lqe2co20rkhw/4cAeWUlaHZBDVjZeH8ymRE/48504470402e579b503221c22c3b83b5/inbox_thumbnail_hammerjam_missinghammer.png?w=900&amp;h=506&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"/>
    <link href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5A7Ns3G1DOc"/>
    <category term="News"/>
    <published>2024-11-04T10:34:44+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>4qiS27QrSzlTrTzhE96NOB</id>
    <title>New Podcast Out Now</title>
    <updated>2024-11-05T10:42:54.316000+00:00</updated>
    <link href="https://clashofclans.inbox.supercell.com/#/en/news/4qiS27QrSzlTrTzhE96NOB"/>
    <link href="https://clashofclans.inbox.supercell.com/lqe2co20rkhw/4br2Q5mkZzllbvff5rQ7ff/6b818a9bd5c0bc12b56e8b1ba26fbe12/MIssing_Hammer_Announcement_Post_16x9.png?w=900&amp;h=506&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"/>
    <link href="https://youtu.be/8kNf73WRE1o"/>
    <category term="News"/>
    <published>2024-11-04T15:05:03+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>6l4ckuGehzEiXxLXCCvhOv</id>
    <title>Listen to the Hamerless Podcast ep2!</title>
    <updated>2024-11-06T01:54:47.912000+00:00</updated>
    <link href="https://clashofclans.inbox.supercell.com/#/en/news/6l4ckuGehzEiXxLXCCvhOv"/>
    <link href="https://clashofclans.inbox.supercell.com/lqe2co20rkhw/IYQBsYdxtZLbynxYYzp5h/505aef9a8e3c178daa2585a869b4ec45/Youtube_Ep2.png?w=900&amp;h=506&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"/>
    <link href="https://youtu.be/pBX7m2jLx4k"/>
    <category term="News"/>
    <published>2024-11-05T15:02:02+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
