<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Clashroyale - Esport News</title>
    <link>https://github.com/skrwo/supercell-inbox-rss/</link>
    <description>RSS wrapper of Clashroyale inbox Esport News</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 08:36:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>What's coming for CR Esports!</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the World of Clash Royale Esports! &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here, you’ll find the most relevant information about the competitive scene, what tournaments are coming up and past tournament information. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This article will be frequently updated. Make sure to come back so you don’t miss anything!
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr/&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Upcoming tournaments&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Get your decks ready, and don’t forget to sign up! Check out the upcoming tournaments here as they are announced.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr/&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Ongoing tournaments&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Want to watch the world’s best players in action? Here’s where you will be able to find the ongoing tournaments supported by us! 

&lt;b&gt;Clash Royale League 2024&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;CRL is back with another year of the highest level of competitive Clash Royale! Following last year&amp;#39;s format, 2024 brings you top-tier gameplay with Monthly Qualifiers, Golden Tickets, an in-person event, and more!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Format: &lt;/b&gt;Starting in April, the top 1000 players of the Path of Legends will be able to face each other in Monthly Qualifiers until only 8 players remain. The top 8 players will then move to the Monthly Finals, with the winner receiving a Golden Ticket directly to the CRL World Finals. A total of 5 monthly competitions will be played in-game via the Tournament Hub from April to August. The top player of the CRL24 Leaderboard, a player from China, and the top player from the Community Tournaments Leaderboard will join the 5 players that qualified through the Monthly Qualifiers. At the World Finals, these 8 players will go head to head for the title of World Champion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Participation criteria: &lt;/b&gt;You need to be 16 years old or older to participate in the CRL Monthly Qualifiers. Players must pass the fair play check, participate with clean accounts, and follow good sportsmanship.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dragon League by QLASH&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The QLASH App events reached the next level! We’re excited to present a new event that will accompany the players throughout the entire Clash Royale competitive season!
From fiery Qualifiers to scorching hot Monthly Finals, the format will reward skill and consistency, granting everyone the chance to compete for a share of the $30.000 prize pool and some exclusive Clash Royale League points for this year&amp;#39;s community leaderboard!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Format: &lt;/b&gt;Starting April 1st, the Dragon League will host 5 seasons, with a total of four stages, each leading to the Grand Final, later this year. Starting in the Path of Dragon, players will be able to play daily tournaments to gather points to the Dragon League Leaderboard. By placing in the top 96, these players along with 16 players from 2 Last Chance Qualifiers, will qualify for the Dragon&amp;#39;s Breath Tournament, a 128 double-elimination bracket where the top 16 players move on to the Dragon League Monthly Final, playing a 16-player double-elimination bracket, which will also award points for the CRL community leaderboard. The best 3 players of each Monthly Final will have the chance to participate in a Grand Final event later this year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Participation criteria: &lt;/b&gt;You need to be 16 years old or older to participate in the CRL Monthly Qualifiers. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Past tournaments&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Below you’ll find some of the past tournaments where players battled for prize money, trophies and glory. Feel free to check the VODs to rewatch all the action!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;CRL Warmup 2023&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;CRL 2023 Warmup brought together last year’s CRL World Finalists along with the 16 best players from open qualifiers! Three stages were played: Open Qualifiers, Double-Round Robin Group Stage and Single-Elimination Bracket finals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Format and rules&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fdocs.google.com%2Fdocument%2Fd%2F1bXmBSgGl-_SYlZUKv21hJungIcHbuApbnNKWrW3yJ7Y%2Fedit')"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;b&gt;Participation &lt;/b&gt;was free and open to 16 year old+ players.
&lt;b&gt;Rewatch the finals:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fyoutu.be%2FaaH-3rxNNc4')"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;
AMG Cup&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sixteen of the best players in the world were invited to compete in a single elimination bracket during two days of competition. Every battle was played in Megadraft, a game mode that consists of picking cards from a total of 36 possible, with the order of choice alternating between the two opponents.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Format: &lt;/b&gt;16 player single elimination bracket using Megadraft mode.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Participation criteria: &lt;/b&gt;Invitational&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rewatch the finals&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fyoutu.be%2F7ZbJmo4vzqI')"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Clash Royale League 2022&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Throughout 2022, 16 players had the chance to qualify for the CRL World Finals. Six managed to do it through community tournaments that guaranteed the winner a Golden Ticket. The remaining ten achieved it during the 6-week official CRL qualifiers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The World Finals took place in Helsinki, Finland, with a prize pool of $1.000,000 on the line! &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Participation was free and open to 16 year old+ players.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Format and rules &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fesports.clashroyale.com%2Fnews%2Fclash-royale-league-2022-world-finals')"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rewatch the World Finals here! &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.twitch.tv%2Fvideos%2F1598923960')"&gt;Day 1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.twitch.tv%2Fvideos%2F1599909508')"&gt;Day 2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.twitch.tv%2Fvideos%2F1600914042')"&gt;Day 3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;b&gt;
&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;LetsPlay.Live Clash Royale Asia-Pacific Tour&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;LPL Clash Royale Asia-Pacific Tour invited mobile esports fans across Oceania, Southeast Asia, Japan and Korea, to compete for a share of $27,500 AUD. The prize pool was shared across the tournament’s two divisions: Open Division and Pro Division, with Pro Division being broadcast by LPL in English, Japanese and Korean!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Participation was free and opened to 16 year old+ players residing in Japan, Korea, SEA or ANZ regions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Format and rules &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fclash.s3.ap-southeast-2.amazonaws.com%2FLPL%2BCLASH%2BROYALE%2BASIA-PACIFIC%2BTOUR%2BRULESET.pdf')"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rewatch the finals &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.twitch.tv%2Fvideos%2F1708505099')"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;b&gt;Dreamhack Dedsafío Royale&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dedsafio Royale was held at one of the biggest live events of the year: DreamHack Valencia. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A total of 9 invited + 3 qualified players competed in the Dreamhack’s mainstage for a share of 15.000€ in prize pool!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Participation was free and open to 16 year old+ players visiting Dreamhack.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Format and rules &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fdreamhack.es%2Fdedsafio-royale-dreamhack%2F%23online')"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rewatch the finals &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fyoutu.be%2Fyb8sVYAKysY')"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;RoyaleMSTRS: &lt;/b&gt;Summer Clash &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A 2-weekend event with 4 Open Qualifiers, each featuring a unique Party Game Mode! The 4 Qualifiers lead into the Combination Championship, featuring all 4 Party Game Modes!

The 4 Party Game Modes that were featured in this event were &lt;b&gt;3x Elixir, Triple Draft, Sudden Death and Heist&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Format: &lt;/b&gt;All 4 Qualifiers followed the same format, except that each Qualifier featured a single, unique Party Game Mode being played. Players competed in as many Qualifiers as they wanted until they qualified for the Combination Championship&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Open Registration, in-game tournament: &lt;/b&gt;The in-game tournament used the Party Game Mode featured that Qualifier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Top 8 players&lt;/b&gt; from the in-game tournament advanced to the single elimination bracket stage, where the Top 2 players qualified for the Combination Championship.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Combination Championship:&lt;/b&gt; Once the 4 qualifier tournaments took place, the Top 2 players from each tournament qualified for the Combination Championship, a single elimination bracket. All matches were Best of 3 across various party game modes featured in the qualifier tournaments, except Grand Finals, which was a Best of 5.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Participation criteria: &lt;/b&gt;You needed to be 16 years old or older to participate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;BESF Cup&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Belgium Esports Federation brought you the BESF Cup, where you were able to compete in a solo and clan track to prove you are one of the best Clash Royale Players.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Format: &lt;/b&gt;Eight qualifiers were held. In each one of them, two players qualified for the offline finals at the Pukkelpop&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;music festival. The game format for all BESF Cup Solo Qualifiers was as follows: 1v1 in-game duel-friendly battle mode. Finals featured a 16-player bracket.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Participation criteria: &lt;/b&gt;You needed to be 16+ years old or to participate and reside in any of the following countries: Albania, Andorra, Armenia, Austria, Azerbaijan, Belarus, Belgium, Bosnia and Herzegovina, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Faroe Islands, Finland, France, Georgia, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Kazakhstan, Kosovo, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Moldova, Monaco, Montenegro, Netherlands, North-Macedonia, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, San Marino, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey, Ukraine, United Kingdom, Vatican city.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Meg 2023&lt;/b&gt;
Meg returned with the 2023 edition, covering multiple esports competitions with offline finals in Rio de Janeiro.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Format:&lt;/b&gt; Three stages were played, the Open Qualifiers and the Playoffs online, and the Grand Finals Offline on the main event.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Participation criteria: &lt;/b&gt;You needed to be 16 years old or older to participate. You needed to reside in the LATAM region.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;RoyaleMSTRS&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;RoyaleMSTRS was back with their traditional 5 week season, and with it returned with the MSTRS Duels format! Their traditional series featured five weeks of competition and included 3 Open Qualifiers, 1 Wild Card Open, and Playoffs to determine a winner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Format:&lt;/b&gt; Players competed in weekly Qualifiers to earn Qualification Points. After three Open Qualifiers, the top 6 players received an automatic invite to the Playoffs. The other 2 players for the Playoffs were decided through the Wild Card Open, where the top 2 players at the end of the event qualified for the last 2 Playoff spots. The 8 players that qualified for the Playoffs were placed into a double-elimination bracket, with all upper bracket matchups being a Bo3 and the Grand Finals &amp;amp; all lower bracket matchups being a Bo5.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Participation criteria: &lt;/b&gt;You needed to be 16 years old or older to participate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Clash Royale League 2023&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Clash Royale League had yet another year of high-level competition! With a new format, a total of 1.3 million USD on the line, and some epic matches to be played, Clash Royale League 2023 was set up to be better than ever! In 2023 we’ve decided to take the best of the 2021 and 2022 CRL formats and combine them to make a perfect combination!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Format: &lt;/b&gt;Starting February 6th with the Path of Legends, the top 1000 players were able to battle it out in Monthly Qualifiers until 8 players remained, who moved on to the Monthly Finals. A total of seven (7) monthly competitions were played in-game via the Tournament hub throughout the year. Through our seven months of competition we had 14 players qualified for the World Finals. They were joined by two players from China to make up the best 16 players in the world who had a chance to prove themselves in the Arena to be crowned World Champion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Participation criteria: &lt;/b&gt;You need to be 16 years old or older to participate in the CRL Monthly Qualifiers. Players must pass the fair play check, participate with clean accounts, and follow good sportsmanship.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;RoyaleMSTRS: King of the Hill &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;RoyaleMSTRS was back with 9 King of the Hill events over 9 months! With 24 games, each player was guaranteed at least three chances to become ‘King’ and remain on top. In addition to remaining King and continuing to play, each win awarded players $100!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Format: &lt;/b&gt;Players competed in an in-game tournament, where the top 8 qualified players were invited to the ‘Main Event’ the following day. Those eight players were randomly sorted, and then the first two played a single game against each other without card restrictions. The winner stays on, the loser goes to the back of the line, and the next player challenges the previous winner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Participation criteria: &lt;/b&gt;You need to be 16 years old or older to participate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;ESL Snapdragon Pro Series Season 3&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Snapdragon Pro Series featured 3 Open Cups of different formats: Duels, Mega Draft, and 2v2. The Season Finals had the duos compete in all 3 modes (1v1 Duels, 1v1 Mega Draft, 2v2) and crowned the best duo in Season 3 of the Snapdragon Pro Series!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Format&lt;/b&gt;: Every Open format type listed below featured 3 Open Cups. The winners of these cups qualified directly to their corresponding Open Finals, while other competitors earned points towards their ranking. The Top 5 players from the ranking system also qualified for the Open Finals. The Top 8 players from their respective qualifiers faced off in a single-elimination bracket to crown the champion!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Participation criteria: &lt;/b&gt;You need to be 16 years old or older to participate and live in the regions of NA, LATAM, Europe or MENA.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;LPL World Tour - Season 2&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Tournament had a total of eight Open Qualifiers, with the top 2 players from each Open Qualifier entering the Pro Division and the rest placed in the Open Division. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Format:&lt;/b&gt; In the Pro Division, the top 16 qualified players entered a 16-team Double-Elimination bracket to crown the global champion, and in the Open Division, players who did not qualify for the Pro Division were placed in a Single-Elimination bracket to find the best Open Division player.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Participation criteria: &lt;/b&gt;You need to be 16 years old or older to participate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;ESL Snapdragon Pro Series Season 4&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Season 4 came packed with exciting opportunities, including a total prize pool of $25,000 and fresh ways to compete and emerge victorious. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Format: &lt;/b&gt;The competition consisted of 3 open cups, a 2v2 Cup, a 1v1 Cup, and a 1v1 Mega Draft Cup, each having a Qualifier Phase, and Finals. The victors of these cups earned direct qualification to their respective Open Finals. Meanwhile, other competitors accumulated points to bolster their rankings. The top 5 players from the ranking system also secured a spot in the Open Finals. The top 8 players&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;from their respective qualifiers engaged in a thrilling single-elimination bracket showdown to determine the ultimate champion!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Participation criteria: &lt;/b&gt;You need to be 16 years old or older to participate. Players must reside in the following regions to participate: Europe &amp;amp; MENA, North America, and Latin America&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dreamhack 2023 Circuit&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dreamhack was back, featuring 4 events, with each final being hosted at gaming festivals in Andorra, Valencia, Barcelona, and the Grand Finals in Valencia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Format:&lt;/b&gt; Each event had an Online Qualifier, qualifying 6 players for the offline event; an Offline Qualifier, qualifying 2 players for the main competitions, which was played in a single-elimination bracket. Players collected points to decide who qualified for the Dreamhack Grand Finals in Valencia, with the top 6 guaranteeing their spot. the remaining 2 spots were decided in an Online Qualifier that was played between the top 16 players (from 7th to 23rd places) and an Offline Qualifier in the event before the main competition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Participation criteria: &lt;/b&gt;You need to be 16 years old or older to participate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Queso Cup&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After the success of the Queso Cup Teams Edition at the end of 2022, we brought you again a more team-driven competition; 4 organizations that were present in the past CRL Teams Edition competed throughout the year against four other teams that entered the event through open qualifiers. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Format:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Split 1 (24th March - 23rd April): 8-team league format: One-way, 7 match days, and Final Bracket.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Split 2 (19th July - 27th August): 8-team league format: Double-way, 14 match days and Final Bracket.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last Chance Qualifier (14th - 17th December): 8-team double elimination bracket (For extra points!)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Grand Finals (20th - 23rd December): The Best six teams at the end of the year will compete over four days in a double-elimination bracket. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Participation criteria:&lt;/b&gt; Open to every team of three to five players. Players need to be 16+ years old.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;GKR Leagues&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;GKR was back with five new team-based competitions for 2023 with a total prize pool of $46,000! There were four competitions to participate in: Spring Split, Summer Split, Autumn Split and Winter Split. From there, you had the chance to qualify for the main event: the GKR Finals 2023.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Format:&lt;/b&gt; For each Split, four (4) qualifiers were held to determine the eight (8) official participant teams. From then on, teams played a group stage to determine the top teams that would qualify for the playoffs. The winner of each Split automatically qualified for the GKR Finals 2023, having a total of four (4) teams meet on December 28th to determine the GKR 2023 World Champion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Participation criteria: &lt;/b&gt;Open to every team. One team captain + four players are needed for each team to participate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;National League Series - 14th Edition&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The competition consisted of 2 regular splits and finals, taking the top 2 teams from each split to the Grand Finals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Format: &lt;/b&gt;Split 1 (National Series Red) and Split 2 (National Series Blue) started with an 8 team Group Phase in which the top 6 teams moved on to a single-elimination bracket, qualifying the top 2 teams from each split to the Grand Finals (National Series Gold)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Participation criteria: &lt;/b&gt;You need to be 16 years old or older to participate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;CRL Warmup 2024&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;CRL Warmup brought together 14 of the CRL23 top players along with 10 players from 5 Qualifiers! The competition consisted of 3 stages: Open Qualifiers, a Double Round-Robin Group Stage, and a Double-elimination Final Bracket.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Format and rules&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fdocs.google.com%2Fdocument%2Fd%2F1-eEido2iSgekm0cjs321eHbPSztwA4UGSAXyPMk7qME%2Fedit')"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Participation &lt;/b&gt;is free and open to 16-year-old+ players. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are always looking for people to collaborate with and are eager to help our community grow! So if you want to explore running a tournament, start by checking out our &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fsupercell.com%2Fen%2Ftournament-guidelines%2F')"&gt;Community Tournament Guidelines&lt;/a&gt; and reach out to us by email at tournaments@supercell.com!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;See you in the Arena!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;- The Clash Royale Team
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;b&gt;Apple is not a sponsor of, or responsible for conducting, the promotions or events.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ruQGwvRwrpChmMOS0j0WNRbcMNVdDSdfMnraSbwJ1T8</guid>
      <category>News</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get ready for Clash Royale League 2024: CRL Warmup is back!</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As we get closer to the start of this year&amp;#39;s CRL season (more on the official program coming soon!), it is time to get yourself ready with the CRL Warmup, a competition that will help all players prepare for this new season of competitive Clash Royale!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The CRL Warmup will bring together the best players of the CRL23, along with 10 more players who will have the chance to participate in the Open Qualifiers on &lt;b&gt;February 23rd and 24th.&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The competition will consist of 3 stages:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Stage 1: Open Qualifiers&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There will be a total of 5 Open Qualifiers, with each one being played in a 1000-player in-game tournament. The Top 16 will then move on and play a single-elimination bracket where the Top 2 will automatically qualify for Stage 2.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Friday, February 23rd:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.twitch.tv%2Frevolaimar')"&gt;RevolAimar&lt;/a&gt; at 16:00 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.twitch.tv%2Fjuicyjcr')"&gt;JuicyJ&lt;/a&gt; at 20:00 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Saturday, February 24th:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fchannel%2FUCeByyP8Re3btC3LiH5pnI1w')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Rush&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; at 12:00 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.twitch.tv%2FBigSpinCR')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;BigSpin&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; at 19:00 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2F%40ArtubeClash')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Artube Clash&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; at 23:00 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;To participate in the Qualifiers, make sure to join the Clash Royale Community Events &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FWpB6nAgTvk')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Discord server&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and stay tuned to get notified when the tournament name and passwords are made available! Once you have all the details, head to the “Tournaments” tab in-game and search for the tournament.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Stage 2: Group Stage&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The 10 qualified players from Stage 1 will join 14 of the CRL23 top players on &lt;b&gt;March 2nd, 3rd, 9th, and 10th&lt;/b&gt;, and will be divided into 4 groups of 6 players each. In this phase, they will play a single round-robin, with the Top 4 of each group advancing to the Grand Final.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The CRL23 confirmed players are &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Ftwitter.com%2FPedrotmClash')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;PedroTM&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Ftwitter.com%2FPandoraRa11')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Pandora&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Ftwitter.com%2Fairsurfercr')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Airsurfer&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Ftwitter.com%2FAdrielEduardo11')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Adriel&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Ftwitter.com%2Frubizalez')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Rubén&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Ftwitter.com%2FMohamedLight3')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Mohamed Light&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Ftwitter.com%2Fardentoas191')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Ardentoas&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Ftwitter.com%2FSamuel_Bassotto')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Samuel Bassotto&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Ftwitter.com%2FVitor75u')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Vitor75&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Ftwitter.com%2FWallaceCR_')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Wallace&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Ftwitter.com%2FFaust_cr')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Faust&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Ftwitter.com%2FwoahSosaa')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Sosaa&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Ftwitter.com%2Fmortenroyale')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Morten&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Ftwitter.com%2FTaa_0922')"&gt;Taa&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Stage 3: Final Bracket&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To top it all off, from &lt;b&gt;March 15th to 17th&lt;/b&gt;, the top 16 players from the Group Stage will face each other in a double-elimination for the title of Champion of the CRL Warmup and the biggest share of the prize pool!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A total of $15,000 prize pool will be shared among the top 8 players as follows:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;1st: $7,500&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;2nd: $3,000&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;3rd: $1,500&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;4th: $1,000&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;5th-8th: $500&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Find out more on the CRL Warmup &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fdocs.google.com%2Fdocument%2Fd%2F1-eEido2iSgekm0cjs321eHbPSztwA4UGSAXyPMk7qME%2Fedit')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Rulebook&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FWpB6nAgTvk')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Discord server&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, and make sure to follow &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Ftwitter.com%2FEsportsRoyaleEN')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Esports Royale&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Ftwitter.com%2FRevolAimar')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;RevolAimar&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; to find out all the latest news!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;See you in the Arena,&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Clash Royale Esports&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">DW5aOLa1nbEIKup3j1QAC</guid>
      <category>Esports</category>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 16:01:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clash Royale League is back!</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;CRL is back with another year of the highest level of competitive Clash Royale! &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Following last year&amp;#39;s format, this year will bring you top-tier gameplay with Monthly Qualifiers, Golden Tickets, an in-person event, and MORE!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;a href="https://youtu.be/ysqNjOgLDXs"&gt;📺 [EMBEDDED VIDEO]&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;We are continuing with monthly competitions!&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With the success the monthly competitions had in 2021 and 2023, there was no way we’d let them out! &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Starting in April, the top 1000 players of the Path of Legends will be able to face each other in Monthly Qualifiers until only 8 players remain. The top 8 players will then move to the Monthly Finals, with the winner receiving a Golden Ticket directly to the CRL World Finals!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A total of 5 monthly competitions will be played in-game via the Tournament Hub from April to August. These competitions will award the top players with prize money, hand out Golden Tickets, and distribute CRL competitive points.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Golden Tickets, Competitive Points, and MORE!&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We heard your dream is to set foot on the big stage, along with the best of the best, is that right? If so, here’s how:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Golden Tickets&lt;/b&gt; - By playing in the PoL and placing in the top 1000, you’ll already increase your chances of winning a Golden Ticket, which will be awarded to the Champion of each Monthly Final. A total of 5 Golden Tickets will be awarded this way.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Competitive Points&lt;/b&gt; - If you don’t reach 1st place, you’ll still earn CRL Competitive Points, which will sum up each month in a leaderboard. The player who places first by the end of August will automatically get the 6th Golden Ticket.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;More?&lt;/b&gt; - There are 2 more ways of securing a place at the World Finals. 1 Golden Ticket will be awarded to the champion of the Chinese Tournament, similar to last year. The final Golden Ticket will be awarded to the top player of yet another leaderboard. Wait, one more leaderboard? Yes! This year, 1 spot will be saved for the Community Tournaments. More news on this will be shared soon!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Check out the full monthly season calendar:&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;April&lt;/b&gt;
•	Path of Legends: 04/03 – 01/04
•	Monthly Qualifiers: 6th &amp;amp; 7th
•	Monthly Final: 13th 

&lt;b&gt;May&lt;/b&gt;
•	Path of Legends: 01/04 – 06/05
•	Monthly Qualifiers: 11th &amp;amp; 12th
•	Monthly Final: 18th 

&lt;b&gt;June&lt;/b&gt;
•	Path of Legends: 06/05 – 03/06
•	Monthly Qualifiers: 8th &amp;amp; 9th
•	Monthly Final: 15th 

&lt;b&gt;July&lt;/b&gt;
•	Path of Legends: 03/06 – 01/07
•	Monthly Qualifiers: 6th &amp;amp; 7th
•	Monthly Final: 13th 

&lt;b&gt;August&lt;/b&gt;
•	Path of Legends: 01/07 – 05/08
•	Monthly Qualifiers: 10th &amp;amp; 11th
•	Monthly Final: 17th&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;World Finals!&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With a total of 8 players locked and ready, the Arena is set for the final showdown, which will take place in an in-person event later this year, crowning the #CRL24 World Champion!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://clashroyale.inbox.supercell.com/9jtsgmsiuthj/59AriO6kj5BlOCuDls2nh0/b3b38f2a222dcd28b47dbdea6cf5617e/IMG_2315.jpg?w=1280&amp;h=1280&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To find out more information on the schedule, rulebook, and everything in between, make sure to regularly check the in-game Esports Tab and follow us on &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Ftwitter.com%2FEsportsRoyaleEN')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;X&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.instagram.com%2Fesportsroyale%2F')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Instagram&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; for all the latest Clash Royale Esports news! And in the meantime, maybe you should… warm up?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;See you in the Arena,&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Clash Royale Esports&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ObWCGkj7NsBzRqbuIZLWm</guid>
      <category>Esports</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRL24: Everything you need to know!</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Another year of the highest level of Clash Royale is right around the corner, and here’s all you need to know to take your shot and become the CRL24 World Champion!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;A FIVE-MONTH JOURNEY. 8 GOLDEN TICKETS. 1 WORLD CHAMPION.&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Clash Royale League is more competitive than ever! With five monthly seasons from March until August, you’ll have five chances to win the title of Monthly Champion and a ticket to the CRL24 World Finals. Three more spots will be available through the CRL Leaderboard, the Community Tournaments Leaderboard, and a separate competition within China.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;From PoL to Monthly Champion, let’s go over how you can get there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;START YOUR CLIMB IN THE PATH OF LEGENDS&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The in-game rewards are nice, but let&amp;#39;s move past that! Keep your eyes on that shiny gate, until you reach the prestigious “Ultimate Champion” League. From there, the true climb is ON! Build up your rating and move up the ladder until you see yourself in the Top 1000. If the season ends and your name is listed in there, congratulations, you are in the Monthly Qualifiers!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;FROM 1000 TO 8: MONTHLY QUALIFIERS&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You arrived at the Top 1000 of the Path of Legends, and you see that little icon appear on your main screen. This is the time for you to sign up through the Tournament Hub, which is also where the competition will be played. Put on your best gear and prepare for two intense days of battles in the Royale Arena! Check out how each day will be played:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Day 1: A 1000-player Swiss Bracket until 32 players remain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Day 2: Players will be placed into one of 8 groups of 4 players each. Each player will play everyone in their group twice. The top player from each group will move on to the next stage and complete our lineup of 8 Monthly Finalists.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All battles will be played in the Duels format, with players receiving an invite for a single game. Once that game is over, players must edit their deck and accept the invite for the next battle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;THE MONTHLY FINAL&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, you made it! Welcome to the Monthly Final, where the eight best players from the Monthly Qualifiers will battle it out for the coveted title of Monthly Champion. In this stage, you’ll be placed in a double-elimination bracket, played in the Duels format, lasting 1 Day. Since you are already here, you might as well give it your all! But if you don’t make it to first place, don’t despair, as there are more ways to get your hands on a Golden Ticket!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;WHAT ABOUT THE MONTHLY PRIZE POOL?&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By reaching the Monthly Final, you will already take home a share of the $50,000 prize pool! Check out how the monthly prizing will be distributed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://clashroyale.inbox.supercell.com/9jtsgmsiuthj/7zTmNOeHwPYV8PdFzZe9KV/8c222cb80433bbb208d9903908e7ae07/monthly_prizing_twitter.jpg?w=1920&amp;h=1080&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;GOLDEN TICKETS, COMPETITIVE POINTS, AND COMMUNITY TOURNAMENTS&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Each monthly champion will be awarded a Golden Ticket, meaning they have their place reserved at the World Finals. But you will also be able to earn CRL Competitive Points during the Monthly Qualifiers. Here’s how the points will be distributed:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monthly Qualifier:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Day 1 (Swiss): 5 points per win (up to 55)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Day 2 (Double Round Robin): 5 points per win (up to 30)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monthly Final:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;1st place: 100 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;2nd place: 80 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;3rd place: 65 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;4th place: 50 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;5th-6th: 40 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;7th-8th: 30 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Keep playing and earning those points because if you finish Top 1 of the CRL Leaderboard, you guarantee yourself a Golden Ticket, marking your spot at the World Finals! &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But what is better than one leaderboard? Two leaderboards! This year, you can also get on the CRL World Finals road by playing community tournaments, as there will be a unique Community Leaderboard awarding the player who finishes 1st with a Golden Ticket. The tournament&amp;#39;s awarding points will be announced soon. Until then, check out how the points will be distributed:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;1st place: 100 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;2nd place: 80 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;3rd place: 65 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;4th place: 50 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;5th-6th: 40 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;7th-8th: 30 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;9th-12th: 20 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;13th-16th: 10 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;SUMMING IT ALL UP&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Time to review all the ways and steps to win a Golden Ticket!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monthly Seasons&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Path of Legends: Finish within the Top 1000 to advance&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monthly Qualifiers: Signup in the Tournament Hub &amp;gt; Reach the top 32 of the Swiss Stage &amp;gt; Get 1st place of your group in the Double Round Robin&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monthly Final: Win in an 8-player double-elimination bracket&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;CRL Competitive Leaderboard: Finish 1st place by gathering points in the Monthly Seasons&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Community Leaderboard: Finish 1st place by gathering points in Community Tournaments&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;China tournament: Win the separate China tournament. Only players residing within China will be eligible to participate&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Important: You need to be at least 16 years old to participate in the CRL Monthly Qualifiers. Players must pass fair play checks, participate with clean accounts, and follow good sportsmanship.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://clashroyale.inbox.supercell.com/9jtsgmsiuthj/3JBQ5vdVn4n1GPZTwrzG0M/1836c7e7db97c1f991b7014316d52067/EN_CRL24_Rulebook.jpg?w=1920&amp;h=1080&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can read the full rulebook &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=http%3A%2F%2Fsupr.cl%2FRulebook_CRL24')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;HERE&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;MARK YOUR CALENDAR&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check out the full schedule for the CRL Monthly Qualifiers below.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;April:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Path of Legends: March 4th - April 1st&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monthly Qualifiers: April 6th &amp;amp; 7th&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monthly Final: April 13th&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;May:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Path of Legends: April 1st - May 6th&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monthly Qualifiers: May 11th &amp;amp; 12th&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monthly Final: May 18th&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;June:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Path of Legends: May 6th - June 3rd&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monthly Qualifiers: June 8th &amp;amp; 9th&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monthly Final: June 15th&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;July:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Path of Legends: June 3rd - July 1st&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monthly Qualifiers: July 6th &amp;amp; 7th&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monthly Final: July 13th&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;August:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Path of Legends: July 1st - August 5th&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monthly Qualifiers: August 10th &amp;amp; 11th&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monthly Final: August 17th&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monthly Qualifiers start at 14:00 UTC and you can check-in between 11:30 and 13:30 UTC in the Tournament Hub. Monthly Final starts at 14:00 UTC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As for the World Finals, they will take place in November, and all the information on the dates, location, and other details will be shared at a later date. Stay tuned and make sure to follow Clash Royale Esports on &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Ftwitter.com%2FEsportsRoyaleEN')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;X&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.instagram.com%2Fesportsroyale%2F')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Instagram&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, and visit our &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fesports.clashroyale.com%2F')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Website&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; to get all the latest updates!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;See you in the Arena,&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Clash Royale Esports&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1SpThsB6dBadCBYJhJ114z</guid>
      <category>Esports</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 15:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing the Dragon League by QLASH!</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The QLASH App events reached the next level! We’re excited to present a new event that will accompany the players throughout the entire Clash Royale competitive season!
From fiery Qualifiers to scorching hot Monthly Finals, the format will reward skill and consistency, granting everyone the chance to compete for a share of the $30.000 prize pool and some exclusive &lt;b&gt;Clash Royale League points for this year&amp;#39;s community leaderboard&lt;/b&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Let’s go over the Dragon League and its seasons&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Starting April 1st, the Dragon League will host 5 seasons, with a total of four stages, each leading to the Grand Final, later this year. Get to know each stage:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Path of Dragons&lt;/b&gt; - Players will be able to gather points by playing tournaments and climbing in the &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fqlash.gg%2Fqlash-app-download%2F')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;QLASH App&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; leaderboard. These tournaments will happen twice a day, with the exception of Saturdays and CRL days. The top 96 players qualify for the main tournament. Matches will be played in the In-Game Duels Format.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dragon League Last Chance Qualifiers&lt;/b&gt; - 2 LCQs will be held monthly, qualifying 16 players each for the main tournament. Matches will be played in the In-Game Duels Format.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dragon’s Breath Tournament &lt;/b&gt;- A total of 128 players (96 from the Path of Dragons and 32 from the Dragon League Last Chance Qualifiers) will face each other in a double-elimination bracket, where the top 16 move on to the Monthly Final. Matches will be played in the In-Game Duels Format.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dragon League Monthly Final&lt;/b&gt; - A 16-player double-elimination bracket crowning that month’s champion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The best 3 players of each Monthly Final will have the chance to participate in a Grand Final event later this year! &lt;b&gt;Who will be the Dragon?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://clashroyale.inbox.supercell.com/9jtsgmsiuthj/3DOewbE4t96AE7BXzRx1a/51402180bf31d2091c14c35403270df2/middle_banner_r_recap.jpg?w=1280&amp;h=720&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Dragon League Calendar&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Season 1:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Path of Dragons - From April 1st at 22:00 UTC until April 29th at 22:00 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dragon League Last Chance Qualifiers - April 30th at 12:00 and 17:00 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dragon’s Breath Tournament - May 24th at 14:00 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dragon League Monthly Final - May 25th &amp;amp; 26th at 14:00 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Season 2:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Path of Dragons - From May 1st at 22:00 UTC until May 30th at 22:00 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dragon League Last Chance Qualifiers - May 31st at 12:00 and 17:00 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dragon’s Breath Tournament - June 21st at 14:00 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dragon League Monthly Final - June 22nd &amp;amp; 23rd at 14:00 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Season 3:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Path of Dragons - From June 2nd at 22:00 UTC until June 28th at 22:00 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dragon League Last Chance Qualifiers - June 30th at 12:00 and 17:00 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dragon’s Breath Tournament - July 19th at 14:00 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dragon League Monthly Final - July 20th &amp;amp; 21st at 14:00 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Season 4:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Path of Dragons - From July 1st at 22:00 UTC until July 30th at 22:00 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dragon League Last Chance Qualifiers - July 31st at 12:00 and 17:00 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dragon’s Breath Tournament - August 23rd at 14:00 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dragon League Monthly Final - August 31st &amp;amp; September 1st at 14:00 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Season 5:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Path of Dragons - From August 1st at 22:00 UTC until August 29th at 22:00 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dragon League Last Chance Qualifiers - August 30th at 12:00 and 17:00 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dragon’s Breath Tournament - September (TBD)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dragon League Monthly Final - September (TBD)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Grand Finals:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;TBD - Stay tuned as more info will be shared at a later date!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;How to participate&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You will be able to play the Dragon League by registering in the &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fqlash.gg%2Fqlash-app-download%2F')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;QLASH App&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For more information on the rules, check out the rules section of each tournament on the QLASH App and the &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fdrive.google.com%2Ffile%2Fd%2F16E_GJeskxwvHvWluKqEQV0PwggcDtCww%2Fview%3Fusp%3Dsharing')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Rulebook&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Prize Pool Distribution&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the Dragon League, you will be able to get prize money both by placing high on the monthly Path of Dragons Leaderboard and by reaching the Monthly Final! Check out how the monthly prize pool will be distributed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Path Of Dragons:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;1st place: 100$&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;2nd place: 85$&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;3rd place: 70$&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;4th place: 50$&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;5th place: 35$&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;6th place: 25$&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;7th place: 20$&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;8th place: 10$&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dragon League Monthly Final:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;1st place: 1300$&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;2nd place: 700$&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;3rd place: 500$&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;4th place: 400$&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;5th-6th places: 125$&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;7th-8th places: 75$&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;9th-12th places: 50$&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;13th-16th places: 25$&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;CRL Community Leaderboard&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Dragon League is one of the competitions where you will be able to participate and still be on the road headed to the Clash Royale League World Finals! By playing in the Monthly Seasons and reaching the Monthly Finals, you will be gathering points that will count for the CRL Community Tournaments Leaderboard, which will award a Golden Ticket to the player who finishes first place when all the selected tournaments end. There is a lot at stake, as the higher you place on the Dragon League monthly seasons, the higher the amount of points and the chances of you getting your hands on the Golden Ticket!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;1st place: 100 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;2nd place: 80 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;3rd place: 65 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;4th place: 50 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;5th-6th places: 40 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;7th-8th places: 30 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;9th-12th places: 20 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;13th-16th places: 10 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Make sure to follow QLASH on &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Ftwitter.com%2FQLASH_App')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;X&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.instagram.com%2Fqlash_clashroyale%2F')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Instagram&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and join the &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2Fqlash-clashroyale')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;QLASH Discord Server&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and Clash Royale Esports on &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Ftwitter.com%2FEsportsRoyaleEN')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;X&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.instagram.com%2Fesportsroyale%2F')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Instagram&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; to get the latest updates!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;See you in the Arena,&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Clash Royale Esports&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5EEc6J208rarbCYyMIU3Bq</guid>
      <category>Esports</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 16:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compete in the Calalas Cup 2024!</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Calalas Cup 2024 is a brand-new competition, giving players the chance to compete for the 15,000€ prize pool and earn points for the CRL24 Community Leaderboard!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;From April 19th to May 5th, the Calalas Cup will be open for everyone to compete in and will be divided into three phases.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://clashroyale.inbox.supercell.com/9jtsgmsiuthj/5xz70zUmaOC1xykysRnPXT/10ac3e78135cc707c251463c81a82d1e/CALALAS_CUP_format_1920X1080_copy.png?w=1920&amp;h=1080&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Phase 1: Open Qualifiers&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There will be a total of 8 open qualifiers, each being played in a 1000-player in-game tournament. The Top 16 will then move on and play a single-elimination bracket where the Top 4 automatically qualify for Phase 2 of the tournament.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Friday, April 19th:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2F%40RichSlaton')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;RichSlaton&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; at 13:00 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.twitch.tv%2Frevolaimar')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;RevolAimar&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; at 17:00 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=http%3A%2F%2Fyoutube.com%2F%40artubeclash')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Artube Clash&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; at 23:00 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Saturday, April 20th:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=http%3A%2F%2Fyoutube.com%2F%40AllanFranzotti')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;AllanFranzotti&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; at 15:00 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.twitch.tv%2Fbigspincr')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Bigspin&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; at 16:30 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sunday, April 21st:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2F%40Rush_Clash%2F')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Rush&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; at 12:00 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.twitch.tv%2Fbale_gg')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Bale&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; at 14:00 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.twitch.tv%2Fsurgicalgoblin')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;SurgicalGoblin&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; at 17:00 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Make sure to join the Clash Royale Community Events &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FWpB6nAgTvk')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Discord server&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, and stay tuned to get notified when the tournament name and passwords are made available! Once you have all the details, head to the “Tournaments” tab in-game and search for the tournament.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For more information on the rules, check out the Calalas Cup 2024 &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fdocs.google.com%2Fdocument%2Fd%2F1exDZb5-IMjdT9OAp8QU13Fk8aPlK3QiWgfdnje7DSrs%2Fedit%3Fusp%3Dsharing')"&gt;Rulebook&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Phase 2: Group Stage&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;From April 25th to the 28th, the 32 qualified players will be divided into 4 groups of 8 players each, competing in a single round-robin format, with the top 4 from each group advancing to the final bracket.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Phase 3: Final Bracket&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With the final 16 all set, from May 3rd to the 5th, a double-elimination bracket will be played, awarding the winner with the title of Champion and the biggest share of the prize pool!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A total of 15,000€ in prizes will be distributed amongst the top 8 players, which will be divided as follows:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;1st: 7,500€&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;2nd: 3,000€&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;3rd: 1,500€&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;4th: 1,000€&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;5th-8th: 500€&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;In addition to a title and prize money, with the Calalas Cup being one of the Community Tournaments awarding points for the CRL Community Leaderboard, everyone getting to the top 16 will be able to gain valuable points for the CRL Community Leaderboard. The player with the most points is guaranteed a spot in the CRL24 World Finals! &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These are the points the top16 players of the Calalas Cup will be awarded:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;1st place: 100 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;2nd place: 80 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;3rd place: 65 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;4th place: 50 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;5th-6th places: 40 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;7th-8th places: 30 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;9th-12th places: 20 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;13th-16th places: 10 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To stay updated on all the news, follow Calalas Cup on &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.instagram.com%2Fcalalascup%2F')"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Ftwitter.com%2Fcalalascup')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;X&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, and Clash Royale Esports on &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.instagram.com%2Fesportsroyale%2F')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Instagram&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Ftwitter.com%2FEsportsRoyaleEN')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;X&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;See you in the Arena,&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Clash Royale Esports&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">75zQTOoJUAF7VaVWH8o1Z</guid>
      <category>Esports</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 16:22:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRL Community Tournaments: Everything you need to know!</title>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://clashroyale.inbox.supercell.com/9jtsgmsiuthj/66OTyFgBx6sAxAY51LMtmy/db1d4ee5d9cbc3bcb71cb92b11029961/CRL_-_Community_Tournaments_AYNTK_Generic.png?w=1920&amp;h=1080&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The 2024 Clash Royale League year is underway, and it’s time we do a deep dive into this year’s CRL Community Tournaments and the CRL Community Points Leaderboard. Let’s get right into it!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As you might already know, there 8 ways to earn a Golden Ticket in #CRL24…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Winning one of the five CRL Monthly Finals &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Being the highest-placing Player on the CRL Points Leaderboard after the conclusion of the August Monthly Final&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Winning the China Regional Tournament&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;And last, but not least, being the highest-placing Player on the CRL Community Points Leaderboard&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The CRL Community Leaderboard tracks points that players earn in officially sanctioned community-organized tournaments. There will be a total of four community-organized tournaments during the #CRL24 year:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dragon League by QLASH&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Calalas cup&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;LPL Clash Royale World Tour 2024&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;GKR 2024 Solo&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Let’s learn a bit more about these Community Tournaments…&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dragon League by QLASH&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dragon League by QLASH is a 5-season competition, running from April through September. Each season will award Community Leaderboard points to players who make it to the final “Phase” of each season. Each season will consist of three Phases, and the tournament format for each season is as follows:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Phase 1&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ladder Tournament, followed by…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;2 Last Chance Qualifiers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Phase 2&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;A 128-player Double Elimination Bracket&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Phase 3&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;16-player Double Elimination Bracket (awarding CRL Community Points)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can learn more about the Dragon League by QLASH &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fesports.clashroyale.com%2Fnews%2Fintroducing-the-dragon-league-by-qlash')"&gt;HERE&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Calalas Cup&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Calalas Cup is a 3-Phase tournament running from 19 April through 5 May. Players that advance to the third Phase will be awarded CRL Community Points. The tournament format is as follows:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Phase 1&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;In-game Qualifiers: 19 April - 21 April&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Phase 2&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;24-player Group Stage tournament: 25 April - 28 April&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Phase 3&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;16-player Final Bracket: 3 May - 5 May (awarding CRL Community Points)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can learn more about the Calalas Cup &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fesports.clashroyale.com%2Fnews%2Fcompete-in-the-calalas-cup-2024')"&gt;HERE&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;LPL Clash Royale World Tour 2024&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;LPL World Tour 2024 is a 2-season competition: Season 1 runs from 23 May to 23 June, and Season 2 runs from 18 July to 25 August. Each Season will have two Phases: Qualifiers &amp;amp; Finals, and the following regions will be allowed to participate: NA, LATAM, EU, MENA, JP, SK, OCE &amp;amp; SEA. The tournament format is as follows:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Season 1:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Qualifiers: 23 May - 26 May&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Top 2 players from the Qualifiers for each region will head to the Finals&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Finals: 20 June - 23 June&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;16-player Final Bracket (awarding CRL Community Points)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Season 2:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Qualifiers: 18 July - 21 July&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Top 2 players from the Qualifiers for each region will head to the Finals&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Finals: 22 August - 25 August&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;16-player Final Bracket (awarding CRL Community Points)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;GKR 2024 Solo:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;GKR 2024 Solo is a 3-Phase tournament running from 22 July through 4 August. The tournament format is as follows…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Phase 1&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Qualifiers: 22 July - 29 July&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Phase 2&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;64-player Swiss Tournament: 30 July - 31 July&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Phase 3&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;16-player Double Elimination bracket: 1 August - 4 August (awarding CRL Community Points)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://clashroyale.inbox.supercell.com/9jtsgmsiuthj/2gzZqSaTFkniY562MNQBfy/9b7ba3bc0b6c5e115f764a30ff10173b/CRL_-_Community_Tournaments_Points_Leaderboard.png?w=1920&amp;h=1080&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;CRL Community Points Leaderboard&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See above for the CRL Community Points Leaderboard. This Leaderboard will be updated after the end of each Tournament (GKR 2024 Solo &amp;amp; Calalas Cup), or after the end of each Tournament’s Season (Dragon League by QLASH &amp;amp; LPL Clash Royale World Tour 2024).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As you may have noticed, the final Phase of each of the four CRL Community Tournaments culminates in a 16-player showdown, and the CRL Community Points Leaderboard shows a total of 16 slots. This is because the Top 16 finishers in each Community Tournament will be awarded points towards the CRL Community Leaderboard - the player with the highest placement, and thus, the most Points after the 4 Community Tournaments end, will earn themselves a Golden Ticket and a spot at the #CRL24 World Finals! See the Points breakdown for the Top 16 tournament finishers below:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;1st Place&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;100 Points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;2nd Place&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;80 Points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;3rd Place&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;65 Points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;4th Place&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;50 Points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;5th &amp;amp; 6th Place&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;40 Points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;7th &amp;amp; 8th Place&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;30 Points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;9th - 12th Place&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;20 Points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;13th - 16th Place&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;10 Points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Frequently Asked Questions&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What happens if a tie occurs between multiple players on the Community Points Leaderboard after the final Community Tournament ends?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;There will be a total of 3 tiebreakers in the case two or more players have the same amount of Community Points. Check out how the winner of the Golden Ticket will be determined below:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tiebreaker 1: Player with the most total number of Community Tournament wins&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tiebreaker 2: Player with the most CRL Points (on the CRL Points Leaderboard)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tiebreaker 3: Player with the highest average placement in all Path of Legends Race Seasons&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Can a player win a Golden Ticket via the CRL Community Points Leaderboard if they have already won a Golden Ticket?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;No. A player can only receive a Golden Ticket via the CRL Community Points Leaderboard if they have not already received a Golden ticket via a Monthly Finals or the CRL Points Leaderboard. If the player with the highest-placement on the Community Points Leaderboard has already received a Golden Ticket, the Golden Ticket will be awarded to the player with the next highest-placement&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;
And you are all set!! Visit this article throughout the #CRL24 to know more on the CRL Community Tournaments and Leaderboard, and check out the 2024 Clash Royale League &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=http%3A%2F%2Fsupr.cl%2FRulebook_CRL24')"&gt;Ruleset&lt;/a&gt; for more information. Stay tuned and make sure to follow Clash Royale Esports on &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=http%3A%2F%2Ftwitter.com%2FesportsroyaleEN')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;X&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=http%3A%2F%2Finstagram.com%2Fesportsroyale')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Instagram&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, and visit our &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=http%3A%2F%2Fesports.clashroyale.com')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Website&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; to get all the latest updates!
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;See you in the Arena,&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Clash Royale Esports&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5vjQcEyTV1NVu8lu59bWM8</guid>
      <category>Esports</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
