<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Clashroyale - Esport News</title>
    <link>https://github.com/skrwo/supercell-inbox-rss/</link>
    <description>RSS wrapper of Clashroyale inbox Esport News</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 17:31:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>What's coming for CR Esports!</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the World of Clash Royale Esports! &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here, you’ll find the most relevant information about the competitive scene, what tournaments are coming up and past tournament information. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This article will be frequently updated. Make sure to come back so you don’t miss anything!
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Upcoming tournaments&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Get your decks ready, and don’t forget to sign up! Check out the upcoming tournaments here as they are announced.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;LPL Clash Royale World Tour 2024&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;LPL World Tour 2024 will be a 2-season competition. Each Season will consist of a Qualifiers stage and a 16-player final bracket awarding CRL community points.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;More info coming soon!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;GKR 2024 Solo&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;GKR 2024 Solo will be a 3-Phase tournament running from 22 July through 4 August. The last phase will be a 16-player final bracket awarding CRL community points.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;More info coming soon!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Ongoing tournaments&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Want to watch the world’s best players in action? Here’s where you will be able to find the ongoing tournaments supported by us! 

&lt;b&gt;Clash Royale League 2024&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;CRL is back with another year of the highest level of competitive Clash Royale! Following last year&amp;#39;s format, 2024 brings you top-tier gameplay with Monthly Qualifiers, Golden Tickets, an in-person event, and more!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Format: &lt;/b&gt;Starting in April, the top 1000 players of the Path of Legends will be able to face each other in Monthly Qualifiers until only 8 players remain. The top 8 players will then move to the Monthly Finals, with the winner receiving a Golden Ticket directly to the CRL World Finals. A total of 5 monthly competitions will be played in-game via the Tournament Hub from April to August. The top player of the CRL24 Leaderboard, a player from China, and the top player from the Community Tournaments Leaderboard will join the 5 players that qualified through the Monthly Qualifiers. At the World Finals, these 8 players will go head to head for the title of World Champion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Participation criteria: &lt;/b&gt;You need to be 16 years old or older to participate in the CRL Monthly Qualifiers. Players must pass the fair play check, participate with clean accounts, and follow good sportsmanship.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dragon League by QLASH&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The QLASH App events reached the next level! We’re excited to present a new event that will accompany the players throughout the entire Clash Royale competitive season!
From fiery Qualifiers to scorching hot Monthly Finals, the format will reward skill and consistency, granting everyone the chance to compete for a share of the $30.000 prize pool and some exclusive Clash Royale League points for this year&amp;#39;s community leaderboard!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Format: &lt;/b&gt;Starting April 1st, the Dragon League will host 5 seasons, with a total of four stages, each leading to the Grand Final, later this year. Starting in the Path of Dragon, players will be able to play daily tournaments to gather points to the Dragon League Leaderboard. By placing in the top 96, these players along with 16 players from 2 Last Chance Qualifiers, will qualify for the Dragon&amp;#39;s Breath Tournament, a 128 double-elimination bracket where the top 16 players move on to the Dragon League Monthly Final, playing a 16-player double-elimination bracket, which will also award points for the CRL community leaderboard. The best 3 players of each Monthly Final will have the chance to participate in a Grand Final event later this year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Participation criteria: &lt;/b&gt;You need to be 16 years old or older to participate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Past tournaments&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Below you’ll find some of the past tournaments where players battled for prize money, trophies, and glory!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;CRL Warmup 2024&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;CRL Warmup brought together 14 of the CRL23 top players along with 10 players from 5 Qualifiers! The competition consisted of 3 stages: Open Qualifiers, a Double Round-Robin Group Stage, and a Double-elimination Final Bracket.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Format and rules&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fdocs.google.com%2Fdocument%2Fd%2F1-eEido2iSgekm0cjs321eHbPSztwA4UGSAXyPMk7qME%2Fedit')"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Participation &lt;/b&gt;is free and open to 16-year-old+ players. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Calalas Cup 2024&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Calalas Cup 2024 was a brand-new competition, giving players the chance to compete for the 15,000€ prize pool and earn points for the CRL24 Community Leaderboard!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Format:&lt;/b&gt; From April 19th to May 5th, the Calalas Cup was open for everyone to compete in and was divided into three phases. In phase 1 players were able to play 8 1000-player in-game qualifiers, with the top 4 players from each qualifier advancing to phase 2, the Group Stage. From there, the 32 qualified players were divided into 4 groups of 8 players competing in a single round-robin format, with the top 4 from each group advancing to the final phase, a 16-player bracket, awarding points for the CRL Community Leaderboard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Participation criteria: &lt;/b&gt;You need to be 16 years old or older to participate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are always looking for people to collaborate with and are eager to help our community grow! So if you want to explore running a tournament, start by checking out our &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fsupercell.com%2Fen%2Ftournament-guidelines%2F')"&gt;Community Tournament Guidelines&lt;/a&gt; and reach out to us by email at tournaments@supercell.com!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;See you in the Arena!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;- The Clash Royale Team
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;b&gt;Apple is not a sponsor of, or responsible for conducting, the promotions or events.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ruQGwvRwrpChmMOS0j0WNRbcMNVdDSdfMnraSbwJ1T8</guid>
      <category>News</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRL24: Everything you need to know!</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Another year of the highest level of Clash Royale is right around the corner, and here’s all you need to know to take your shot and become the CRL24 World Champion!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;A FIVE-MONTH JOURNEY. 8 GOLDEN TICKETS. 1 WORLD CHAMPION.&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Clash Royale League is more competitive than ever! With five monthly seasons from March until August, you’ll have five chances to win the title of Monthly Champion and a ticket to the CRL24 World Finals. Three more spots will be available through the CRL Leaderboard, the Community Tournaments Leaderboard, and a separate competition within China.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;From PoL to Monthly Champion, let’s go over how you can get there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;START YOUR CLIMB IN THE PATH OF LEGENDS&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The in-game rewards are nice, but let&amp;#39;s move past that! Keep your eyes on that shiny gate, until you reach the prestigious “Ultimate Champion” League. From there, the true climb is ON! Build up your rating and move up the ladder until you see yourself in the Top 1000. If the season ends and your name is listed in there, congratulations, you are in the Monthly Qualifiers!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;FROM 1000 TO 8: MONTHLY QUALIFIERS&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You arrived at the Top 1000 of the Path of Legends, and you see that little icon appear on your main screen. This is the time for you to sign up through the Tournament Hub, which is also where the competition will be played. Put on your best gear and prepare for two intense days of battles in the Royale Arena! Check out how each day will be played:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Day 1: A 1000-player Swiss Bracket until 32 players remain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Day 2: Players will be placed into one of 8 groups of 4 players each. Each player will play everyone in their group twice. The top player from each group will move on to the next stage and complete our lineup of 8 Monthly Finalists.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All battles will be played in the Duels format, with players receiving an invite for a single game. Once that game is over, players must edit their deck and accept the invite for the next battle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;THE MONTHLY FINAL&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, you made it! Welcome to the Monthly Final, where the eight best players from the Monthly Qualifiers will battle it out for the coveted title of Monthly Champion. In this stage, you’ll be placed in a double-elimination bracket, played in the Duels format, lasting 1 Day. Since you are already here, you might as well give it your all! But if you don’t make it to first place, don’t despair, as there are more ways to get your hands on a Golden Ticket!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;WHAT ABOUT THE MONTHLY PRIZE POOL?&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By reaching the Monthly Final, you will already take home a share of the $50,000 prize pool! Check out how the monthly prizing will be distributed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://clashroyale.inbox.supercell.com/9jtsgmsiuthj/7zTmNOeHwPYV8PdFzZe9KV/8c222cb80433bbb208d9903908e7ae07/monthly_prizing_twitter.jpg?w=1920&amp;h=1080&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;GOLDEN TICKETS, COMPETITIVE POINTS, AND COMMUNITY TOURNAMENTS&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Each monthly champion will be awarded a Golden Ticket, meaning they have their place reserved at the World Finals. But you will also be able to earn CRL Competitive Points during the Monthly Qualifiers. Here’s how the points will be distributed:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monthly Qualifier:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Day 1 (Swiss): 5 points per win (up to 55)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Day 2 (Double Round Robin): 5 points per win (up to 30)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monthly Final:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;1st place: 100 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;2nd place: 80 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;3rd place: 65 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;4th place: 50 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;5th-6th: 40 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;7th-8th: 30 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Keep playing and earning those points because if you finish Top 1 of the CRL Leaderboard, you guarantee yourself a Golden Ticket, marking your spot at the World Finals! &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But what is better than one leaderboard? Two leaderboards! This year, you can also get on the CRL World Finals road by playing community tournaments, as there will be a unique Community Leaderboard awarding the player who finishes 1st with a Golden Ticket. The tournament&amp;#39;s awarding points will be announced soon. Until then, check out how the points will be distributed:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;1st place: 100 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;2nd place: 80 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;3rd place: 65 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;4th place: 50 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;5th-6th: 40 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;7th-8th: 30 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;9th-12th: 20 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;13th-16th: 10 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;SUMMING IT ALL UP&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Time to review all the ways and steps to win a Golden Ticket!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monthly Seasons&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Path of Legends: Finish within the Top 1000 to advance&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monthly Qualifiers: Signup in the Tournament Hub &amp;gt; Reach the top 32 of the Swiss Stage &amp;gt; Get 1st place of your group in the Double Round Robin&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monthly Final: Win in an 8-player double-elimination bracket&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;CRL Competitive Leaderboard: Finish 1st place by gathering points in the Monthly Seasons&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Community Leaderboard: Finish 1st place by gathering points in Community Tournaments&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;China tournament: Win the separate China tournament. Only players residing within China will be eligible to participate&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Important: You need to be at least 16 years old to participate in the CRL Monthly Qualifiers. Players must pass fair play checks, participate with clean accounts, and follow good sportsmanship.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://clashroyale.inbox.supercell.com/9jtsgmsiuthj/3JBQ5vdVn4n1GPZTwrzG0M/1836c7e7db97c1f991b7014316d52067/EN_CRL24_Rulebook.jpg?w=1920&amp;h=1080&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can read the full rulebook &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=http%3A%2F%2Fsupr.cl%2FRulebook_CRL24')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;HERE&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;MARK YOUR CALENDAR&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check out the full schedule for the CRL Monthly Qualifiers below.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;April:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Path of Legends: March 4th - April 1st&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monthly Qualifiers: April 6th &amp;amp; 7th&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monthly Final: April 13th&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;May:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Path of Legends: April 1st - May 6th&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monthly Qualifiers: May 11th &amp;amp; 12th&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monthly Final: May 18th&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;June:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Path of Legends: May 6th - June 3rd&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monthly Qualifiers: June 8th &amp;amp; 9th&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monthly Final: June 15th&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;July:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Path of Legends: June 3rd - July 1st&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monthly Qualifiers: July 6th &amp;amp; 7th&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monthly Final: July 13th&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;August:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Path of Legends: July 1st - August 5th&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monthly Qualifiers: August 10th &amp;amp; 11th&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monthly Final: August 17th&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monthly Qualifiers start at 14:00 UTC and you can check-in between 11:30 and 13:30 UTC in the Tournament Hub. Monthly Final starts at 14:00 UTC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As for the World Finals, they will take place in November, and all the information on the dates, location, and other details will be shared at a later date. Stay tuned and make sure to follow Clash Royale Esports on &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Ftwitter.com%2FEsportsRoyaleEN')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;X&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.instagram.com%2Fesportsroyale%2F')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Instagram&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, and visit our &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fesports.clashroyale.com%2F')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Website&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; to get all the latest updates!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;See you in the Arena,&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Clash Royale Esports&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1SpThsB6dBadCBYJhJ114z</guid>
      <category>Esports</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 15:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing the Dragon League by QLASH!</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The QLASH App events reached the next level! We’re excited to present a new event that will accompany the players throughout the entire Clash Royale competitive season!
From fiery Qualifiers to scorching hot Monthly Finals, the format will reward skill and consistency, granting everyone the chance to compete for a share of the $30.000 prize pool and some exclusive &lt;b&gt;Clash Royale League points for this year&amp;#39;s community leaderboard&lt;/b&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Let’s go over the Dragon League and its seasons&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Starting April 1st, the Dragon League will host 5 seasons, with a total of four stages, each leading to the Grand Final, later this year. Get to know each stage:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Path of Dragons&lt;/b&gt; - Players will be able to gather points by playing tournaments and climbing in the &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fqlash.gg%2Fqlash-app-download%2F')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;QLASH App&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; leaderboard. These tournaments will happen twice a day, with the exception of Saturdays and CRL days. The top 96 players qualify for the main tournament. Matches will be played in the In-Game Duels Format.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dragon League Last Chance Qualifiers&lt;/b&gt; - 2 LCQs will be held monthly, qualifying 16 players each for the main tournament. Matches will be played in the In-Game Duels Format.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dragon’s Breath Tournament &lt;/b&gt;- A total of 128 players (96 from the Path of Dragons and 32 from the Dragon League Last Chance Qualifiers) will face each other in a double-elimination bracket, where the top 16 move on to the Monthly Final. Matches will be played in the In-Game Duels Format.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dragon League Monthly Final&lt;/b&gt; - A 16-player double-elimination bracket crowning that month’s champion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The best 3 players of each Monthly Final will have the chance to participate in a Grand Final event later this year! &lt;b&gt;Who will be the Dragon?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://clashroyale.inbox.supercell.com/9jtsgmsiuthj/3DOewbE4t96AE7BXzRx1a/51402180bf31d2091c14c35403270df2/middle_banner_r_recap.jpg?w=1280&amp;h=720&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Dragon League Calendar&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Season 1:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Path of Dragons - From April 1st at 22:00 UTC until April 29th at 22:00 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dragon League Last Chance Qualifiers - April 30th at 12:00 and 17:00 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dragon’s Breath Tournament - May 24th at 14:00 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dragon League Monthly Final - May 25th &amp;amp; 26th at 14:00 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Season 2:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Path of Dragons - From May 1st at 22:00 UTC until May 30th at 22:00 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dragon League Last Chance Qualifiers - May 31st at 12:00 and 17:00 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dragon’s Breath Tournament - June 21st at 14:00 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dragon League Monthly Final - June 22nd &amp;amp; 23rd at 14:00 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Season 3:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Path of Dragons - From June 2nd at 22:00 UTC until June 28th at 22:00 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dragon League Last Chance Qualifiers - June 30th at 12:00 and 17:00 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dragon’s Breath Tournament - July 19th at 14:00 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dragon League Monthly Final - July 20th &amp;amp; 21st at 14:00 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Season 4:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Path of Dragons - From July 1st at 22:00 UTC until July 30th at 22:00 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dragon League Last Chance Qualifiers - July 31st at 12:00 and 17:00 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dragon’s Breath Tournament - August 23rd at 14:00 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dragon League Monthly Final - August 31st &amp;amp; September 1st at 14:00 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Season 5:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Path of Dragons - From August 1st at 22:00 UTC until August 29th at 22:00 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dragon League Last Chance Qualifiers - August 30th at 12:00 and 17:00 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dragon’s Breath Tournament - September (TBD)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dragon League Monthly Final - September (TBD)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Grand Finals:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;TBD - Stay tuned as more info will be shared at a later date!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;How to participate&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You will be able to play the Dragon League by registering in the &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fqlash.gg%2Fqlash-app-download%2F')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;QLASH App&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For more information on the rules, check out the rules section of each tournament on the QLASH App and the &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fdrive.google.com%2Ffile%2Fd%2F16E_GJeskxwvHvWluKqEQV0PwggcDtCww%2Fview%3Fusp%3Dsharing')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Rulebook&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Prize Pool Distribution&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the Dragon League, you will be able to get prize money both by placing high on the monthly Path of Dragons Leaderboard and by reaching the Monthly Final! Check out how the monthly prize pool will be distributed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Path Of Dragons:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;1st place: 100$&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;2nd place: 85$&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;3rd place: 70$&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;4th place: 50$&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;5th place: 35$&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;6th place: 25$&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;7th place: 20$&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;8th place: 10$&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dragon League Monthly Final:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;1st place: 1300$&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;2nd place: 700$&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;3rd place: 500$&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;4th place: 400$&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;5th-6th places: 125$&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;7th-8th places: 75$&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;9th-12th places: 50$&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;13th-16th places: 25$&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;CRL Community Leaderboard&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Dragon League is one of the competitions where you will be able to participate and still be on the road headed to the Clash Royale League World Finals! By playing in the Monthly Seasons and reaching the Monthly Finals, you will be gathering points that will count for the CRL Community Tournaments Leaderboard, which will award a Golden Ticket to the player who finishes first place when all the selected tournaments end. There is a lot at stake, as the higher you place on the Dragon League monthly seasons, the higher the amount of points and the chances of you getting your hands on the Golden Ticket!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;1st place: 100 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;2nd place: 80 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;3rd place: 65 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;4th place: 50 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;5th-6th places: 40 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;7th-8th places: 30 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;9th-12th places: 20 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;13th-16th places: 10 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Make sure to follow QLASH on &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Ftwitter.com%2FQLASH_App')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;X&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.instagram.com%2Fqlash_clashroyale%2F')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Instagram&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and join the &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2Fqlash-clashroyale')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;QLASH Discord Server&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and Clash Royale Esports on &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Ftwitter.com%2FEsportsRoyaleEN')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;X&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.instagram.com%2Fesportsroyale%2F')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Instagram&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; to get the latest updates!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;See you in the Arena,&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Clash Royale Esports&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5EEc6J208rarbCYyMIU3Bq</guid>
      <category>Esports</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 16:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRL Community Tournaments: Everything you need to know!</title>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://clashroyale.inbox.supercell.com/9jtsgmsiuthj/66OTyFgBx6sAxAY51LMtmy/db1d4ee5d9cbc3bcb71cb92b11029961/CRL_-_Community_Tournaments_AYNTK_Generic.png?w=1920&amp;h=1080&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The 2024 Clash Royale League year is underway, and it’s time we do a deep dive into this year’s CRL Community Tournaments and the CRL Community Points Leaderboard. Let’s get right into it!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As you might already know, there 8 ways to earn a Golden Ticket in #CRL24…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Winning one of the five CRL Monthly Finals &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Being the highest-placing Player on the CRL Points Leaderboard after the conclusion of the August Monthly Final&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Winning the China Regional Tournament&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;And last, but not least, being the highest-placing Player on the CRL Community Points Leaderboard&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The CRL Community Leaderboard tracks points that players earn in officially sanctioned community-organized tournaments. There will be a total of four community-organized tournaments during the #CRL24 year:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dragon League by QLASH&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Calalas cup&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;LPL Clash Royale World Tour 2024&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;GKR 2024 Solo&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Let’s learn a bit more about these Community Tournaments…&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dragon League by QLASH&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dragon League by QLASH is a 5-season competition, running from April through September. Each season will award Community Leaderboard points to players who make it to the final “Phase” of each season. Each season will consist of three Phases, and the tournament format for each season is as follows:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Phase 1&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ladder Tournament, followed by…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;2 Last Chance Qualifiers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Phase 2&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;A 128-player Double Elimination Bracket&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Phase 3&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;16-player Double Elimination Bracket (awarding CRL Community Points)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can learn more about the Dragon League by QLASH &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fesports.clashroyale.com%2Fnews%2Fintroducing-the-dragon-league-by-qlash')"&gt;HERE&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Calalas Cup&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Calalas Cup is a 3-Phase tournament running from 19 April through 5 May. Players that advance to the third Phase will be awarded CRL Community Points. The tournament format is as follows:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Phase 1&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;In-game Qualifiers: 19 April - 21 April&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Phase 2&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;24-player Group Stage tournament: 25 April - 28 April&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Phase 3&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;16-player Final Bracket: 3 May - 5 May (awarding CRL Community Points)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can learn more about the Calalas Cup &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fesports.clashroyale.com%2Fnews%2Fcompete-in-the-calalas-cup-2024')"&gt;HERE&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;LPL Clash Royale World Tour 2024&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;LPL World Tour 2024 is a 2-season competition, with each Season having two Phases: Qualifiers &amp;amp; Finals. The tournament will be as follows:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Season 1:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Qualifiers: Dates to be confirmed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Finals: Dates to be confirmed (16-player Final Bracket, awarding CRL Community Points)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Season 2:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Qualifiers: Dates to be confirmed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Finals: Dates to be confirmed (16-player Final Bracket, awarding CRL Community Points)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;GKR 2024 Solo:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;GKR 2024 Solo is a 3-Phase tournament running from 22 July through 4 August. The tournament format is as follows…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Phase 1&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Qualifiers: 22 July - 29 July&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Phase 2&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;64-player Swiss Tournament: 30 July - 31 July&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Phase 3&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;16-player Double Elimination bracket: 1 August - 4 August (awarding CRL Community Points)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://clashroyale.inbox.supercell.com/9jtsgmsiuthj/1hNrcnrDXbjcYiOsRmYr4y/00b3b3da7606f6314e68f8be48b00c70/CRL_-_Community_Tournaments_Points_Leaderboard_2.jpg?w=1920&amp;h=1080&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;CRL Community Points Leaderboard&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See above for the CRL Community Points Leaderboard. This Leaderboard will be updated after the end of each Tournament (GKR 2024 Solo &amp;amp; Calalas Cup), or after the end of each Tournament’s Season (Dragon League by QLASH &amp;amp; LPL Clash Royale World Tour 2024).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As you may have noticed, the final Phase of each of the four CRL Community Tournaments culminates in a 16-player showdown, and the CRL Community Points Leaderboard shows a total of 16 slots. This is because the Top 16 finishers in each Community Tournament will be awarded points towards the CRL Community Leaderboard - the player with the highest placement, and thus, the most Points after the 4 Community Tournaments end, will earn themselves a Golden Ticket and a spot at the #CRL24 World Finals! See the Points breakdown for the Top 16 tournament finishers below:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;1st Place&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;100 Points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;2nd Place&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;80 Points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;3rd Place&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;65 Points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;4th Place&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;50 Points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;5th &amp;amp; 6th Place&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;40 Points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;7th &amp;amp; 8th Place&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;30 Points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;9th - 12th Place&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;20 Points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;13th - 16th Place&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;10 Points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Frequently Asked Questions&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What happens if a tie occurs between multiple players on the Community Points Leaderboard after the final Community Tournament ends?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;There will be a total of 3 tiebreakers in the case two or more players have the same amount of Community Points. Check out how the winner of the Golden Ticket will be determined below:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tiebreaker 1: Player with the most total number of Community Tournament wins&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tiebreaker 2: Player with the most CRL Points (on the CRL Points Leaderboard)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tiebreaker 3: Player with the highest average placement in all Path of Legends Race Seasons&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Can a player win a Golden Ticket via the CRL Community Points Leaderboard if they have already won a Golden Ticket?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;No. A player can only receive a Golden Ticket via the CRL Community Points Leaderboard if they have not already received a Golden ticket via a Monthly Finals or the CRL Points Leaderboard. If the player with the highest-placement on the Community Points Leaderboard has already received a Golden Ticket, the Golden Ticket will be awarded to the player with the next highest-placement&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;
And you are all set!! Visit this article throughout the #CRL24 to know more on the CRL Community Tournaments and Leaderboard, and check out the 2024 Clash Royale League &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=http%3A%2F%2Fsupr.cl%2FRulebook_CRL24')"&gt;Ruleset&lt;/a&gt; for more information. Stay tuned and make sure to follow Clash Royale Esports on &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=http%3A%2F%2Ftwitter.com%2FesportsroyaleEN')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;X&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=http%3A%2F%2Finstagram.com%2Fesportsroyale')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Instagram&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, and visit our &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=http%3A%2F%2Fesports.clashroyale.com')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Website&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; to get all the latest updates!
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;See you in the Arena,&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Clash Royale Esports&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5vjQcEyTV1NVu8lu59bWM8</guid>
      <category>Esports</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRL24 June Monthly Finals!</title>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://clashroyale.inbox.supercell.com/9jtsgmsiuthj/4gQPSZ0YkZGzMGObKcdznt/24c0913a1df7104b9dbe5b5ee7ef0a02/CRL_-_June_MF_Tournament_Article.png?w=1920&amp;h=1080&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;The Clash Royale League June Monthly Finals is this Saturday!&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Two Golden Tickets of #CRL24 have already been awarded - &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fx.com%2FMohamedLightCr1')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Mohamed Light&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; started the year off by claiming the first Golden Ticket in April, followed by &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fx.com%2FTaa_0922')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Taa&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; securing the second in May! We’ve got six more to award, with the third one being awarded this weekend with the June Monthly Finals!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://clashroyale.inbox.supercell.com/9jtsgmsiuthj/3fqPAT96fFWIn0e6uicg0t/1279882c4733028a154aced0aab36143/CRL_-_June_Golden_Ticket_Infographic_16x9.png?w=1920&amp;h=1080&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let’s take a closer look at the upcoming June Monthly Finals…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;The Road to the Golden Ticket&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It all started with the June Path of Legends Race - millions of players battled it out for just under one month, climbing the Ladder leaderboard until we found the top 1000. Then came the June Monthly Qualifier - a two-day tournament consisting of a Swiss Stage and a Group Stage, where those top 1000 players competed until only 8 players remained. And now, these 8 players are advancing to the June Monthly Finals, a one-day, double-elimination bracket tournament where everything is on the line. They will fight for the largest-share of the $50,000 prize pool and a shot at a #CRL24 Golden Ticket! &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;The June Monthly Finals will take place on June 15, starting at 14:00 UTC - mark your calendars and set a reminder, you’re not going to want to miss this!&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let’s take a look at this month’s competitors…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://clashroyale.inbox.supercell.com/9jtsgmsiuthj/y4aHij44hPVURzQ4F0Nw9/13311c11c7e9dfe6d14b86208840359b/CRL_-_June_MF_Starting_Bracket_16x9.png?w=1920&amp;h=1080&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;The Competitors&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take a look at the 8 players who will be competing in the June Monthly Finals and show your support to who you want to see crowned champion!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fx.com%2FMohamedLightCr1')"&gt;Mohamed Light&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fx.com%2FRyIey42')"&gt;Ryley&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fx.com%2FPedrotmcr')"&gt;CAL Pedro&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fx.com%2Flucasxgamercr')"&gt;CAL Lucas&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fx.com%2FAdrielEduardo11')"&gt;Adriel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fx.com%2FEgwCr')"&gt;EGW&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fx.com%2FTaa_0922')"&gt;Taa&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fx.com%2FSubTm_CR')"&gt;CAL Sub&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mohamed Light, CAL Pedro, Adriel &amp;amp; Taa are returning from previous Monthly Finals, while CAL Lucas, Ryley, EGW &amp;amp; CAL Sub are joining a #CRL24 Monthly Finals for the first time!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Where to Watch&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The best place to watch the official broadcast of the June Monthly Finals is the &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fevent.supercell.com%2Fclashroyale%2Fen%2F%3F%3Dpfg')"&gt;Clash Royale Event Site&lt;/a&gt;! On the Event Site, you can choose between 8 different languages to watch - English, Spanish, Portuguese, French, Italian, German, Japanese and Korean! But that’s not all! By linking your Supercell ID, you can earn in-game rewards by making predictions and watching the match action live! Choose your language and check out the Event Site below…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fevent.supercell.com%2Fclashroyale%2Fen%3Fpfg%3Dtrue')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;English&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fevent.supercell.com%2Fclashroyale%2Fes%3Fpfg%3Dtrue')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Spanish&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fevent.supercell.com%2Fclashroyale%2Fpt%3Fpfg%3Dtrue')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Portuguese&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fevent.supercell.com%2Fclashroyale%2Fde%3Fpfg%3Dtrue')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;German&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fevent.supercell.com%2Fclashroyale%2Fit%3Fpfg%3Dtrue')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Italian&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fevent.supercell.com%2Fclashroyale%2Ffr%3Fpfg%3Dtrue')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;French&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fevent.supercell.com%2Fclashroyale%2Fjp%3Fpfg%3Dtrue')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Japanese&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fevent.supercell.com%2Fclashroyale%2Fkr%3Fpfg%3Dtrue')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Korean&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;And that’s it!! Set a reminder, grab your popcorn, and lock in for the third #CRL24 Monthly Finals! Check out the &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fcrl-rules.scescdn.com%2F2024-en-v1')"&gt;2024 Clash Royale League ruleset&lt;/a&gt; for more information. Stay tuned and make sure to follow &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fx.com%2FEsportsRoyaleEN')"&gt;Clash Royale Esports on X&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.instagram.com%2Fesportsroyale')"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;, and visit our &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fesports.clashroyale.com%2F')"&gt;Website&lt;/a&gt; to get all the latest updates!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
See you in the Arena,&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Clash Royale Esports&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7zL1OIcbzkE41IiCRuA1hW</guid>
      <category>Esports</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 16:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
