<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>clashroyale-esportNewsEntries-en</id>
  <title>Clashroyale - Esport News</title>
  <updated>2025-02-26T17:33:35.939460+00:00</updated>
  <link href="https://github.com/skrwo/supercell-inbox-rss/"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="1.0.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <subtitle>RSS wrapper of Clashroyale inbox Esport News</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>ruQGwvRwrpChmMOS0j0WNRbcMNVdDSdfMnraSbwJ1T8</id>
    <title>What's coming for CR Esports!</title>
    <updated>2025-02-17T15:48:58.374000+00:00</updated>
    <content>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the World of Clash Royale Esports! &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here, you’ll find the most relevant information about the competitive scene, what tournaments are coming up and past tournament information. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This article will be frequently updated. Make sure to come back so you don’t miss anything!
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Upcoming tournaments&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Get your decks ready, and don’t forget to sign up! Check out the upcoming tournaments here as they are announced.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Ongoing tournaments&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Want to watch the world’s best players in action? Here’s where you will be able to find the ongoing tournaments supported by us! &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Past tournaments&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Below you’ll find some of the past tournaments where players battled for prize money, trophies, and glory!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;CRL Warmup 2024&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;CRL Warmup brought together 14 of the CRL23 top players along with 10 players from 5 Qualifiers! The competition consisted of 3 stages: Open Qualifiers, a Double Round-Robin Group Stage, and a Double-elimination Final Bracket.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Format and rules&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fdocs.google.com%2Fdocument%2Fd%2F1-eEido2iSgekm0cjs321eHbPSztwA4UGSAXyPMk7qME%2Fedit')"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Participation &lt;/b&gt;is free and open to 16-year-old+ players. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Calalas Cup 2024&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Calalas Cup 2024 was a brand-new competition, giving players the chance to compete for the 15,000€ prize pool and earn points for the CRL24 Community Leaderboard!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Format:&lt;/b&gt; From April 19th to May 5th, the Calalas Cup was open for everyone to compete in and was divided into three phases. In phase 1 players were able to play 8 1000-player in-game qualifiers, with the top 4 players from each qualifier advancing to phase 2, the Group Stage. From there, the 32 qualified players were divided into 4 groups of 8 players competing in a single round-robin format, with the top 4 from each group advancing to the final phase, a 16-player bracket, awarding points for the CRL Community Leaderboard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Participation criteria: &lt;/b&gt;You need to be 16 years old or older to participate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;GKR 2024 Solo&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;GKR 2024 brought a new individual format that was part of the CRL Community Tournaments Leaderboard, where players have the opportunity to accumulate points, with the player that finishes first winning the coveted Golden Ticket to the CRL24 World Finals!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Format&lt;/b&gt;: From July 22nd to the 29th, 16 open qualifiers were held, organized via the QLASH Community App, where the top 4 players from each qualifier moved on to phase 2, a 2-day event featuring a swiss bracket for each day, where the top 32 players from day 1 played a new swiss bracket until we got our top 16. The final phase was a 16-player double-elimination bracket awarding CRL community points and a share of the $16,625 prize pool&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Participation criteria: &lt;/b&gt;You need to be 16 years old or older to participate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;LPL Clash Royale World Tour 2024&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;LPL World Tour 2024 was a 2-season competition contributing to the CRL Community Leaderboard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Format&lt;/b&gt;: Each Season consisted of a Qualifier stage and 2 separate Finals, the Pro Division where the top 4 players from each qualifier played in a 16-player double-elimination bracket awarding CRL community points and a share of the $11,500 prize pool, and the Open Division, where the players that didn&amp;#39;t reach the top 4 of the qualifiers played for a share of the $1,000 prize pool.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Participation criteria: &lt;/b&gt;You need to be 16 years old or older to participate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dragon League by QLASH&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The QLASH App events reached the next level! We presented a new event that accompanied the players throughout the entire Clash Royale competitive season!
From fiery Qualifiers to scorching hot Monthly Finals, the format reward skill and consistency, granting everyone the chance to compete for a share of the $30,000 prize pool and some exclusive Clash Royale League points for the community leaderboard!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Format: &lt;/b&gt;Starting April 1st, the Dragon League hosted 5 seasons, with a total of four stages, each leading to the Grand Final, later in the year. Starting in the Path of Dragon, players were able to play daily tournaments to gather points to the Dragon League Leaderboard. By placing in the top 96, these players along with 16 players from 2 Last Chance Qualifiers, qualified for the Dragon&amp;#39;s Breath Tournament, a 128 double-elimination bracket where the top 16 players moved on to the Dragon League Monthly Final, playing a 16-player double-elimination bracket, which also awarded points for the CRL community leaderboard. The best 3 players of each Monthly Final had the chance to participate in a Grand Final event later in the year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Participation criteria: &lt;/b&gt;You need to be 16 years old or older to participate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;BLAST Royale 2024&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Blast Royale was an invite-only online tournament for Clash Royale where top players from around the globe went head-to-head to claim the title of ultimate champion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Format:&lt;/b&gt; On October 12 and 13, the 8 invited players played in a crew battle format, getting divided into 2 teams of 4, with each team having a total of 16 lives. The winning crew was then placed in the upper bracket, while the loser team was placed in the lower bracket, determining our starting bracket this way. In this phase, players were no longer in teams and played against each other in a double-elimination bracket.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Clash Royale League 2024&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;CRL was back with another year of the highest level of competitive Clash Royale! Following 2023&amp;#39;s format, 2024 brought you top-tier gameplay with Monthly Qualifiers, Golden Tickets, an in-person event, and more!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Format: &lt;/b&gt;Starting in April, the top 1000 players of the Path of Legends were able to face each other in Monthly Qualifiers until only 8 players remained. The top 8 players then moved to the Monthly Finals, with the winner receiving a Golden Ticket directly to the CRL World Finals. A total of 5 monthly competitions were played in-game via the Tournament Hub from April to August. The top player of the CRL24 Leaderboard, a player from China, and the top player from the Community Tournaments Leaderboard joined the 5 players that qualified through the Monthly Qualifiers. At the World Finals, these 8 players went head to head for the title of World Champion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mohamed Light won it all and is the 2024 Clash Royale League World Champion!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Participation criteria: &lt;/b&gt;You need to be 16 years old or older to participate in the CRL Monthly Qualifiers. Players must pass the fair play check, participate with clean accounts, and follow good sportsmanship.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are always looking for people to collaborate with and are eager to help our community grow! So if you want to explore running a tournament, start by checking out our &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fsupercell.com%2Fen%2Ftournament-guidelines%2F')"&gt;Community Tournament Guidelines&lt;/a&gt; and reach out to us by email at tournaments@supercell.com!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;See you in the Arena!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;- The Clash Royale Team
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Apple is not a sponsor of, or responsible for conducting the promotions or events.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <category term="News"/>
    <published>2023-01-23T14:00:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>3B7f1DVQbxudiUtOVt87ya</id>
    <title>The 2024 World Finals are coming!</title>
    <updated>2025-02-26T15:07:23.236000+00:00</updated>
    <content>&lt;img src="https://clashroyale.inbox.supercell.com/9jtsgmsiuthj/7FjX6N80BuXw1Uyj7GGwwo/948737c77f16b614aa41fa414a6a0c30/CRL_-_World_Finals_AYNTK.png?w=1920&amp;h=1080&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The 2024 Clash Royale League year has been a wild ride so far, and all 8 Golden Tickets have been awarded! The top Clash Royale competitors in the world have been battling it out throughout Monthly Competitions and Community tournaments to cement their spot at World Finals - and they haven’t disappointed! And now, it all comes down to one final showdown to see who the best player in the world is!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Let’s take a closer look at the tournament format...&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The 2024 World Finals is a double-elimination bracket tournament, similar to this year’s Monthly Finals, taking place over three days: November 1 - 3. It will take place at SuperFEST, and will occur between the Clash of Clans World Championship Finals and the Brawl Stars Championship Finals on all 3 days. All three competition days will start at 14:00 EET and have a maximum of 5 matches on each day - make sure to take a look at the updated &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fcrl-rules.scescdn.com%2F2024-en')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;World Finals Ruleset&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and visit the &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fesports.clashroyale.com%2Fnews%2Fsuperfest-24')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;SuperFEST Article&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; to take a closer look at the SuperFEST schedule!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;The Road to World Finals&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Throughout the 2024 year, 8 Golden Tickets were up for grabs, signifying 8 available spots at World Finals: 5 Golden Tickets from the Monthly Finals tournaments, 1 Golden Ticket from the China Regional Tournament, 1 Golden Ticket from the CRL Points Leaderboard, and 1 Golden Ticket from the Community Leaderboard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s been a wild and tight race to claim these Golden Tickets, but also without surprises in some areas! In the April, May and June Monthly Finals, Mohamed Light was dominant and took the top spot in all three competitions! He claimed the April Golden Ticket, with Taa and Pedro, the May and June runner-ups. Then the July Monthly Finals came along, and Lucas was able to knock Mohamed Light off of his pedestal! Lucas defeated Mohamed Light in the Grand Finals to end his Monthly Finals win streak and claim the fourth Golden Ticket of the year! In the last Monthly Finals of the year, the August Monthly Finals, two more Golden Tickets were claimed: Guriko claimed the August Monthly Finals, while CAL Sub secured enough points on the CRL Points Leaderboard to claim his Golden Ticket as well! In the China Regional Tournament, the Clash Royale League veteran LCIOP claimed his Golden Ticket and on the Community Tournaments Leaderboard, Ryley took the top spot with a margin of just 20 points!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With all 8 players locked in for the World Finals, it’s time to take a closer look at who will be competing…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://clashroyale.inbox.supercell.com/9jtsgmsiuthj/3RLyZCegSNo81dPY727Lp5/e58a0dfc5ac8968666b8753d009b8d2e/CRL_-_Golden_Ticket_Infographic_16x9.png?w=1920&amp;h=1080&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;The Competitors&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take a look at the 8 players who will be competing at the 2024 World Finals and show your support to who you want to see crowned World champion!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fx.com%2FMohamedLightCr1')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Mohamed Light &lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fx.com%2FTaa_0922')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Taa&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fx.com%2FPedrotmcr')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Pedro&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fx.com%2Flucasxgamercr')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Lucas&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fx.com%2FAksms_')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Guriko&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fx.com%2FSubTm_CR')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Sub&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fx.com%2FRyIey42')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Ryley&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fx.com%2FLciopCRCN')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;LCIOP&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;But that’s not all! Check out the starting bracket to see how they will stack up against each other in the first round!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://clashroyale.inbox.supercell.com/9jtsgmsiuthj/1g5ZEw2uC60bc30Xg2R6R0/f8577c3de8f98f6e6a4f673923842f9a/CRL_-_World_Finals_Bracket_16x9.png?w=1920&amp;h=1080&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Prize Pool&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let’s not forget about the $! The 2024 World Finals is the biggest competition of the year, and the prize pool reflects that - with $500,000 on the line, this is going to be an event to remember! Take a look at the prizing breakdown in the graphic below…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://clashroyale.inbox.supercell.com/9jtsgmsiuthj/Ul54KNzdBWYsBPF3v09VY/d6733393308f1eb2f016a8ae5a2e99a1/CRL_-_World_Finals_Prize_Pool_16x9.png?w=1920&amp;h=1080&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Where to Watch&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The best place to watch the official broadcast of the World Finals is the &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fevent.supercell.com%2Fclashroyale%2Fen%2F%3Fpfg%3Dtrue')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Clash Royale Event Site&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;! On the Event Site, you can choose between 8 different languages to watch - English, Spanish, Portuguese, French, Italian, German, Japanese and Korean! But that’s not all! By linking your Supercell ID, you can earn in-game rewards by making predictions and watching the match action live! Choose your language and check out the Event Site below…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fevent.supercell.com%2Fclashroyale%2Fen%2F%3Fpfg%3Dtrue')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;English&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fevent.supercell.com%2Fclashroyale%2Fes%2F%3Fpfg%3Dtrue')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Spanish&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fevent.supercell.com%2Fclashroyale%2Fpt%2F%3Fpfg%3Dtrue')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Portuguese&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fevent.supercell.com%2Fclashroyale%2Fde%2F%3Fpfg%3Dtrue')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;German&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fevent.supercell.com%2Fclashroyale%2Fit%2F%3Fpfg%3Dtrue')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Italian&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fevent.supercell.com%2Fclashroyale%2Ffr%2F%3Fpfg%3Dtrue')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;French&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fevent.supercell.com%2Fclashroyale%2Fjp%2F%3Fpfg%3Dtrue')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Japanese&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fevent.supercell.com%2Fclashroyale%2Fkr%2F%3Fpfg%3Dtrue')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Korean&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;And that’s it! Set a reminder, grab your popcorn, and lock in for the finale of #CRL24! Stay tuned and make sure to follow &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fx.com%2FEsportsRoyaleEN')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Clash Royale Esports on X&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.instagram.com%2Fesportsroyale%2F%3Fhl%3Den')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Instagram&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, and visit our &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fesports.clashroyale.com%2F')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Website&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; to get all the latest updates!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;See you in the Arena,&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Clash Royale Esports&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <category term="Esports"/>
    <published>2024-10-01T14:11:37+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>4w4jL8GIX03tVHAiHNi1OG</id>
    <title>CONGRATULATIONS TO THE 2024 WORLD CHAMPION - MOHAMED LIGHT!</title>
    <updated>2025-02-26T15:06:12.565000+00:00</updated>
    <content>&lt;img src="https://clashroyale.inbox.supercell.com/9jtsgmsiuthj/2JocE53Jh8jeeCH2jxrXOO/ebd2bd9008ddb2ffe0d922738493433f/CRL_-_WF_Champion_Article_16x9.png?w=1920&amp;h=1080&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The #CRL24 year has been a wild ride - Five monthly competitions, multiple Community Tournaments, epic showdowns on the CRL &amp;amp; Community points leaderboards, and a China Qualifier, all led to the World Finals at SuperFest! And now, after three days of the highest-level competitive Clash Royale action…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;The 2024 Clash Royale League World Champion has been crowned!&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;img src="https://clashroyale.inbox.supercell.com/9jtsgmsiuthj/3DETCFtgbcsRXS4NDnmfaV/c012ebf4b726450bd975eacd83fa8c90/CRL_SFEST_-_Champion_TW.png?w=1920&amp;h=1080&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fx.com%2FMohamedLightCr1')"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Mohamed Light&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; has been DOMINANT throughout the 2024 year! In his first three Monthly Finals appearances, he took the top spot, claiming his Golden Ticket and a spot at World Finals in April and retaining his top spot for three months straight! He continued to be a top contender throughout the year - whether it be his second place finishes in the July and August Monthly Finals, first place finishes in the multiple Dragon League and LPL World Tour 2024 Seasons, or securing the top spots on the #CRL24 Points &amp;amp; Community Leaderboards, Mohamed Light was unstoppable!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And then we arrived at the 2024 Clash Royale League World Finals! After dropping only a single game to LCIOP in the first round, he went on to go undefeated against OS Lucas and Ryley in the upper bracket to claim the World Finals trophy. With an impressive record of eight wins and only one loss over three days, there is only one player who deserves the title of WORLD CHAMPION!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://clashroyale.inbox.supercell.com/9jtsgmsiuthj/36O5S5zarlxLyAuXsVJle0/5f068c1737eb5e9ebd1408729d24cd03/CRL_SFEST_-_Bracket__3_.png?w=1920&amp;h=1080&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Mohamed Light has claimed the World Finals trophy and largest share of the $500,000 prize pool!&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;img src="https://clashroyale.inbox.supercell.com/9jtsgmsiuthj/2ztjzp91ysAOBHc5cULxnA/c5bde8d795878fac568c3b56798fc5ce/CRL_-_WF_Prizing_16x9.png?w=1920&amp;h=1080&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rewatch the epic three-day showdown of Mohamed Light’s road to World Champion!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/live/QO45r5CzEXI?si=l6ZPJaJ09tInLmFG&amp;t=1286"&gt;📺 [EMBEDDED VIDEO]&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/live/-vWwOc69c_c?si=oT6IJ1c4f6sqXh8z&amp;t=875"&gt;📺 [EMBEDDED VIDEO]&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/live/Sa0QOSJ5AVY?si=BV_BY-S_OOW7zXJ4&amp;t=1288"&gt;📺 [EMBEDDED VIDEO]&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A HUGE thank you and congratulations to all players who competed throughout the #CRL24 year - and, of course, to the fans who have been following their journeys as well! The conclusion of the World Finals at SuperFest wraps up the year! Stay tuned to the Clash Royale in-game Esports tab, &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fx.com%2FEsportsRoyaleEN')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Clash Royale Esports on X&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.instagram.com%2Fesportsroyale%2F%3Fhl%3Den')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Instagram&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fesports.clashroyale.com%2F')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Website&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; to learn more about future plans and to make sure you&amp;#39;re up-to-date on everything #CRL related!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;See you in the Arena,&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Clash Royale Esports&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <category term="Esports"/>
    <published>2024-11-03T15:00:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
