<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Clashroyale - Esport News</title>
    <link>https://github.com/skrwo/supercell-inbox-rss/</link>
    <description>RSS wrapper of Clashroyale inbox Esport News</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>id</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 05:36:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>What's coming for CR Esports!</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the World of Clash Royale Esports! &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here, you’ll find the most relevant information about the competitive scene, what tournaments are coming up and past tournament information. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This article will be frequently updated. Make sure to come back so you don’t miss anything!
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Upcoming tournaments&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Get your decks ready, and don’t forget to sign up! Check out the upcoming tournaments here as they are announced.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Ongoing tournaments&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Want to watch the world’s best players in action? Here’s where you will be able to find the ongoing tournaments supported by us! &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Past tournaments&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Below you’ll find some of the past tournaments where players battled for prize money, trophies, and glory!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;CRL Warmup 2024&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;CRL Warmup brought together 14 of the CRL23 top players along with 10 players from 5 Qualifiers! The competition consisted of 3 stages: Open Qualifiers, a Double Round-Robin Group Stage, and a Double-elimination Final Bracket.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Format and rules&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fdocs.google.com%2Fdocument%2Fd%2F1-eEido2iSgekm0cjs321eHbPSztwA4UGSAXyPMk7qME%2Fedit')"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Participation &lt;/b&gt;is free and open to 16-year-old+ players. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Calalas Cup 2024&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Calalas Cup 2024 was a brand-new competition, giving players the chance to compete for the 15,000€ prize pool and earn points for the CRL24 Community Leaderboard!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Format:&lt;/b&gt; From April 19th to May 5th, the Calalas Cup was open for everyone to compete in and was divided into three phases. In phase 1 players were able to play 8 1000-player in-game qualifiers, with the top 4 players from each qualifier advancing to phase 2, the Group Stage. From there, the 32 qualified players were divided into 4 groups of 8 players competing in a single round-robin format, with the top 4 from each group advancing to the final phase, a 16-player bracket, awarding points for the CRL Community Leaderboard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Participation criteria: &lt;/b&gt;You need to be 16 years old or older to participate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;GKR 2024 Solo&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;GKR 2024 brought a new individual format that was part of the CRL Community Tournaments Leaderboard, where players have the opportunity to accumulate points, with the player that finishes first winning the coveted Golden Ticket to the CRL24 World Finals!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Format&lt;/b&gt;: From July 22nd to the 29th, 16 open qualifiers were held, organized via the QLASH Community App, where the top 4 players from each qualifier moved on to phase 2, a 2-day event featuring a swiss bracket for each day, where the top 32 players from day 1 played a new swiss bracket until we got our top 16. The final phase was a 16-player double-elimination bracket awarding CRL community points and a share of the $16,625 prize pool&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Participation criteria: &lt;/b&gt;You need to be 16 years old or older to participate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;LPL Clash Royale World Tour 2024&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;LPL World Tour 2024 was a 2-season competition contributing to the CRL Community Leaderboard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Format&lt;/b&gt;: Each Season consisted of a Qualifier stage and 2 separate Finals, the Pro Division where the top 4 players from each qualifier played in a 16-player double-elimination bracket awarding CRL community points and a share of the $11,500 prize pool, and the Open Division, where the players that didn&amp;#39;t reach the top 4 of the qualifiers played for a share of the $1,000 prize pool.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Participation criteria: &lt;/b&gt;You need to be 16 years old or older to participate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dragon League by QLASH&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The QLASH App events reached the next level! We presented a new event that accompanied the players throughout the entire Clash Royale competitive season!
From fiery Qualifiers to scorching hot Monthly Finals, the format reward skill and consistency, granting everyone the chance to compete for a share of the $30,000 prize pool and some exclusive Clash Royale League points for the community leaderboard!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Format: &lt;/b&gt;Starting April 1st, the Dragon League hosted 5 seasons, with a total of four stages, each leading to the Grand Final, later in the year. Starting in the Path of Dragon, players were able to play daily tournaments to gather points to the Dragon League Leaderboard. By placing in the top 96, these players along with 16 players from 2 Last Chance Qualifiers, qualified for the Dragon&amp;#39;s Breath Tournament, a 128 double-elimination bracket where the top 16 players moved on to the Dragon League Monthly Final, playing a 16-player double-elimination bracket, which also awarded points for the CRL community leaderboard. The best 3 players of each Monthly Final had the chance to participate in a Grand Final event later in the year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Participation criteria: &lt;/b&gt;You need to be 16 years old or older to participate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;BLAST Royale 2024&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Blast Royale was an invite-only online tournament for Clash Royale where top players from around the globe went head-to-head to claim the title of ultimate champion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Format:&lt;/b&gt; On October 12 and 13, the 8 invited players played in a crew battle format, getting divided into 2 teams of 4, with each team having a total of 16 lives. The winning crew was then placed in the upper bracket, while the loser team was placed in the lower bracket, determining our starting bracket this way. In this phase, players were no longer in teams and played against each other in a double-elimination bracket.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Clash Royale League 2024&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;CRL was back with another year of the highest level of competitive Clash Royale! Following 2023&amp;#39;s format, 2024 brought you top-tier gameplay with Monthly Qualifiers, Golden Tickets, an in-person event, and more!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Format: &lt;/b&gt;Starting in April, the top 1000 players of the Path of Legends were able to face each other in Monthly Qualifiers until only 8 players remained. The top 8 players then moved to the Monthly Finals, with the winner receiving a Golden Ticket directly to the CRL World Finals. A total of 5 monthly competitions were played in-game via the Tournament Hub from April to August. The top player of the CRL24 Leaderboard, a player from China, and the top player from the Community Tournaments Leaderboard joined the 5 players that qualified through the Monthly Qualifiers. At the World Finals, these 8 players went head to head for the title of World Champion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mohamed Light won it all and is the 2024 Clash Royale League World Champion!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Participation criteria: &lt;/b&gt;You need to be 16 years old or older to participate in the CRL Monthly Qualifiers. Players must pass the fair play check, participate with clean accounts, and follow good sportsmanship.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are always looking for people to collaborate with and are eager to help our community grow! So if you want to explore running a tournament, start by checking out our &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fsupercell.com%2Fen%2Ftournament-guidelines%2F')"&gt;Community Tournament Guidelines&lt;/a&gt; and reach out to us by email at tournaments@supercell.com!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;See you in the Arena!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;- The Clash Royale Team
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Apple is not a sponsor of, or responsible for conducting the promotions or events.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ruQGwvRwrpChmMOS0j0WNRbcMNVdDSdfMnraSbwJ1T8</guid>
      <category>News</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRL24: Everything you need to know!</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Another year of the highest level of Clash Royale is right around the corner, and here’s all you need to know to take your shot and become the CRL24 World Champion!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;A FIVE-MONTH JOURNEY. 8 GOLDEN TICKETS. 1 WORLD CHAMPION.&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Clash Royale League is more competitive than ever! With five monthly seasons from March until August, you’ll have five chances to win the title of Monthly Champion and a ticket to the CRL24 World Finals. Three more spots will be available through the CRL Leaderboard, the Community Tournaments Leaderboard, and a separate competition within China.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;From PoL to Monthly Champion, let’s go over how you can get there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;START YOUR CLIMB IN THE PATH OF LEGENDS&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The in-game rewards are nice, but let&amp;#39;s move past that! Keep your eyes on that shiny gate, until you reach the prestigious “Ultimate Champion” League. From there, the true climb is ON! Build up your rating and move up the ladder until you see yourself in the Top 1000. If the season ends and your name is listed in there, congratulations, you are in the Monthly Qualifiers!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;FROM 1000 TO 8: MONTHLY QUALIFIERS&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You arrived at the Top 1000 of the Path of Legends, and you see that little icon appear on your main screen. This is the time for you to sign up through the Tournament Hub, which is also where the competition will be played. Put on your best gear and prepare for two intense days of battles in the Royale Arena! Check out how each day will be played:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Day 1: A 1000-player Swiss Bracket until 32 players remain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Day 2: Players will be placed into one of 8 groups of 4 players each. Each player will play everyone in their group twice. The top player from each group will move on to the next stage and complete our lineup of 8 Monthly Finalists.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All battles will be played in the Duels format, with players receiving an invite for a single game. Once that game is over, players must edit their deck and accept the invite for the next battle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;THE MONTHLY FINAL&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, you made it! Welcome to the Monthly Final, where the eight best players from the Monthly Qualifiers will battle it out for the coveted title of Monthly Champion. In this stage, you’ll be placed in a double-elimination bracket, played in the Duels format, lasting 1 Day. Since you are already here, you might as well give it your all! But if you don’t make it to first place, don’t despair, as there are more ways to get your hands on a Golden Ticket!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;WHAT ABOUT THE MONTHLY PRIZE POOL?&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By reaching the Monthly Final, you will already take home a share of the $50,000 prize pool! Check out how the monthly prizing will be distributed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://clashroyale.inbox.supercell.com/9jtsgmsiuthj/7zTmNOeHwPYV8PdFzZe9KV/8c222cb80433bbb208d9903908e7ae07/monthly_prizing_twitter.jpg?w=1920&amp;h=1080&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;GOLDEN TICKETS, COMPETITIVE POINTS, AND COMMUNITY TOURNAMENTS&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Each monthly champion will be awarded a Golden Ticket, meaning they have their place reserved at the World Finals. But you will also be able to earn CRL Competitive Points during the Monthly Qualifiers. Here’s how the points will be distributed:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monthly Qualifier:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Day 1 (Swiss): 5 points per win (up to 55)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Day 2 (Double Round Robin): 5 points per win (up to 30)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monthly Final:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;1st place: 100 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;2nd place: 80 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;3rd place: 65 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;4th place: 50 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;5th-6th: 40 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;7th-8th: 30 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Keep playing and earning those points because if you finish Top 1 of the CRL Leaderboard, you guarantee yourself a Golden Ticket, marking your spot at the World Finals! &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But what is better than one leaderboard? Two leaderboards! This year, you can also get on the CRL World Finals road by playing community tournaments, as there will be a unique Community Leaderboard awarding the player who finishes 1st with a Golden Ticket. The tournament&amp;#39;s awarding points will be announced soon. Until then, check out how the points will be distributed:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;1st place: 100 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;2nd place: 80 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;3rd place: 65 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;4th place: 50 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;5th-6th: 40 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;7th-8th: 30 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;9th-12th: 20 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;13th-16th: 10 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;SUMMING IT ALL UP&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Time to review all the ways and steps to win a Golden Ticket!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monthly Seasons&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Path of Legends: Finish within the Top 1000 to advance&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monthly Qualifiers: Signup in the Tournament Hub &amp;gt; Reach the top 32 of the Swiss Stage &amp;gt; Get 1st place of your group in the Double Round Robin&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monthly Final: Win in an 8-player double-elimination bracket&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;CRL Competitive Leaderboard: Finish 1st place by gathering points in the Monthly Seasons&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Community Leaderboard: Finish 1st place by gathering points in Community Tournaments&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;China tournament: Win the separate China tournament. Only players residing within China will be eligible to participate&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Important: You need to be at least 16 years old to participate in the CRL Monthly Qualifiers. Players must pass fair play checks, participate with clean accounts, and follow good sportsmanship.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://clashroyale.inbox.supercell.com/9jtsgmsiuthj/3JBQ5vdVn4n1GPZTwrzG0M/1836c7e7db97c1f991b7014316d52067/EN_CRL24_Rulebook.jpg?w=1920&amp;h=1080&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can read the full rulebook &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fcrl-rules.scescdn.com%2F2024-en')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;HERE&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;MARK YOUR CALENDAR&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check out the full schedule for the CRL Monthly Qualifiers below.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;April:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Path of Legends: March 4th - April 1st&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monthly Qualifiers: April 6th &amp;amp; 7th&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monthly Final: April 13th&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;May:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Path of Legends: April 1st - May 6th&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monthly Qualifiers: May 11th &amp;amp; 12th&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monthly Final: May 18th&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;June:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Path of Legends: May 6th - June 3rd&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monthly Qualifiers: June 8th &amp;amp; 9th&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monthly Final: June 15th&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;July:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Path of Legends: June 3rd - July 1st&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monthly Qualifiers: July 6th &amp;amp; 7th&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monthly Final: July 13th&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;August:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Path of Legends: July 1st - August 5th&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monthly Qualifiers: August 10th &amp;amp; 11th&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monthly Final: August 17th&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monthly Qualifiers start at 14:00 UTC and you can check-in between 11:30 and 13:30 UTC in the Tournament Hub. Monthly Final starts at 14:00 UTC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As for the World Finals, they will take place in November, and all the information on the dates, location, and other details will be shared at a later date. Stay tuned and make sure to follow Clash Royale Esports on &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Ftwitter.com%2FEsportsRoyaleEN')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;X&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.instagram.com%2Fesportsroyale%2F')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Instagram&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, and visit our &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fesports.clashroyale.com%2F')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Website&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; to get all the latest updates!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;See you in the Arena,&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Clash Royale Esports&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1SpThsB6dBadCBYJhJ114z</guid>
      <category>Esports</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 15:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRL Community Tournaments: Everything you need to know!</title>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://clashroyale.inbox.supercell.com/9jtsgmsiuthj/66OTyFgBx6sAxAY51LMtmy/db1d4ee5d9cbc3bcb71cb92b11029961/CRL_-_Community_Tournaments_AYNTK_Generic.png?w=1920&amp;h=1080&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The 2024 Clash Royale League year is underway, and it’s time we do a deep dive into this year’s CRL Community Tournaments and the CRL Community Points Leaderboard. Let’s get right into it!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As you might already know, there 8 ways to earn a Golden Ticket in #CRL24…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Winning one of the five CRL Monthly Finals &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Being the highest-placing Player on the CRL Points Leaderboard after the conclusion of the August Monthly Final&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Winning the China Regional Tournament&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;And last, but not least, being the highest-placing Player on the CRL Community Points Leaderboard&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The CRL Community Leaderboard tracks points that players earn in officially sanctioned community-organized tournaments. There will be a total of four community-organized tournaments during the #CRL24 year:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dragon League by QLASH&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Calalas cup&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;LPL Clash Royale World Tour 2024&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;GKR 2024 Solo&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Let’s learn a bit more about these Community Tournaments…&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dragon League by QLASH&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dragon League by QLASH is a 5-season competition, running from April through September. Each season will award Community Leaderboard points to players who make it to the final “Phase” of each season. Each season will consist of three Phases, and the tournament format for each season is as follows:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Phase 1&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ladder Tournament, followed by…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;2 Last Chance Qualifiers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Phase 2&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;A 128-player Double Elimination Bracket&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Phase 3&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;16-player Double Elimination Bracket (awarding CRL Community Points)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can learn more about the Dragon League by QLASH &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fesports.clashroyale.com%2Fnews%2Fintroducing-the-dragon-league-by-qlash')"&gt;HERE&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Calalas Cup&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Calalas Cup is a 3-Phase tournament running from 19 April through 5 May. Players that advance to the third Phase will be awarded CRL Community Points. The tournament format is as follows:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Phase 1&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;In-game Qualifiers: 19 April - 21 April&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Phase 2&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;24-player Group Stage tournament: 25 April - 28 April&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Phase 3&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;16-player Final Bracket: 3 May - 5 May (awarding CRL Community Points)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can learn more about the Calalas Cup &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fesports.clashroyale.com%2Fnews%2Fcompete-in-the-calalas-cup-2024')"&gt;HERE&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;LPL Clash Royale World Tour 2024&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;LPL World Tour 2024 is a 2-season competition, with each Season having two Phases: Qualifiers &amp;amp; Finals. The tournament will be as follows:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Season 1:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Qualifiers: Dates to be confirmed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Finals: Dates to be confirmed (16-player Final Bracket, awarding CRL Community Points)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Season 2:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Qualifiers: Dates to be confirmed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Finals: Dates to be confirmed (16-player Final Bracket, awarding CRL Community Points)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;GKR 2024 Solo:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;GKR 2024 Solo is a 3-Phase tournament running from 22 July through 4 August. The tournament format is as follows…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Phase 1&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Qualifiers: 22 July - 29 July&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Phase 2&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;64-player Swiss Tournament: 30 July - 31 July&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Phase 3&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;16-player Double Elimination bracket: 1 August - 4 August (awarding CRL Community Points)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://clashroyale.inbox.supercell.com/9jtsgmsiuthj/2V4hBLPRJoOwVLZ92YVZuI/c60b459949ee8ad7898e532bc994bef3/CRL_-_Community_Tournaments_Points_Leaderboard_16x9_8.jpg?w=1920&amp;h=1080&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;CRL Community Points Leaderboard&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See above for the CRL Community Points Leaderboard. This Leaderboard will be updated after the end of each Tournament (GKR 2024 Solo &amp;amp; Calalas Cup), or after the end of each Tournament’s Season (Dragon League by QLASH &amp;amp; LPL Clash Royale World Tour 2024).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As you may have noticed, the final Phase of each of the four CRL Community Tournaments culminates in a 16-player showdown, and the CRL Community Points Leaderboard shows a total of 16 slots. This is because the Top 16 finishers in each Community Tournament will be awarded points towards the CRL Community Leaderboard - the player with the highest placement, and thus, the most Points after the 4 Community Tournaments end, will earn themselves a Golden Ticket and a spot at the #CRL24 World Finals! See the Points breakdown for the Top 16 tournament finishers below:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;1st Place&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;100 Points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;2nd Place&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;80 Points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;3rd Place&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;65 Points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;4th Place&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;50 Points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;5th &amp;amp; 6th Place&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;40 Points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;7th &amp;amp; 8th Place&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;30 Points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;9th - 12th Place&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;20 Points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;13th - 16th Place&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;10 Points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Frequently Asked Questions&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What happens if a tie occurs between multiple players on the Community Points Leaderboard after the final Community Tournament ends?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;There will be a total of 3 tiebreakers in the case two or more players have the same amount of Community Points. Check out how the winner of the Golden Ticket will be determined below:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tiebreaker 1: Player with the most total number of Community Tournament wins&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tiebreaker 2: Player with the most CRL Points (on the CRL Points Leaderboard)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tiebreaker 3: Player with the highest average placement in all Path of Legends Race Seasons&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Can a player win a Golden Ticket via the CRL Community Points Leaderboard if they have already won a Golden Ticket?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;No. A player can only receive a Golden Ticket via the CRL Community Points Leaderboard if they have not already received a Golden ticket via a Monthly Finals or the CRL Points Leaderboard. If the player with the highest-placement on the Community Points Leaderboard has already received a Golden Ticket, the Golden Ticket will be awarded to the player with the next highest-placement&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;
And you are all set!! Visit this article throughout the #CRL24 to know more on the CRL Community Tournaments and Leaderboard, and check out the 2024 Clash Royale League &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=http%3A%2F%2Fsupr.cl%2FRulebook_CRL24')"&gt;Ruleset&lt;/a&gt; for more information. Stay tuned and make sure to follow Clash Royale Esports on &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=http%3A%2F%2Ftwitter.com%2FesportsroyaleEN')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;X&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=http%3A%2F%2Finstagram.com%2Fesportsroyale')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Instagram&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, and visit our &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=http%3A%2F%2Fesports.clashroyale.com')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Website&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; to get all the latest updates!
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;See you in the Arena,&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Clash Royale Esports&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5vjQcEyTV1NVu8lu59bWM8</guid>
      <category>Esports</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRL World Finals are coming to SuperFEST!</title>
      <link>https://youtu.be/8jW-Br9nrnE</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">321iuzGUxlGrTem53YB6Hw</guid>
      <category>Esports</category>
      <enclosure url="https://clashroyale.inbox.supercell.com/9jtsgmsiuthj/47ncT1kYm7sSNF8D7jQTFX/7d344ff37b80c4d8e37faec05f346f61/SuperFest-Esport_Thumbnail_4_1.jpg?w=960&amp;h=540&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 14:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SuperFEST 2024!</title>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://clashroyale.inbox.supercell.com/9jtsgmsiuthj/XlRFBIhimXi5l27BM2Tgf/64ba74f09903968f356e323d96e4c4a8/CRL_-_SuperFEST_AYNTK_.png?w=1920&amp;h=1080&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;SuperFEST 2024 is coming!&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let’s talk about SuperFEST 2024! SuperFEST 2024 is a 3-day event that will host the World Finals of the Clash Royale League, Clash of Clans World Championship &amp;amp; Brawl Stars Championship. It is an in-person, live event that will take place in Helsinki, Finland, where fans can come watch their favorite players and teams fight for supremacy and for their claims as World Champions. As this is the first time that Clash of Clans, Clash Royale and Brawl Stars Esports will come together in one grand event, you’re not going to want to miss this!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;SuperFEST 2024 will take place November 1 - 3! Check out the SuperFEST 2024 announcement video below…&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8jW-Br9nrnE"&gt;📺 [EMBEDDED VIDEO]&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All three events will be played across 3 days and the schedule is as follows…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Clash of Clans World Championship Finals:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Day 1: 10:00 - 13:00 EET&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Day 2: 10:00 - 13:00 EET&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Day 3: 10:00 - 13:00 EET&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Clash Royale League World Finals: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Day 1: 14:00 - 16:30 EET&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Day 2: 14:00 - 16:30 EET&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Day 3: 14:00 - 16:30 EET&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brawl Stars Championship Finals:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Day 1: 17:30 - 22:00 EET&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Day 2: 17:30 - 21:30 EET&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Day 3: 17:30 - 20:30 EET&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Get your tickets now!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Don’t miss out on your opportunity to see history be made! Tickets for SuperFEST 2024 are on sale now - spots are limited, so make sure to secure your ticket as soon as you can! &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Tickets can be purchased &lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fevent.supercell.com%2Fclashroyale%2Fen%2F%3Fpog%3Dtrue')"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;here!&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All the best clash action will be streamed on our event platform, so make sure to bookmark the&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fevent.supercell.com%2Fclashroyale%2Fen%2F%3Fpfg%3Dtrue')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Clash Royale Event Site&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;! Set a reminder and grab your tickets now, and stay tuned for more information related to the Clash Royale League World Finals coming in the future. Make sure to follow &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fx.com%2FEsportsRoyaleEN')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Clash Royale Esports on X&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.instagram.com%2Fesportsroyale%2F%3Fhl%3Den')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Instagram&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, and visit our &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fesports.clashroyale.com%2F')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Website&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; to get all the latest updates!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
See you in the Arena,&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Clash Royale Esports&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5DYdyUBigPvOob6O1cFl6H</guid>
      <category>Esports</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 15:06:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Participate in the LPL Clash Royale World Tour 2024!</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The LPL Clash Royale World Tour 2024 is just about to kick off. Register today as this is your chance to compete against the best players across the globe in the Open Qualifiers!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;Format&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;LPL Clash Royale World Tour 2024 consists of 2 seasons, where you’ll be able to participate in and join the race for the coveted Golden Ticket that will be awarded in the CRL Community Leaderboard. Check out below how each season will be played.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Open Qualifiers&lt;/b&gt; - The Open Qualifiers are your gateway to either enter the Pro Division or the Open Division. The top 4 players from each of the qualifiers will join the Pro Division and the remaining players will enter the Open Division.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Pro Division&lt;/b&gt; - The top 4 players from each of the Open Qualifiers will battle it out in a 16-player double-elimination bracket to get a piece of the &lt;b&gt;US$11,500 Prize Pool &amp;amp; CRL Community Points. &lt;/b&gt;You can see all the Pro Division action LIVE on LPL’s broadcast channels!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Open Division&lt;/b&gt; - Players who don&amp;#39;t qualify for the Pro Division will automatically be placed in the Open Division, where a single-elimination bracket will be played and a &lt;b&gt;US$1,000 Prize Pool &lt;/b&gt;will be up for grabs. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;Schedule&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Per season, there are 4 Open Qualifiers that you can play, welcoming anyone and everyone, and &lt;b&gt;will NOT be region-specific&lt;/b&gt;! Make sure to sign up on the tournament page for all qualifiers so you have the best odds of getting into the Pro Division.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sign up for season 2:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Open Qualifiers - September 14th &amp;amp; 15th&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fgg.letsplay.live%2Ftournament%2Fqualifier1-lpl-clash-royale-world-tour-stage-2-66d7ef70937d450ab79be882')"&gt;Open Qualifiers #1&lt;/a&gt; on September 14th, starting at 09:00 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fgg.letsplay.live%2Ftournament%2Fqualifier-2-lpl-clash-royale-world-tour-stage-2-2024-66d7efe5937d450ab79be98a')"&gt;Open Qualifiers #2&lt;/a&gt; on September 14th, starting at 15:30 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fgg.letsplay.live%2Ftournament%2Fqualifier-3-lpl-clash-royale-world-tour-stage-2-2024-66d7f124378c383aed334706')"&gt;Open Qualifiers #3&lt;/a&gt; on September 15th, starting at 16:00 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fgg.letsplay.live%2Ftournament%2Fqualifier-4-lpl-clash-royale-world-tour-stage-2-2024-66d7f057b8b6c25ea3cb75d0')"&gt;Open Qualifiers #4 &lt;/a&gt;on September 15th, starting at 23:00 UTC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pro and Open Divisions - September 19th &amp;amp; 20th&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;Prize Distribution &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The prize distribution for both seasons of the Clash Royale World Tour 2024&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;will be as follows: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Pro Division:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;1st place: $5,500&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;2nd place: $2,500&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;3rd place: $1,200&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;4th place: $800&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;5th &amp;amp; 6th places: $500&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;7th &amp;amp; 8th places: $250&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Open Division:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;1st place: $500&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;2nd place: $250&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;3rd &amp;amp; 4th places: $125&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;Important Rules &amp;amp; Regulations &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Before you jump into the action, a few key rules to remember: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Players are allowed to participate in more than one tournament unless they have already qualified for the Pro division. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Single Elimination: All Open Qualifier matches follow a single-elimination format.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Make sure to read the &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Flpl-document-storage.s3.ap-southeast-2.amazonaws.com%2FLPL%2BCLASH%2BROYALE%2BWORLD%2BTOUR%2B2024%2BRULESET.pdf')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Rulebook&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;: go through the rules thoroughly under the &amp;quot;Rules&amp;quot; tab to avoid any surprises and to be informed of all the details!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;For more details and updates, join our &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=http%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fletsplaylive')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Discord server&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. This is where you’ll find support, chat with other players, and stay informed with all tournament updates! &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where to watch? &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Pro Division Playoffs will be broadcasted on LetsPlay.Live’s official channels and by some of your favorite content creators. Season 1 playoffs will happen on August 29th &amp;amp; 30th at 13:00 UTC and Season 2 on September 19th &amp;amp; 20th at 13:00 UTC. Bookmark a link below to watch the live broadcast! &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.twitch.tv%2Flpl_play')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;LPL Twitch&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2F%40LetsPlayLive')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;LPL YouTube&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fgg.letsplay.live%2Fwatch')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;LetsPlay.Live platform&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;CRL Community Leaderboard&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The LPL Clash Royale World Tour 2024 is the last announced competition that will be awarding points for the CRL Community Leaderboard, where the winner will secure a Golden Ticket to the CRL24 World Finals!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Per season, and by reaching the Pro Division, you’ll be able to get the following points, based on your performance:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;1st place: 100 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;2nd place: 80 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;3rd place: 65 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;4th place: 50 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;5th-6th places: 40 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;7th-8th places: 30 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;9th-12th places: 20 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;13th-16th places: 10 points&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;
So, are you ready to clash, strategize, and dominate the Arena in the LPL Clash Royale World Tour 2024? &lt;b&gt;Sign up today!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Make sure to follow LetsPlay.Live on &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fx.com%2Flpl_global')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;X&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.instagram.com%2Fletsplaylivehq')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Instagram&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.facebook.com%2Fletsplaylivenz')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Facebook&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, and Clash Royale Esports on &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fx.com%2FEsportsRoyaleEN')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;X&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.instagram.com%2Fesportsroyale%2F')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Instagram&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; to get all the latest updates!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;See you in the Arena,&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Clash Royale Esports&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">18n6WGkKHyi8SSPwW5OFe2</guid>
      <category>Esports</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLAST Royale 2024</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;BLAST is taking esports to the next level with its thrilling events and global reach. Known for bringing together top teams and stars in epic tournaments, BLAST is once again setting the stage for excitement with the upcoming BLAST Bash. During the show, you will be able to watch the best players from all around the world competing in Clash Royale, Clash of Clans, and Brawl Stars.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;a href="https://youtu.be/Newg80l1MY0"&gt;📺 [EMBEDDED VIDEO]&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;BLAST Royale 2024&lt;/b&gt; is an invite-only online tournament for Clash Royale where top players from around the globe will go head-to-head to claim the title of ultimate champion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://clashroyale.inbox.supercell.com/9jtsgmsiuthj/61o4nmI7QI0TaXLgZbpYOj/2db86ca5719379e6295e15411b790493/Format_BlastRoyale.jpg?w=3840&amp;h=2160&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;BLAST Royale 2024 is an exclusive, invite-only tournament where eight of the top players from around the world will face off in a thrilling crew battle into a double-elimination format.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Finals Show:&lt;/b&gt; October 12th-13th&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Prize Pool&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The prize pool for BLAST Royale 2024 is a whopping $15,000!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Invited Players&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stay tuned! &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Watch the Ultimate Face-Off!&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Catch all the action on BLAST’s official &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.twitch.tv%2Fblastpremier')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Twitch&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.tiktok.com%2F%40blasttv')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;TikTok&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; channel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Don’t miss out on the epic action of BLAST Royale 2024! Make sure to follow BLAST on &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fx.com%2FBLASTtv')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;X&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.instagram.com%2Fblastpremier')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Instagram&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, and the &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fblast.tv%2Fsupercell')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;official website&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; to stay in the loop. And for all the latest updates, keep an eye on Clash Royale’s in-game Esports tab, as well as their &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.instagram.com%2Fesportsroyale%2F%3Fhl%3Den')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Instagram&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Ftwitter.com%2FEsportsRoyaleEN')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;X&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fesports.clashroyale.com%2F')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Esports website&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;See you in the Arena,&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Clash Royale Esports&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6k174XfHGHeHRZVlGc7oDF</guid>
      <category>Esports</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 14:39:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dragon League by Qlash: Grand Final!</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Dragon League, organized by &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fx.com%2FQLASH_App')"&gt;QLASH&lt;/a&gt;, reached its final phase on Sunday, September 22nd! During the past six months, this event was a big part of CRL24, offering participants the chance to qualify for the World Finals through 5 out of the 9 Community Tournaments awarding points to the CRL Community Leaderboard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thousands of players competed every month to secure one of the 16 available spots in the Dragon League Monthly Finals. Success in these finals earned them crucial points on the CRL Community Leaderboard, with the top-ranked player from the leaderboard securing a Golden Ticket to the Clash Royale League World Finals. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The path to the Monthly Finals was a grind, with daily tournaments on the QLASH App, progression through the &amp;quot;Path of Dragons Leaderboard,&amp;quot; and survival in the “Dragon’s Breath” tournament. The rigorous selection process has delivered incredible finals!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Five Monthly Finals took place from April to August, each crowning a Champion:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;April:&lt;/b&gt; Mohamed Light&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;May:&lt;/b&gt; LucasXGamer&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;June:&lt;/b&gt; Pedro™&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;July:&lt;/b&gt; Mohamed Light &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;August:&lt;/b&gt; Mohamed Light&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Notably, Mohamed Light won three (out of five) Monthly Finals, while FurkanArabaci consistently placed second in 2 finals, narrowly losing to Mohamed Light.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In addition to the points for the CRL Community Leaderboard, the top 3 players from each Monthly Final earned a spot in the Dragon League Grand Final. And so far, the following 15 players have secured their places in this ultimate showdown:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://clashroyale.inbox.supercell.com/9jtsgmsiuthj/6qVDxBU7PFxit4CyUD294c/43b7b9bd08633db33754006df7e75d55/QUALIFIED-Players_GRAND_FINAL.jpg?w=1280&amp;h=720&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The final 16th spot will be decided via a single-elimination Last Chance Qualifier on &lt;b&gt;September 28th at 14:00 UTC&lt;/b&gt;. With the best players in the world competing, the Dragon League Grand Final promises to be one of the most thrilling events of the year!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;How to join the Last Chance Qualifier&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you want to qualify, you can register to the Last Chance Qualifier on the QLASH App, by &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fqlash.gg%2Fqlash-app-download%2F')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;downloading the App&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and following this &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fdeeplink.qlash.gg%2FKphdKfRMiQjNNMGF9')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;link&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Grand Final&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Dragon League Grand Final will follow the same format as the Monthly Finals, with a 16-player double-elimination tournament being played over 2 days, on&lt;b&gt; October 5th and 6th, starting at 14:00 UTC.&lt;/b&gt;

If you want to find out who will be the Dragon League Champion, make sure to tune in! More details on the event&amp;#39;s casters will be revealed in the next few days.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Prize Pool&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A total of $10,000 will be up for grabs in the Dragon League Grand Final and will be distributed as follows:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;1st place: $5,250&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;2nd place:$2,500&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;3rd place: $1,500&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;4th place: $750&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;To get the latest updates, make sure to follow Clash Royale Esports on&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Ftwitter.com%2FEsportsRoyaleEN')"&gt; &lt;u&gt;X&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.instagram.com%2Fesportsroyale%2F')"&gt; &lt;u&gt;Instagram&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, and QLASH on&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Ftwitter.com%2FQLASH_App')"&gt; &lt;u&gt;X&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, and&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.instagram.com%2Fqlash_clashroyale%2F')"&gt; &lt;u&gt;Instagram&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, join the&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2Fqlash-clashroyale')"&gt; &lt;u&gt;QLASH Discord Server&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, and check the competition’s &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fdrive.google.com%2Ffile%2Fd%2F16E_GJeskxwvHvWluKqEQV0PwggcDtCww%2Fview%3Fusp%3Dsharing')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;rulebook&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; to know more!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;See you in the Arena,&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Clash Royale Esports&lt;/i&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1fIR2P3SO7tyH3rKKtT9Lw</guid>
      <category>Esports</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 15:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 2024 World Finals are coming!</title>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://clashroyale.inbox.supercell.com/9jtsgmsiuthj/7FjX6N80BuXw1Uyj7GGwwo/948737c77f16b614aa41fa414a6a0c30/CRL_-_World_Finals_AYNTK.png?w=1920&amp;h=1080&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The 2024 Clash Royale League year has been a wild ride so far, and all 8 Golden Tickets have been awarded! The top Clash Royale competitors in the world have been battling it out throughout Monthly Competitions and Community tournaments to cement their spot at World Finals - and they haven’t disappointed! And now, it all comes down to one final showdown to see who the best player in the world is!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Let’s take a closer look at the tournament format...&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The 2024 World Finals is a double-elimination bracket tournament, similar to this year’s Monthly Finals, taking place over three days: November 1 - 3. It will take place at SuperFEST, and will occur between the Clash of Clans World Championship Finals and the Brawl Stars Championship Finals on all 3 days. All three competition days will start at 14:00 EET and have a maximum of 5 matches on each day - make sure to take a look at the updated &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fcrl-rules.scescdn.com%2F2024-en')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;World Finals Ruleset&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and visit the &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fesports.clashroyale.com%2Fnews%2Fsuperfest-24')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;SuperFEST Article&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; to take a closer look at the SuperFEST schedule!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;The Road to World Finals&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Throughout the 2024 year, 8 Golden Tickets were up for grabs, signifying 8 available spots at World Finals: 5 Golden Tickets from the Monthly Finals tournaments, 1 Golden Ticket from the China Regional Tournament, 1 Golden Ticket from the CRL Points Leaderboard, and 1 Golden Ticket from the Community Leaderboard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s been a wild and tight race to claim these Golden Tickets, but also without surprises in some areas! In the April, May and June Monthly Finals, Mohamed Light was dominant and took the top spot in all three competitions! He claimed the April Golden Ticket, with Taa and Pedro, the May and June runner-ups. Then the July Monthly Finals came along, and Lucas was able to knock Mohamed Light off of his pedestal! Lucas defeated Mohamed Light in the Grand Finals to end his Monthly Finals win streak and claim the fourth Golden Ticket of the year! In the last Monthly Finals of the year, the August Monthly Finals, two more Golden Tickets were claimed: Guriko claimed the August Monthly Finals, while CAL Sub secured enough points on the CRL Points Leaderboard to claim his Golden Ticket as well! In the China Regional Tournament, the Clash Royale League veteran LCIOP claimed his Golden Ticket and on the Community Tournaments Leaderboard, Ryley took the top spot with a margin of just 20 points!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With all 8 players locked in for the World Finals, it’s time to take a closer look at who will be competing…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://clashroyale.inbox.supercell.com/9jtsgmsiuthj/3RLyZCegSNo81dPY727Lp5/e58a0dfc5ac8968666b8753d009b8d2e/CRL_-_Golden_Ticket_Infographic_16x9.png?w=1920&amp;h=1080&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;The Competitors&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take a look at the 8 players who will be competing at the 2024 World Finals and show your support to who you want to see crowned World champion!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fx.com%2FMohamedLightCr1')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Mohamed Light &lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fx.com%2FTaa_0922')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Taa&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fx.com%2FPedrotmcr')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Pedro&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fx.com%2Flucasxgamercr')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Lucas&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fx.com%2FAksms_')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Guriko&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fx.com%2FSubTm_CR')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Sub&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fx.com%2FRyIey42')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Ryley&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fx.com%2FLciopCRCN')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;LCIOP&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;But that’s not all! Check out the starting bracket to see how they will stack up against each other in the first round!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://clashroyale.inbox.supercell.com/9jtsgmsiuthj/1g5ZEw2uC60bc30Xg2R6R0/f8577c3de8f98f6e6a4f673923842f9a/CRL_-_World_Finals_Bracket_16x9.png?w=1920&amp;h=1080&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Prize Pool&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let’s not forget about the $! The 2024 World Finals is the biggest competition of the year, and the prize pool reflects that - with $500,000 on the line, this is going to be an event to remember! Take a look at the prizing breakdown in the graphic below…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://clashroyale.inbox.supercell.com/9jtsgmsiuthj/Ul54KNzdBWYsBPF3v09VY/d6733393308f1eb2f016a8ae5a2e99a1/CRL_-_World_Finals_Prize_Pool_16x9.png?w=1920&amp;h=1080&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Where to Watch&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The best place to watch the official broadcast of the World Finals is the &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fevent.supercell.com%2Fclashroyale%2Fen%2F%3Fpfg%3Dtrue')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Clash Royale Event Site&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;! On the Event Site, you can choose between 8 different languages to watch - English, Spanish, Portuguese, French, Italian, German, Japanese and Korean! But that’s not all! By linking your Supercell ID, you can earn in-game rewards by making predictions and watching the match action live! Choose your language and check out the Event Site below…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fevent.supercell.com%2Fclashroyale%2Fen%2F%3Fpfg%3Dtrue')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;English&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fevent.supercell.com%2Fclashroyale%2Fes%2F%3Fpfg%3Dtrue')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Spanish&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fevent.supercell.com%2Fclashroyale%2Fpt%2F%3Fpfg%3Dtrue')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Portuguese&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fevent.supercell.com%2Fclashroyale%2Fde%2F%3Fpfg%3Dtrue')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;German&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fevent.supercell.com%2Fclashroyale%2Fit%2F%3Fpfg%3Dtrue')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Italian&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fevent.supercell.com%2Fclashroyale%2Ffr%2F%3Fpfg%3Dtrue')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;French&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fevent.supercell.com%2Fclashroyale%2Fjp%2F%3Fpfg%3Dtrue')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Japanese&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fevent.supercell.com%2Fclashroyale%2Fkr%2F%3Fpfg%3Dtrue')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Korean&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;And that’s it! Set a reminder, grab your popcorn, and lock in for the finale of #CRL24! Stay tuned and make sure to follow &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fx.com%2FEsportsRoyaleEN')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Clash Royale Esports on X&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.instagram.com%2Fesportsroyale%2F%3Fhl%3Den')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Instagram&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, and visit our &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fesports.clashroyale.com%2F')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Website&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; to get all the latest updates!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;See you in the Arena,&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Clash Royale Esports&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3B7f1DVQbxudiUtOVt87ya</guid>
      <category>Esports</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 14:11:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONGRATULATIONS TO THE 2024 WORLD CHAMPION - MOHAMED LIGHT!</title>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://clashroyale.inbox.supercell.com/9jtsgmsiuthj/2JocE53Jh8jeeCH2jxrXOO/ebd2bd9008ddb2ffe0d922738493433f/CRL_-_WF_Champion_Article_16x9.png?w=1920&amp;h=1080&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The #CRL24 year has been a wild ride - Five monthly competitions, multiple Community Tournaments, epic showdowns on the CRL &amp;amp; Community points leaderboards, and a China Qualifier, all led to the World Finals at SuperFest! And now, after three days of the highest-level competitive Clash Royale action…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;The 2024 Clash Royale League World Champion has been crowned!&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;img src="https://clashroyale.inbox.supercell.com/9jtsgmsiuthj/3DETCFtgbcsRXS4NDnmfaV/c012ebf4b726450bd975eacd83fa8c90/CRL_SFEST_-_Champion_TW.png?w=1920&amp;h=1080&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fx.com%2FMohamedLightCr1')"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Mohamed Light&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; has been DOMINANT throughout the 2024 year! In his first three Monthly Finals appearances, he took the top spot, claiming his Golden Ticket and a spot at World Finals in April and retaining his top spot for three months straight! He continued to be a top contender throughout the year - whether it be his second place finishes in the July and August Monthly Finals, first place finishes in the multiple Dragon League and LPL World Tour 2024 Seasons, or securing the top spots on the #CRL24 Points &amp;amp; Community Leaderboards, Mohamed Light was unstoppable!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And then we arrived at the 2024 Clash Royale League World Finals! After dropping only a single game to LCIOP in the first round, he went on to go undefeated against OS Lucas and Ryley in the upper bracket to claim the World Finals trophy. With an impressive record of eight wins and only one loss over three days, there is only one player who deserves the title of WORLD CHAMPION!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://clashroyale.inbox.supercell.com/9jtsgmsiuthj/36O5S5zarlxLyAuXsVJle0/5f068c1737eb5e9ebd1408729d24cd03/CRL_SFEST_-_Bracket__3_.png?w=1920&amp;h=1080&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Mohamed Light has claimed the World Finals trophy and largest share of the $500,000 prize pool!&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;img src="https://clashroyale.inbox.supercell.com/9jtsgmsiuthj/2ztjzp91ysAOBHc5cULxnA/c5bde8d795878fac568c3b56798fc5ce/CRL_-_WF_Prizing_16x9.png?w=1920&amp;h=1080&amp;f=center&amp;fit=fill"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rewatch the epic three-day showdown of Mohamed Light’s road to World Champion!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/live/QO45r5CzEXI?si=l6ZPJaJ09tInLmFG&amp;t=1286"&gt;📺 [EMBEDDED VIDEO]&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/live/-vWwOc69c_c?si=oT6IJ1c4f6sqXh8z&amp;t=875"&gt;📺 [EMBEDDED VIDEO]&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/live/Sa0QOSJ5AVY?si=BV_BY-S_OOW7zXJ4&amp;t=1288"&gt;📺 [EMBEDDED VIDEO]&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A HUGE thank you and congratulations to all players who competed throughout the #CRL24 year - and, of course, to the fans who have been following their journeys as well! The conclusion of the World Finals at SuperFest wraps up the year! Stay tuned to the Clash Royale in-game Esports tab, &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fx.com%2FEsportsRoyaleEN')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Clash Royale Esports on X&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.instagram.com%2Fesportsroyale%2F%3Fhl%3Den')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Instagram&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="javascript:window.sendCommand('OpenWeb?url=https%3A%2F%2Fesports.clashroyale.com%2F')"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Website&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; to learn more about future plans and to make sure you&amp;#39;re up-to-date on everything #CRL related!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;See you in the Arena,&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Clash Royale Esports&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4w4jL8GIX03tVHAiHNi1OG</guid>
      <category>Esports</category>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2024 15:35:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
